{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0000", "tokens": ["The", "role", "of", "China", "in", "the", "Persian", "Gulf", "and", "potential", "cyberthreats", ":"], "text": "The role of China in the Persian Gulf and potential cyberthreats:", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0001", "tokens": ["February", "18", ",", "2020"], "text": "February 18, 2020", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0002", "tokens": ["After", "the", "rise", "of", "tensions", "between", "the", "US", "and", "Iran", "due", "to", "the", "US", "military", "operation", "that", "ended", "the", "life", "of", "the", "Iranian", "General", "Qasem", "Soleimani", "and", "the", "Iraqi", "Commander", "Abu", "Mahdi", "al-Muhandis", "(", "[", "12", "]", ")", ",", "Iran", "carried", "out", "an", "attack", "with", "missiles", "against", "two", "US", "military", "bases", "located", "in", "Iraq", "(", "[", "13", "]", ")", "."], "text": "After the rise of tensions between the US and Iran due to the US military operation that ended the life of the Iranian General Qasem Soleimani and the Iraqi Commander Abu Mahdi al-Muhandis ([12]), Iran carried out an attack with missiles against two US military bases located in Iraq ([13]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0003", "tokens": ["These", "events", "have", "generated", "a", "climate", "of", "uncertainty", "and", "an", "increase", "of", "geopolitical", "risk", "in", "one", "of", "the", "most", "relevant", "areas", ",", "the", "Persian", "Gulf", "."], "text": "These events have generated a climate of uncertainty and an increase of geopolitical risk in one of the most relevant areas, the Persian Gulf.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0004", "tokens": ["This", "fact", "does", "not", "only", "involve", "the", "US", "and", "Iran", ",", "furthermore", "it", "involves", "other", "actors", "with", "a", "high", "influence", "in", "the", "world", "order", "such", "as", "China", "."], "text": "This fact does not only involve the US and Iran, furthermore it involves other actors with a high influence in the world order such as China.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0005", "tokens": ["This", "phenomenon", "could", "provoke", "that", "China", "carries", "out", "certain", "strategies", "to", "keep", "its", "energy", "interests", "safeguarded", "in", "the", "Middle", "East", "area", "."], "text": "This phenomenon could provoke that China carries out certain strategies to keep its energy interests safeguarded in the Middle East area.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0006", "tokens": ["During", "2019", ",", "some", "technical", "traces", "were", "detected", "and", "this", "traces", "where", "potentially", "related", "to", "certain", "APT", "groups", "presumably", "associated", "with", "the", "People", "’", "s", "Republic", "of", "China", "(", "APT10", ")", "that", "would", "be", "carrying", "out", "malicious", "campaigns", "against", "various", "targets", "like", "critical", "infrastructures", " ", "organizations", "among", "others", "(", "[", "14", "]", ")", "(", "[", "15", "]", ")", "."], "text": "During 2019, some technical traces were detected and this traces where potentially related to certain APT groups presumably associated with the People’s Republic of China (APT10) that would be carrying out malicious campaigns against various targets like critical infrastructures  organizations among others ([14]) ([15]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0007", "tokens": ["In", "the", "past", ",", "the", "relationship", "between", "Tehran", "and", "Beijing", "was", "based", "on", "a", "trade", "agreement", "focused", "in", "the", "exchanging", "of", "crude", "oil", "and", "weapons", "(", "[", "19", "]", ")", "."], "text": "In the past, the relationship between Tehran and Beijing was based on a trade agreement focused in the exchanging of crude oil and weapons ([19]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0008", "tokens": ["Regarding", "the", "second", "point", ",", "in", "the", "war", "between", "Iran", "and", "Iraq", "(", "1980", "-", "1988", ")", ",", "when", "the", "targets", "of", "both", "actors", "were", "the", "oil", "stations", "and", "oil", "freighters", ",", "reaching", "the", "blockade", "of", "the", "Strait", "of", "Hormuz", ",", "the", "situation", "began", "to", "be", "unsustainable", "from", "the", "point", "of", "view", "of", "the", "trade", "of", "crude", "."], "text": "Regarding the second point, in the war between Iran and Iraq (1980-1988), when the targets of both actors were the oil stations and oil freighters, reaching the blockade of the Strait of Hormuz, the situation began to be unsustainable from the point of view of the trade of crude.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0009", "tokens": ["In", "order", "to", "reduce", "the", "tension", ",", "the", "USSR", "and", "the", "USA", ",", "agreed", "in", "1985", "to", "cease", "the", "sale", "of", "weapons", "."], "text": "In order to reduce the tension, the USSR and the USA, agreed in 1985 to cease the sale of weapons.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0011", "tokens": ["China", "was", "always", "faithful", "to", "Iran", "to", "keep", "the", "arm", "sales", "operations", "and", "currently", "it", "is", "still", "being", "one", "of", "the", "most", "relevant", "Iran", "’", "s", "partners", "(", "[", "21", "]", ")", "."], "text": "China was always faithful to Iran to keep the arm sales operations and currently it is still being one of the most relevant Iran’s partners ([21]).", "ne_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0012", "tokens": ["The", "Chinese", "interests", "in", "Iran", "directly", "clashed", "with", "the", "long-standing", "confrontation", "between", "the", "USA", "and", "Iran", "since", "the", "fall", "of", "Shah", "M", ".", "Reza", "Pahlavi", "and", "subsequently", "with", "the", "power", "of", "Ayatollah", "R", ".", "Khomeini", "in", "1979", ",", "establishing", "the", "Islamic", "Republic", "of", "Iran", ",", "thus", "Islamic", "Revolution", "ended", "its", "westernization", "."], "text": "The Chinese interests in Iran directly clashed with the long-standing confrontation between the USA and Iran since the fall of Shah M. Reza Pahlavi and subsequently with the power of Ayatollah R. Khomeini in 1979, establishing the Islamic Republic of Iran, thus Islamic Revolution ended its westernization.", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0013", "tokens": ["That", "’", "s", "why", ",", "currently", "the", "new", "commercial", "approach", "between", "the", "US", "and", "China", "comes", "with", "the", "US", "imposition", "to", "try", "to", "finish", "within", "the", "crude", "oil", "trade", "with", "Iran", "."], "text": "That’s why, currently the new commercial approach between the US and China comes with the US imposition to try to finish within the crude oil trade with Iran.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0014", "tokens": ["Consequently", ",", "china", "has", "significantly", "reduced", "its", "crude", "oil", "imports", "from", "Iran", "since", "the", "US", "again", "imposed", "sanctions", "during", "November", "2018", "(", "[", "16", "]", ")", "."], "text": "Consequently, china has significantly reduced its crude oil imports from Iran since the US again imposed sanctions during November 2018 ([16]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0015", "tokens": ["During", "2015", ",", "the", "Obama", "Administration", "carried", "out", "jointly", "with", "Iran", ",", "Germany", ",", "Great", "Britain", ",", "China", ",", "France", "and", "Russia", ",", "the", "Tehran", "nuclear", "agreement", ",", "at", "those", "time", "China", "significantly", "increased", "its", "commercial", "ties", "with", "Iran", "."], "text": "During 2015, the Obama Administration carried out jointly with Iran, Germany, Great Britain, China, France and Russia, the Tehran nuclear agreement, at those time China significantly increased its commercial ties with Iran.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0016", "tokens": ["During", "2016", ",", "Iran", "and", "China", "agreed", "to", "expand", "bilateral", "ties", "and", "increase", "trade", "to", "$", "600", "billion", "by", "2025", "."], "text": "During 2016, Iran and China agreed to expand bilateral ties and increase trade to $ 600 billion by 2025.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-DATE", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0017", "tokens": ["This", "business", "planning", "was", "truncated", "at", "the", "time", "that", "the", "Trump", "Administration", "withdrew", "from", "the", "Nuclear", "Pact", "."], "text": "This business planning was truncated at the time that the Trump Administration withdrew from the Nuclear Pact.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0018", "tokens": ["Chinese", "imports", "of", "Iranian", "crude", "oil", "fell", "from", "650,000", "barrels", "per", "day", "to", "an", "average", "of", "140,000", "barrels", "in", "recent", "months", "(", "[", "16", "]", ")", "."], "text": "Chinese imports of Iranian crude oil fell from 650,000 barrels per day to an average of 140,000 barrels in recent months ([16]).", "ne_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0019", "tokens": ["China", ",", "in", "response", "to", "the", "impossibility", "of", "establishing", "and", "developing", "business", "operations", "with", "Iran", ",", "imported", "a", "total", "of", "76.3", "million", "tons", "of", "crude", "oil", "from", "Saudi", "Arabia", "in", "the", "first", "11", "months", "of", "last", "year", ",", "53%", "more", "than", "in", "the", "same", "period", "of", "2018", "(", "[", "16", "]", ")", "."], "text": "China, in response to the impossibility of establishing and developing business operations with Iran, imported a total of 76.3 million tons of crude oil from Saudi Arabia in the first 11 months of last year, 53% more than in the same period of 2018 ([16]).", "ne_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0020", "tokens": ["On", "the", "other", "hand", ",", "Iranian", "oil", "exports", "fell", "to", "14.4", "million", "tons", "."], "text": "On the other hand, Iranian oil exports fell to 14.4 million tons.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0021", "tokens": ["Moreover", ",", "China", "has", "a", "relative", "neutral", "role", "in", "the", "Iran-USA", "conflict", ",", "Pekin", "is", "trying", "to", "strength", "the", "ties", "with", "Saudi", "Arabia", ",", "looking", "to", "supply", "them", "specific", "military", "material", "and", "weapons", "that", "the", "USA", "does", "not", "supply", "them", "as", "the", "CH", "-", "4", "UAV", "drones", ",", "similar", "to", "the", "American", "MQ", "-", "1", "Predator", "(", "[", "21", "]", ")", "."], "text": "Moreover, China has a relative neutral role in the Iran-USA conflict, Pekin is trying to strength the ties with Saudi Arabia, looking to supply them specific military material and weapons that the USA does not supply them as the CH-4 UAV drones, similar to the American MQ-1 Predator ([21]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0022", "tokens": ["China", "aims", "to", "balance", "its", "crude", "oil", "suppliers", "against", "the", "rise", "of", "instability", "in", "the", "Middle", "East", "."], "text": "China aims to balance its crude oil suppliers against the rise of instability in the Middle East.", "ne_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0023", "tokens": ["In", "addition", ",", "China", "is", "one", "of", "the", "world", "’", "s", "leading", "oil", "consumers", ",", "this", "means", "that", "its", "economy", "has", "an", "important", "high", "dependence", "on", "oil", "."], "text": "In addition, China is one of the world’s leading oil consumers, this means that its economy has an important high dependence on oil.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0024", "tokens": ["As", "can", "be", "seen", "in", "the", "following", "table", ",", "China", "remain", "in", "the", "second", "place", "in", "the", "top", "of", "oil", "consumers", "after", "the", "US", "(", "[", "6", "]", ")", "."], "text": "As can be seen in the following table, China remain in the second place in the top of oil consumers after the US ([6]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0025", "tokens": ["|", "*", "*", "Country", "*", "*", "|", "*", "*", "M", ".", "barrels", "per", "day", "*", "*", "|", "*", "*", "Share", "of", "world", "total", "*", "*", "|"], "text": "| **Country**         | **M. barrels per day**      | **Share of world total** |", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0026", "tokens": ["|", "United", "States", "|", "19.96", "|", "20%", "|"], "text": "|  United States      |  19.96                      |  20%                     |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0027", "tokens": ["|", "China", "|", "13.57", "|", "14%", "|"], "text": "|  China              |  13.57                      |  14%                     |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0028", "tokens": ["|", "India", "|", "4.34", "|", "4%", "|"], "text": "|  India              |  4.34                       |  4%                      |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0029", "tokens": ["|", "Japan", "|", "3.92", "|", "4%", " ", "|"], "text": "|  Japan              |  3.92                       |  4%                      |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0030", "tokens": ["|", "Russia", "|", "3.69", "|", "4%", "|"], "text": "|  Russia             |  3.69                       |  4%                      |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0031", "tokens": ["|", "Saudi", "Arabia", "|", "3.33", "|", "3%", "|"], "text": "|  Saudi Arabia       |  3.33                       |  3%                      |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0032", "tokens": ["|", "Brazil", "|", "3.03", "|", "3%", "|"], "text": "|  Brazil             |  3.03                       |  3%                      |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0033", "tokens": ["|", "South", "Korea", "|", "2.63", "|", "3%", " ", "|"], "text": "|  South Korea        |  2.63                       |  3%                      |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0034", "tokens": ["|", "Germany", "|", "2.45", "|", "2%", "|"], "text": "|  Germany            |  2.45                       |  2%                      |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0035", "tokens": ["|", "Canada", "|", "2.42", "|", "2%", " ", "|"], "text": "|  Canada             |  2.42                       |  2%                      |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0036", "tokens": ["|", "Total", "top", "10", "|", "59.33", "|", "60%", "|"], "text": "|  Total top 10       |  59.33                      |  60%                     |", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0037", "tokens": ["|", "World", "total", "|", "98.76", "|", "|"], "text": "|  World total        |  98.76                      |                          |", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0038", "tokens": ["*", "Illustration", "1", ".", "Oil", "consumption", "(", "2018", ")", "*"], "text": "*Illustration 1. Oil consumption (2018)*", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0039", "tokens": ["Moreover", ",", "as", "can", "be", "seen", "in", "the", "following", "graph", ",", "China", "ranks", "fifth", "in", "the", "ranking", "of", "oil", "producing", "countries", "in", "the", "worldwide", "(", "[", "6", "]", ")", ":"], "text": "Moreover, as can be seen in the following graph, China ranks fifth in the ranking of oil producing countries in the worldwide ([6]):", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0040", "tokens": ["|", "*", "*", "Country", "*", "*", "|", "*", "*", "Million", "barrels", "per", "day", "*", "*", "|", "*", "*", "Share", "of", "world", "total", "*", "*", "|"], "text": "| **Country**         | **Million barrels per day** | **Share of world total** |", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0041", "tokens": ["|", "United", "States", "|", "17.94", "|", "18%", "|"], "text": "| United States       |  17.94                      |   18%                    |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0042", "tokens": ["|", "Saudi", "Arabia", "|", "12.42", "|", "12%", "|"], "text": "| Saudi Arabia        |  12.42                      |   12%                    |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0043", "tokens": ["|", "Russia", "|", "11.40", "|", "11%", "|"], "text": "| Russia              |  11.40                      |   11%                    |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0044", "tokens": ["|", "Canada", "|", " ", "5.38", "|", " ", "5%", "|"], "text": "| Canada              |   5.38                      |    5%                    |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0045", "tokens": ["|", "China", "|", " ", "4.81", "|", " ", "5%", "|"], "text": "| China               |   4.81                      |    5%                    |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0046", "tokens": ["|", "Iraq", "|", " ", "4.62", "|", " ", "5%", "|"], "text": "| Iraq                |   4.62                      |    5%                    |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0047", "tokens": ["|", "Iran", "|", " ", "4.46", "|", " ", "4%", "|"], "text": "| Iran                |   4.46                      |    4%                    |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0048", "tokens": ["|", "United", "Arab", "Emirates", "|", " ", "3.79", "|", " ", "4%", "|"], "text": "| United Arab Emirates|   3.79                      |    4%                    |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0049", "tokens": ["|", "Brazil", "|", " ", "3.43", "|", " ", "3%", "|"], "text": "| Brazil              |   3.43                      |    3%                    |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0050", "tokens": ["|", "Kuwait", "|", " ", "2.91", "|", " ", "3%", "|"], "text": "| Kuwait              |   2.91                      |    3%                    |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0051", "tokens": ["|", "Total", "top", "10", "|", "71.15", "|", " ", "71%", "|"], "text": "| Total top 10        |  71.15                      |    71%                   |", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0052", "tokens": ["|", "World", "total", "|", "100.89", "|", "|"], "text": "| World total         | 100.89                      |                          |", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0053", "tokens": ["*", "Illustration", "2", ".", "Origin", "of", "oil", "imports", "in", "China", ".", "*"], "text": "*Illustration 2. Origin of oil imports in China.*", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0054", "tokens": ["The", "graph", "shows", "us", "that", "a", "significant", "part", "of", "China", "’", "s", "oil", "suppliers", "comes", "from", "politically", "unstable", "regions", "and", "must", "be", "transported", "through", "narrow", "and", "sea", "lanes", "disputed", "with", "other", "States", "with", "high", "military", "competence", "."], "text": "The graph shows us that a significant part of China’s oil suppliers comes from politically unstable regions and must be transported through narrow and sea lanes disputed with other States with high military competence.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0055", "tokens": ["It", "is", "relevant", "for", "China", "to", "keep", "these", "logistic", "access", "roads", "insured", "to", "keep", "its", "development", "and", "economic", "expansion", "."], "text": "It is relevant for China to keep these logistic access roads insured to keep its development and economic expansion.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0056", "tokens": ["In", "addition", ",", "this", "dependence", "on", "foreign", "energy", "resources", "is", "likely", "to", "increase", "considerably", "."], "text": "In addition, this dependence on foreign energy resources is likely to increase considerably.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0057", "tokens": ["It", "is", "expected", "that", "in", "2040", "about", "80%", "of", "the", "oil", "consumed", "by", "China", "will", "come", "from", "other", "States", "(", "[", "7", "]", ")", "."], "text": "It is expected that in 2040 about 80% of the oil consumed by China will come from other States ([7]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0058", "tokens": ["For", "this", "reason", ",", "China", "is", "interested", "in", "investigating", "and", "controlling", "the", "instability", "in", "the", "Middle", "East", ",", "since", "a", "significant", "percentage", "of", "its", "oil", "imports", "come", "from", "Iran", ",", "Iraq", ",", "Saudi", "Arabia", ",", "Oman", "and", "Kuwait", ",", "all", "within", "the", "Persian", "Gulf", "."], "text": "For this reason, China is interested in investigating and controlling the instability in the Middle East, since a significant percentage of its oil imports come from Iran, Iraq, Saudi Arabia, Oman and Kuwait, all within the Persian Gulf.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0059", "tokens": ["To", "maintain", "this", "flow", "of", "energy", "resources", ",", "China", "and", "the", "Saudi", "King", "Salman", "signed", "an", "oil", "trade", "agreement", "for", "$", "65", "billion", "in", "2017", "(", "[", "8", "]", ")", "."], "text": "To maintain this flow of energy resources, China and the Saudi King Salman signed an oil trade agreement for $ 65 billion in 2017 ([8]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0060", "tokens": ["In", "addition", ",", "the", "OBOR", "route", ",", "the", "main", "international", "route", "to", "carry", "out", "the", "transport", "of", "goods", ",", "is", "increasingly", "getting", "consolidated", "and", "more", "functional", "."], "text": "In addition, the OBOR route, the main international route to carry out the transport of goods, is increasingly getting consolidated and more functional.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0061", "tokens": ["!", "[", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "lab52", ".", "io", "/", "blog", "/", "wp-content", "/", "uploads", "/", "2020", "/", "02", "/", "image", "-", "10", ".", "png", ")"], "text": "![](https://lab52.io/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/image-10.png)", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0062", "tokens": ["*", "Illustration", "3", ".", "OBOR", "route", "for", "the", "oil", "trade", ".", "*"], "text": "*Illustration 3. OBOR route for the oil trade.*", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0063", "tokens": ["Currently", ",", "all", "imports", "from", "Iran", "and", "Saudi", "Arabia", "are", "introduced", "into", "China", "through", "the", "Malacca", "Canal", ",", "near", "the", "South", "China", "Sea", "."], "text": "Currently, all imports from Iran and Saudi Arabia are introduced into China through the Malacca Canal, near the South China Sea.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0064", "tokens": ["Probably", ",", "the", "presence", "and", "influence", "of", "China", "in", "the", "Middle", "East", "is", "not", "going", "to", "be", "militarily", "."], "text": "Probably, the presence and influence of China in the Middle East is not going to be militarily.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0065", "tokens": ["However", ",", "it", "constantly", "looks", "for", "diplomatic", "and", "business", "opportunities", "to", "acquire", "organizations", "from", "the", "energy", "sector", "in", "order", "to", "accomplish", "their", "future", "energy", "demands", "(", "[", "9", "]", ")", "."], "text": "However, it constantly looks for diplomatic and business opportunities to acquire organizations from the energy sector in order to accomplish their future energy demands ([9]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0066", "tokens": ["These", "business", "and", "diplomatic", "opportunities", "could", "be", "preceded", "by", "cyber", "espionage", "operations", "with", "the", "purpose", "of", "acquiring", "advantages", "in", "the", "sector", "."], "text": "These business and diplomatic opportunities could be preceded by cyber espionage operations with the purpose of acquiring advantages in the sector.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0067", "tokens": ["Organizations", "in", "the", "energy", "sector", "have", "important", "confidential", "information", "that", "certain", "governments", "may", "be", "highly", "interested", "in", "."], "text": "Organizations in the energy sector have important confidential information that certain governments may be highly interested in.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0068", "tokens": ["The", "energy", "organizations", "which", "are", "located", "in", "certain", "Middle", "East", "locations", "of", "interest", "of", "China", "would", "be", "a", "potential", "target", "of", "cyberespionage", "."], "text": "The energy organizations which are located in certain Middle East locations of interest of China would be a potential target of cyberespionage.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0069", "tokens": ["CAMPAIGN", "AGAINST", "THE", "USA", "ADMINISTRATION", "AND", "THE", "ENERGY", "SECTOR"], "text": "CAMPAIGN AGAINST THE USA ADMINISTRATION AND THE ENERGY SECTOR", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0070", "tokens": ["During", "2019", ",", "a", "malicious", "campaign", "was", "executed", "against", "US", "public", "sector", "organizations", "."], "text": "During 2019, a malicious campaign was executed against US public sector organizations.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0071", "tokens": ["This", "campaign", ",", "due", "to", "the", "macros", "used", ",", "is", "likely", "to", "be", "attributed", "to", "APT10", ",", "a", "group", "allegedly", "linked", "to", "the", "Ministry", "of", "Security", "and", "Intelligence", "of", "China", "(", "[", "1", "]", ")", "(", "[", "18", "]", ")", "."], "text": "This campaign, due to the macros used, is likely to be attributed to APT10, a group allegedly linked to the Ministry of Security and Intelligence of China ([1]) ([18]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0072", "tokens": ["The", "malware", "used", "was", "“", "Lookback", "."], "text": "The malware used was “Lookback.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0073", "tokens": ["The", "spear", "phishing", "carried", "out", "an", "impersonation", "of", "GEC", "(", "Global", "Energy", "Certification", ")", "to", "offer", "certain", "certification", "courses", "(", "[", "2", "]", ")", "."], "text": "The spear phishing carried out an impersonation of GEC (Global Energy Certification) to offer certain certification courses ([2]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0074", "tokens": ["Topic", "which", "would", "be", "highly", "interesting", "for", "critical", "infrastructure", "or", "energy", "professionals", "."], "text": "Topic which would be highly interesting for critical infrastructure or energy professionals.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0075", "tokens": ["Several", "spear", "phishing", "emails", "came", "from", "the", "following", "malicious", "domain", ":", "globalenergycertification", "[", ".", "]", "Net", ".", "The", "same", "domain", "was", "used", "in", "previous", "malicious", "campaigns", "."], "text": "Several spear phishing emails came from the following malicious domain: globalenergycertification[.]Net. The same domain was used in previous malicious campaigns.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0076", "tokens": ["The", "hostile", "actor", "tries", "to", "impersonate", "a", "licensing", "agency", "that", "is", "linked", "to", "the", "public", "sector", "globalenergycertification", "[", ".", "]", "Org", ".", "In", "the", "body", "of", "the", "email", ",", "topics", "are", "included", "to", "impersonate", "the", "“", "Global", "Energy", "Certification", "”", "(", "GEC", ")", "."], "text": "The hostile actor tries to impersonate a licensing agency that is linked to the public sector globalenergycertification[.]Org. In the body of the email, topics are included to impersonate the “Global Energy Certification” (GEC).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0077", "tokens": ["The", "word", "file", "attached", "in", "the", "email", "has", "the", "macros", "that", "once", "is", "downloaded", "and", "executed", "infects", "the", "systems", "of", "the", "victim", "(", "[", "2", "]", ")", "."], "text": "The word file attached in the email has the macros that once is downloaded and executed infects the systems of the victim ([2]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0078", "tokens": ["During", "the", "first", "stages", "of", "the", "infection", "it", "was", "possible", "to", "identify", "that", "the", "attackers", "carried", "out", "a", "reconnaissance", "phase", "through", "SMB", "scans", "on", "the", "port", "445", "."], "text": "During the first stages of the infection it was possible to identify that the attackers carried out a reconnaissance phase through SMB scans on the port 445.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0079", "tokens": ["This", "activity", "was", "carried", "out", "two", "weeks", "before", "to", "the", "reception", "of", "spear", "phishing", "."], "text": "This activity was carried out two weeks before to the reception of spear phishing.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0080", "tokens": ["The", "delivery", "was", "a", "fake", "invitation", "to", "carry", "out", "the", "exam", "to", "get", "the", "Global", "Energy", "Certification", "(", "[", "2", "]", ")", ":"], "text": "The delivery was a fake invitation to carry out the exam to get the Global Energy Certification ([2]):", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0081", "tokens": ["!", "[", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "lab52", ".", "io", "/", "blog", "/", "wp-content", "/", "uploads", "/", "2020", "/", "02", "/", "image", "-", "11", ".", "png", ")"], "text": "![](https://lab52.io/blog/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/image-11.png)", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0082", "tokens": ["*", "Illustration", "4", ".", "Spear", "phishing", "email", "body", "*"], "text": "*Illustration 4. Spear phishing email body*", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0083", "tokens": ["The", "domain", "globalenergycertification", "[", ".", "]", "Net", "resolves", "to", "this", "IP", "79.141.169", "[", ".", "]", "3", "."], "text": "The domain globalenergycertification[.]Net resolves to this IP 79.141.169[.]3.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0084", "tokens": ["In", "the", "following", "chart", "there", "are", "the", "domains", "and", "IPs", "which", "were", "hosted", "with", "their", "respective", "date", "and", "impersonated", "entity", "records", ":"], "text": "In the following chart there are the domains and IPs which were hosted with their respective date and impersonated entity records:", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0085", "tokens": ["|", "*", "*", "IP", "*", "*", "|", "*", "*", "Domain", "*", "*", "|", "*", "*", "Dates", "Registered", "*", "*", "|", "*", "*", "Impersonated", "entity", "*", "*", "|"], "text": "| **IP**          | **Domain**                     | **Dates Registered**         | **Impersonated entity**                                  |", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0086", "tokens": ["|", "79.141.169", "[", ".3", "|", "globalenergycertification", "[", ".", "net", "|", "August", "1", "–", "September", "19", ",", "2019", "|", "Global", "Energy", "Certification", "(", "“", "GEC", "”", ")", "|"], "text": "|  79.141.169[.3  | globalenergycertification [.net| August 1 – September 19, 2019| Global Energy Certification (“GEC”)                      |", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-02-18_the-role-of-china-in__s0087", "tokens": ["|", "103.253.41", "[", ".75", "|", "globalenergycertification", "[", ".", "net", "|", "June", "12", "–", "July", "30", ",", "2019", "|", "Global", "Energy", "Certification", "(", "“", "GEC", "”", ")", "|"], "text": "| 103.253.41 [.75 | globalenergycertification [.net| June 12 – July 30, 2019      | Global Energy Certification (“GEC”)                      |", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
