{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0000", "tokens": ["The", "energy", "reserves", "in", "the", "Eastern", "Mediterranean", "Sea", "and", "a", "malicious", "campaign", "of", "APT10", "against", "Turkey"], "text": "The energy reserves in the Eastern Mediterranean Sea and a malicious campaign of APT10 against Turkey", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "B-LOC"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0001", "tokens": ["May", "14", ",", "2020"], "text": "May 14, 2020", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0002", "tokens": ["Energy", "reserves", "in", "the", "Eastern", "Mediterranean", "Sea", "and", "the", "“", "MEDEAST", "”", "gas", "pipeline", ":"], "text": "Energy reserves in the Eastern Mediterranean Sea and the “MEDEAST” gas pipeline:", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0003", "tokens": ["The", "Mediterranean", "Sea", "has", "become", "an", "increasingly", "relevant", "geostrategic", "topic", "for", "the", "Ministries", "of", "Foreign", "Affairs", "of", "Turkey", ",", "Greece", ",", "Cyprus", ",", "Israel", "and", "even", "China", "due", "to", "the", "controversies", "generated", "during", "the", "last", "decade", "for", "the", "discoveries", "of", "natural", "gas", "resources", "located", "in", "the", "Eastern", "Mediterranean", "seas", "of", "States", "such", "Israel", ",", "Cyprus", "and", "Egypt", "(", "[", "1", "]", ")", "."], "text": "The Mediterranean Sea has become an increasingly relevant geostrategic topic for the Ministries of Foreign Affairs of Turkey, Greece, Cyprus, Israel and even China due to the controversies generated during the last decade for the discoveries of natural gas resources located in the Eastern Mediterranean seas of States such Israel, Cyprus and Egypt ([1]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0004", "tokens": ["The", "presence", "of", "Turkish", "troops", "in", "Libya", "and", "Syria", ",", "and", "the", "Franco-Greek", "alliance", "to", "avoid", "Turkish", "intrusions", "in", "the", "maritime", "territory", "of", "Greece", "show", "the", "relevance", "and", "global", "interest", "in", "energy", "resources", "in", "the", "area", "."], "text": "The presence of Turkish troops in Libya and Syria, and the Franco-Greek alliance to avoid Turkish intrusions in the maritime territory of Greece show the relevance and global interest in energy resources in the area.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0005", "tokens": ["As", "it", "could", "be", "seen", "in", "the", "following", "map", ",", "part", "of", "the", "geostrategic", "conflict", "is", "focused", "on", "the", "Turkish", "EEZ", "."], "text": "As it could be seen in the following map, part of the geostrategic conflict is focused on the Turkish EEZ.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0006", "tokens": ["Turkey", "carried", "out", "an", "agreement", "with", "Libya", "which", "tries", "to", "carry", "out", "an", "expansion", "of", "its", "exclusive", "maritime", "economic", "zones", "(", "[", "2", "]", ")", "."], "text": "Turkey carried out an agreement with Libya which tries to carry out an expansion of its exclusive maritime economic zones ([2]).", "ne_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0007", "tokens": ["It", "is", "relevant", "to", "clarify", "that", "an", "EEZ", "is", "a", "maritime", "zone", "prescribed", "by", "the", "United", "Nations", "Convention", "on", "the", "law", "of", "the", "sea", "over", "which", "a", "state", "has", "special", "rights", "regarding", "the", "exploration", "and", "exploitation", "of", "sea", "resources", ",", "including", "the", "production", "of", "energy", "through", "the", "water", "and", "wind", "(", "[", "3", "]", ")", "(", "[", "17", "]", ")", ":"], "text": "It is relevant to clarify that an EEZ is a maritime zone prescribed by the United Nations Convention on the law of the sea over which a state has special rights regarding the exploration and exploitation of sea resources, including the production of energy through the water and wind ([3]) ([17]):", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0009", "tokens": ["*", "Illustration", "1", ".", "Expansion", "of", "Turkish", "EEZ", "*"], "text": "*Illustration 1.Expansion of Turkish EEZ*", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0010", "tokens": ["The", "expansion", "that", "the", "Turkish", "government", "tries", "to", "carry", "out", "could", "increase", "the", "geopolitical", "risk", "among", "Cypriots", ",", "Greeks", "and", "even", "Israeli", "governments", "."], "text": "The expansion that the Turkish government tries to carry out could increase the geopolitical risk among Cypriots, Greeks and even Israeli governments.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0011", "tokens": ["The", "military", "presence", "in", "the", "area", "by", "those", "States", "could", "be", "seen", "in", "the", "map", "shown", "above", "."], "text": "The military presence in the area by those States could be seen in the map shown above.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0012", "tokens": ["The", "strategy", "of", "increasing", "Turkey", "’", "s", "EEZ", "would", "leave", "without", "an", "important", "part", "of", "the", "continental", "shelf", "Athens", "(", "[", "4", "]", ")", "."], "text": "The strategy of increasing Turkey’s EEZ would leave without an important part of the continental shelf Athens ([4]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0013", "tokens": ["In", "addition", ",", "Cyprus", "is", "significantly", "affected", "by", "this", "EEZ", "’", "s", "expansion", "as", "there", "is", "an", "occupation", "of", "the", "Cyprus", "’", "EEZ", "area", "."], "text": "In addition, Cyprus is significantly affected by this EEZ’s expansion as there is an occupation of the Cyprus’ EEZ area.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0014", "tokens": ["Furthermore", ",", "the", "President", "Erdogan", "has", "publicly", "declared", "that", "his", "oil", "exploration", "projects", "in", "the", "coast", "of", "Cyprus", "will", "not", "cease", "."], "text": "Furthermore, the President Erdogan has publicly declared that his oil exploration projects in the coast of Cyprus will not cease.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0015", "tokens": ["Turkey", "tries", "to", "stablish", "a", "zone", "of", "EEZ", "controlled", "by", "the", "Turkish", "influence", "which", "would", "be", "represented", "as", "in", "the", "following", "map", "(", "[", "5", "]", ")", ":"], "text": "Turkey tries to stablish a zone of EEZ controlled by the Turkish influence which would be represented as in the following map ([5]):", "ne_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0017", "tokens": ["*", "Illustration", "2", ".", "Expansion", "of", "the", "Turkish", "EEZ", "and", "location", "of", "energy", "resources", "*"], "text": "*Illustration 2.Expansion of the Turkish EEZ and location of energy resources*", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0018", "tokens": ["In", "the", "previous", "map", ",", "you", "can", "see", "which", "energy", "exploration", "areas", "are", "located", "in", "Israel", ",", "Cyprus", "and", "Egypt", "."], "text": "In the previous map, you can see which energy exploration areas are located in Israel, Cyprus and Egypt.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0019", "tokens": ["Moreover", ",", "these", "States", "give", "diplomatic", "support", "to", "Cyprus", "and", "Greece", "regarding", "the", "expansion", "’", "s", "conflict", "of", "the", "Turkish", "EEZ", "."], "text": "Moreover, these States give diplomatic support to Cyprus and Greece regarding the expansion’s conflict of the Turkish EEZ.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0020", "tokens": ["Furthermore", ",", "the", "27th", "of", "February", "of", "2020", ",", "Greece", ",", "Cyprus", "and", "Israel", "signed", "an", "agreement", "to", "build", "up", "a", "gas", "pipeline", "to", "transport", "gas", "to", "Europe", "from", "the", "Leviathan", "gas", "reserves", "located", "in", "Israel", "."], "text": "Furthermore, the 27th of February of 2020, Greece, Cyprus and Israel signed an agreement to build up a gas pipeline to transport gas to Europe from the Leviathan gas reserves located in Israel.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0021", "tokens": ["Moreover", ",", "in", "the", "near", "future", "there", "is", "the", "intention", "of", "joining", "to", "the", "pipeline", "the", "extractions", "from", "the", "Cypriot", "gas", "reserves", ",", "Aphrodite", "and", "Calypso", "(", "[", "6", "]", ")", "."], "text": "Moreover, in the near future there is the intention of joining to the pipeline the extractions from the Cypriot gas reserves, Aphrodite and Calypso ([6]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0023", "tokens": ["*", "Illustration", "3", ".", "Mediterranean", "Gas", "Pipeline", "*"], "text": "*Illustration 3.Mediterranean Gas Pipeline*", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0024", "tokens": ["Turkey", "has", "displaced", "several", "warships", "to", "the", "coast", "of", "Cyprus", "in", "order", "to", "carry", "out", "gas", "exploration", "projects", "."], "text": "Turkey has displaced several warships to the coast of Cyprus in order to carry out gas exploration projects.", "ne_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0025", "tokens": ["The", "Eastern", "European", "gas", "pipeline", "reduces", "the", "geopolitical", "power", "of", "Turkey", "as", "it", "tries", "to", "exclude", "Turkey", "from", "any", "participation", "in", "it", "."], "text": "The Eastern European gas pipeline reduces the geopolitical power of Turkey as it tries to exclude Turkey from any participation in it.", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0026", "tokens": ["This", "“", "pipeline", "”", "has", "been", "called", "“", "EastMed", "”", "(", "[", "6", "]", ")", "."], "text": "This “pipeline” has been called “EastMed” ([6]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0027", "tokens": ["However", ",", "during", "March", ",", "Turkey", "will", "put", "an", "offshore", "drilling", "vessel", "in", "order", "to", "continue", "with", "its", "oil", "exploration", "projects", "in", "the", "EEZ", "waters", "of", "Greece", ",", "Cyprus", "and", "the", "EU", "in", "order", "to", "try", "to", "acquire", "in", "the", "future", "the", "role", "of", "gas", "supplier", "for", "the", "EU", "(", "[", "8", "]", ")", "."], "text": "However, during March, Turkey will put an offshore drilling vessel in order to continue with its oil exploration projects in the EEZ waters of Greece, Cyprus and the EU in order to try to acquire in the future the role of gas supplier for the EU ([8]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0028", "tokens": ["Interests", "and", "influence", "of", "China", "in", "the", "Mediterranean", "area", ":"], "text": "Interests and influence of China in the Mediterranean area:", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0029", "tokens": ["China", ",", "unlike", "the", "US", "diplomatic-military", "expansionism", ",", "has", "focused", "its", "expansionist", "strategy", "on", "the", "diplomatic-commercial", "strategy", "."], "text": "China, unlike the US diplomatic-military expansionism, has focused its expansionist strategy on the diplomatic-commercial strategy.", "ne_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0030", "tokens": ["For", "China", ",", "one", "of", "its", "geo-strategically", "key", "regions", ",", "has", "been", "the", "Port", "of", "Piraeus", "of", "Greece", "."], "text": "For China, one of its geo-strategically key regions, has been the Port of Piraeus of Greece.", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0031", "tokens": ["The", "Greek", "government", "tendered", "for", "the", "next", "35", "years", "the", "67%", "of", "the", "Port", "’", "s", "operations", "to", "COSCO", "(", "China", "Ocean", "Shipping", "Company", ")", "for", "368.5", "million", "and", "350", "million", "of", "euros", "to", "be", "invested", "in", "the", "Piraeus", "’", "port", "infrastructure", "(", "[", "9", "]", ")", "."], "text": "The Greek government tendered for the next 35 years the 67% of the Port’s operations to COSCO (China Ocean Shipping Company) for 368.5 million and 350 million of euros to be invested in the Piraeus’ port infrastructure ([9]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0032", "tokens": ["The", "Port", "of", "Piraeus", "represents", "a", "potential", "gate", "of", "all", "the", "commercial", "flow", "that", "comes", "from", "the", "OBOR", "sea", "route", "."], "text": "The Port of Piraeus represents a potential gate of all the commercial flow that comes from the OBOR sea route.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0033", "tokens": ["In", "addition", ",", "during", "November", "of", "2019", ",", "China", "and", "Greece", "signed", "up", "16", "cooperation", "agreements", "of", "different", "matters", ",", "including", "trade", "and", "energy", "investments", "(", "[", "10", "]", ")", "."], "text": "In addition, during November of 2019, China and Greece signed up 16 cooperation agreements of different matters, including trade and energy investments ([10]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0034", "tokens": ["On", "the", "other", "hand", ",", "Cyprus", "signed", "an", "agreement", "with", "a", "consortium", "led", "by", "China", "to", "build", "up", "the", "first", "natural", "gas", "import", "terminal", "in", "Cyprus", "."], "text": "On the other hand, Cyprus signed an agreement with a consortium led by China to build up the first natural gas import terminal in Cyprus.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0035", "tokens": ["The", "terminal", "is", "designed", "to", "convert", "imported", "liquefied", "gas", "into", "a", "gaseous", "form", "to", "be", "used", "in", "energy", "plants", "(", "[", "11", "]", ")", "."], "text": "The terminal is designed to convert imported liquefied gas into a gaseous form to be used in energy plants ([11]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0036", "tokens": ["The", "construction", "is", "being", "developed", "by", "China", "Petroleum", "Pipeline", "Engineering", ",", "Metron", ",", "Hudong-Zhngua", "Shipbuilding", "and", "Wilhelmsen", "Ship", "Management", "."], "text": "The construction is being developed by China Petroleum Pipeline Engineering, Metron, Hudong-Zhngua Shipbuilding and Wilhelmsen Ship Management.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0037", "tokens": ["Construction", "is", "expected", "to", "be", "done", "in", "2022", "."], "text": "Construction is expected to be done in 2022.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0038", "tokens": ["Regarding", "the", "international", "security", ",", "China", "investigates", "Turkey", "’", "s", "relation", "with", "the", "Uighur", "community", "."], "text": "Regarding the international security, China investigates Turkey’s relation with the Uighur community.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0039", "tokens": ["The", "Uyghurs", "are", "Turkish-speaking", "people", "from", "the", "interior", "of", "Asia", "and", "mostly", "of", "them", "have", "Muslim", "religious", "confession", "."], "text": "The Uyghurs are Turkish-speaking people from the interior of Asia and mostly of them have Muslim religious confession.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0040", "tokens": ["The", "Uyghurs", "live", "in", "northwestern", "China", ",", "in", "the", "Uyghur", "autonomous", "region", "of", "Xinjiang", "and", "are", "considered", "a", "threat", "to", "the", "People", "’", "s", "Republic", "of", "China", "as", "they", "are", "considered", "largely", "jihadist", "terrorists", "(", "[", "12", "]", ")", "."], "text": "The Uyghurs live in northwestern China, in the Uyghur autonomous region of Xinjiang and are considered a threat to the People’s Republic of China as they are considered largely jihadist terrorists ([12]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0041", "tokens": ["Turkey", "is", "the", "country", "that", "has", "given", "the", "most", "international", "support", "to", "the", "Uyghur", "community", "."], "text": "Turkey is the country that has given the most international support to the Uyghur community.", "ne_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0042", "tokens": ["Currently", ",", "up", "to", "45,000", "Uyghur", "refugees", "live", "in", "Turkey", "on", "a", "temporary", "visa", "or", "even", "with", "a", "permanent", "residence", "permit", "(", "[", "13", "]", ")", "."], "text": "Currently, up to 45,000 Uyghur refugees live in Turkey on a temporary visa or even with a permanent residence permit ([13]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0043", "tokens": ["Turkey", "’", "s", "foreign", "affairs", "policies", "are", "misaligned", "from", "those", "of", "China", "."], "text": "Turkey’s foreign affairs policies are misaligned from those of China.", "ne_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0044", "tokens": ["The", "possible", "obstruction", "of", "the", "OBOR", "route", "to", "the", "Port", "of", "Piraeus", "and", "the", "collaborative", "policies", "with", "the", "Uyghur", "community", "in", "the", "Xinjiang", "region", "of", "China", "could", "damage", "their", "diplomatic", "relations", "."], "text": "The possible obstruction of the OBOR route to the Port of Piraeus and the collaborative policies with the Uyghur community in the Xinjiang region of China could damage their diplomatic relations.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0045", "tokens": ["Due", "to", "the", "diplomatic", "confrontations", "and", "conflicting", "interests", "of", "the", "two", "countries", ",", "China", "could", "carry", "out", "cyber", "espionage", "operations", "against", "Turkish", "organizations", "and", "institutions", "linked", "to", "diplomacy", ",", "defense", ",", "energy", ",", "telecommunications", "and", "foreign", "trade", "."], "text": "Due to the diplomatic confrontations and conflicting interests of the two countries, China could carry out cyber espionage operations against Turkish organizations and institutions linked to diplomacy, defense, energy, telecommunications and foreign trade.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0046", "tokens": ["Its", "main", "objective", "could", "be", "to", "collect", "confidential", "information", "in", "order", "to", "gain", "advantages", "within", "the", "future", "geostrategic", "movements", "of", "Turkey", "and", "the", "rest", "of", "the", "actors", "involved", "in", "the", "conflicts", "over", "the", "energy", "resources", "located", "in", "the", "Mediterranean", "Sea", "."], "text": "Its main objective could be to collect confidential information in order to gain advantages within the future geostrategic movements of Turkey and the rest of the actors involved in the conflicts over the energy resources located in the Mediterranean Sea.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0047", "tokens": ["Malicious", "campaign", "against", "Turkish", "organizations", ":"], "text": "Malicious campaign against Turkish organizations:", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0048", "tokens": ["A", "malicious", "campaign", "allegedly", "attributed", "to", "APT10", "against", "Turkish", "organizations", "from", "various", "sectors", "such", "as", "telecommunications", "and", "finance", "has", "been", "identified", "by", "Adeo", "in", "January", "of", "2020", "(", "[", "14", "]", ")", "."], "text": "A malicious campaign allegedly attributed to APT10 against Turkish organizations from various sectors such as telecommunications and finance has been identified by Adeo in January of 2020 ([14]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0049", "tokens": ["APT10", "is", "a", "group", "presumably", "attributed", "to", "the", "Ministry", "of", "State", "Security", "of", "China", "(", "[", "15", "]", ")", "."], "text": "APT10 is a group presumably attributed to the Ministry of State Security of China ([15]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0050", "tokens": ["In", "addition", ",", "it", "is", "a", "group", "that", "usually", "targets", "organizations", "from", "various", "sectors", "such", "as", "defense", ",", "energy", ",", "health", ",", "telecommunications", ",", "governments", ",", "military", ",", "shipping", "and", "IT", "(", "[", "16", "]", ")", "."], "text": "In addition, it is a group that usually targets organizations from various sectors such as defense, energy, health, telecommunications, governments, military, shipping and IT ([16]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0051", "tokens": ["It", "has", "been", "identified", "that", "APT10", "usually", "carries", "out", "malicious", "campaigns", "against", "organizations", "that", "could", "damage", "the", "China", "’", "s", "State", "interests", "into", "the", "global", "market", "."], "text": "It has been identified that APT10 usually carries out malicious campaigns against organizations that could damage the China’s State interests into the global market.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0052", "tokens": ["On", "the", "other", "hand", ",", "it", "has", "also", "been", "detected", "that", "APT10", "usually", "carries", "out", "malicious", "campaigns", "against", "organizations", "that", "support", "foundations", "which", "carry", "out", "aid", "projects", "with", "ethnic", "groups", "that", "may", "be", "a", "potential", "threat", "against", "the", "Chinese", "national", "security", ",", "as", "the", "case", "of", "the", "Uyghur", "community", "."], "text": "On the other hand, it has also been detected that APT10 usually carries out malicious campaigns against organizations that support foundations which carry out aid projects with ethnic groups that may be a potential threat against the Chinese national security, as the case of the Uyghur community.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0053", "tokens": ["Moreover", ",", "in", "this", "campaign", "has", "been", "identified", "several", "similarities", "with", "the", "TTP", "published", "in", "other", "APT10", "reports", "in", "2019", "(", "[", "14", "]", ")", "."], "text": "Moreover, in this campaign has been identified several similarities with the TTP published in other APT10 reports in 2019 ([14]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0054", "tokens": ["In", "this", "case", ",", "it", "was", "identified", "that", "this", "campaign", "began", "in", "2016", "and", "the", "initial", "access", "was", "carried", "out", "with", "the", "exploitation", "of", "a", "public", "web", "application", "."], "text": "In this case, it was identified that this campaign began in 2016 and the initial access was carried out with the exploitation of a public web application.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0055", "tokens": ["Summary", "of", "the", "executed", "Kill", "Chain", "(", "[", "14", "]", ")", ":"], "text": "Summary of the executed Kill Chain ([14]):", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0056", "tokens": ["•", "Initial", "access", ":"], "text": "• Initial access:", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0057", "tokens": ["The", "attackers", "deployed", "the", "following", "China", "Chopper4", ",", "JspSpy5", "webshells", "to", "obtain", "a", "foothold", "on", "the", "victim", "’", "s", "network", "that", "they", "used", "to", "execute", "commands", "to", "upload", "files", "to", "the", "target", "machines", "."], "text": "The attackers deployed the following China Chopper4, JspSpy5 webshells to obtain a foothold on the victim’s network that they used to execute commands to upload files to the target machines.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0058", "tokens": ["•", "Reconnaissance", ",", "execution", "and", "theft", "of", "credentials", ":"], "text": "• Reconnaissance, execution and theft of credentials:", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0059", "tokens": ["In", "the", "reconnaissance", "phase", ",", "a", "series", "of", "commands", "were", "launched", "to", "collect", "information", "from", "users", ",", "domains", "and", "shared", "folders", "."], "text": "In the reconnaissance phase, a series of commands were launched to collect information from users, domains and shared folders.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0060", "tokens": ["The", "hostile", "actor", "used", "legitimate", "tools", "of", "the", "Windows", "operating", "systems", "for", "the", "reconnaissance", "stage", ",", "such", "as", "“", "ipconfig.exe", "”", ",", "“", "whoami.exe", "”", ",", "“", "net.exe", "”", ",", "“", "ping.exe", "”", ",", "“", "powershell.exe", "”", "and", "”", "BloodHound", "”", "(", "bloodHound", "is", "not", "a", "legitimate", "binary", "from", "Microsoft", ")", "."], "text": "The hostile actor used legitimate tools of the Windows operating systems for the reconnaissance stage, such as “ipconfig.exe”, “whoami.exe”, “net.exe”, “ping.exe”, “powershell.exe” and ” BloodHound ”(bloodHound is not a legitimate binary from Microsoft).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TOOL", "O", "O", "O", "B-TOOL", "O", "O", "O", "B-TOOL", "O", "O", "O", "B-TOOL", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "B-TOOL", "O", "O", "B-TOOL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TOOL", "O", "O", "O", "B-TOOL", "O", "O", "O", "B-TOOL", "O", "O", "O", "B-TOOL", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "B-TOOL", "O", "O", "B-TOOL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0061", "tokens": ["The", "attacker", "used", "an", "advanced", "tool", "called", "“", "dns.exe", "”", "to", "list", "all", "the", "machines", "that", "were", "registered", "in", "a", "particular", "domain", "."], "text": "The attacker used an advanced tool called “dns.exe” to list all the machines that were registered in a particular domain.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0062", "tokens": ["Regarding", "the", "execution", ",", "the", "hostile", "actor", "implemented", "“", "hTran", "”", "backdoor", "to", "be", "able", "to", "exfiltrate", "information", "."], "text": "Regarding the execution, the hostile actor implemented “hTran” backdoor to be able to exfiltrate information.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0063", "tokens": ["In", "previous", "malicious", "APT10", "campaigns", "against", "Turkey", ",", "this", "executable", "file", "was", "seen", "with", "the", "name", "“", "java.exe", "”", "on", "compromised", "hosts", "."], "text": "In previous malicious APT10 campaigns against Turkey, this executable file was seen with the name “java.exe” on compromised hosts.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0064", "tokens": ["Hostile", "actors", "loaded", "a", "malicious", "DLL", "into", "the", "memory", "of", "a", "legitimate", "binary", "."], "text": "Hostile actors loaded a malicious DLL into the memory of a legitimate binary.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0065", "tokens": ["The", "final", "payload", "is", "injected", "into", "the", "legitimate", "process", "“", "svchost.exe", "”", "."], "text": "The final payload is injected into the legitimate process “svchost.exe”.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "B-CON", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "B-CON", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0066", "tokens": ["It", "was", "identified", "that", "this", "payload", "was", "a", "PlugX", "variant", "or", "a", "CobaltStrike", "Beacon", "as", "a", "post-exploitation", "framework", "."], "text": "It was identified that this payload was a PlugX variant or a CobaltStrike Beacon as a post-exploitation framework.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CON", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "O", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "B-MALWARE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CON", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "O", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "B-MALWARE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0067", "tokens": ["To", "carry", "out", "the", "theft", "of", "credentials", "the", "hostile", "actor", "used", "the", "following", "tools", ":", "“", "QuarksPWdump", "”", "and", "“", "Mimikatz", "”", "."], "text": "To carry out the theft of credentials the hostile actor used the following tools: “QuarksPWdump” and “Mimikatz”.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "O", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "O", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0068", "tokens": ["•", "Lateral", "movements"], "text": "• Lateral movements", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0069", "tokens": ["Through", "the", "lateral", "movements", "they", "were", "able", "to", "compromise", "critical", "servers", "and", "gain", "access", "as", "a", "domain", "administrator", "."], "text": "Through the lateral movements they were able to compromise critical servers and gain access as a domain administrator.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0070", "tokens": ["The", "group", "used", "NTLM", "hashes", "to", "move", "laterally", "."], "text": "The group used NTLM hashes to move laterally.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0071", "tokens": ["They", "used", "the", "tools", "“", "net.exe", "”", ",", "“", "wmic.exe", "”", ",", "“", "psexec.exe", "”", ",", "“", "smbexec", "”", ",", "and", "“", "wmiexec", "”", "."], "text": "They used the tools “net.exe”, “wmic.exe”, “psexec.exe”, “smbexec”, and “wmiexec”.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TOOL", "O", "O", "O", "B-TOOL", "O", "O", "O", "B-TOOL", "O", "O", "O", "B-TOOL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TOOL", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TOOL", "O", "O", "O", "B-TOOL", "O", "O", "O", "B-TOOL", "O", "O", "O", "B-TOOL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TOOL", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0072", "tokens": ["•", "Persistence"], "text": "• Persistence", "ne_tags": ["O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "B-TACTIC"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-TACTIC"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0073", "tokens": ["The", "advanced", "group", "established", "persistence", "in", "certain", "servers", "that", "were", "of", "their", "interest", "and", "deployed", "a", "remote", "access", "Trojans", "such", "as", "“", "QuasarRAT", "”", "and", "“", "PlugX", "”", ",", "moreover", "penetration", "or", "“", "pentesting", "”", "tools", "such", "as", "“", "Cobalt", "Strike", "”", "and", "“", "kerberos", "”", "."], "text": "The advanced group established persistence in certain servers that were of their interest and deployed a remote access Trojans such as “QuasarRAT” and “PlugX”, moreover penetration or “pentesting” tools such as “Cobalt Strike” and “kerberos”.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "O", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "I-MALWARE", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "I-MALWARE", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "O", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "I-MALWARE", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "I-MALWARE", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0074", "tokens": ["•", "C", "&", "C", "connections"], "text": "• C&C connections", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0075", "tokens": ["Hostile", "actors", "used", "two", "different", "ways", "to", "keep", "connections", "with", "C", "&", "C", "servers", "."], "text": "Hostile actors used two different ways to keep connections with C&C servers.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0076", "tokens": ["Once", "the", "vulnerability", "was", "exploited", "to", "establish", "itself", "on", "the", "public", "server", ",", "the", "group", "moved", "to", "the", "“", "terminal", "server", "”", "."], "text": "Once the vulnerability was exploited to establish itself on the public server, the group moved to the “terminal server”.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2020-05-14_the-energy-reserves-in-the__s0077", "tokens": ["To", "establish", "communications", "with", "the", "other", "hosts", "in", "the", "internal", "network", ",", "they", "installed", "an", "SMB", "beacon", "on", "the", "“", "terminal", "server", "”", ",", "using", "it", "as", "a", "bridge", "between", "the", "internal", "network", "and", "the", "C", "&", "C", "server", "."], "text": "To establish communications with the other hosts in the internal network, they installed an SMB beacon on the “terminal server”, using it as a bridge between the internal network and the C&C server.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
