{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0000", "tokens": ["Leviathan", ":", "Geostrategy", "and", "TTP", "(", "Tactics", ",", "Techniques", "and", "Procedures", ")"], "text": "Leviathan: Geostrategy and TTP (Tactics, Techniques and Procedures)", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0001", "tokens": ["May", "30", ",", "2019"], "text": "May 30, 2019", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0003", "tokens": ["-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-"], "text": "----------------------", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0004", "tokens": ["FireEye", "posted", "a", "relevant", "report", "regarding", "one", "of", "the", "most", "active", "threat", "groups", ";", "Leviathan", ",", "also", "known", "as", "TEMP", ",", "Periscope", "or", "TEMP", ".", "Jumper", "."], "text": "FireEye posted a relevant report regarding one of the most active threat groups; Leviathan, also known as TEMP, Periscope or TEMP. Jumper.", "ne_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "B-GROUP", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "B-GROUP", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0005", "tokens": ["This", "APT", "is", "supposedly", "attributed", "to", "the", "Chinese", "government", "(", "[", "1", "]", ")", "."], "text": "This APT is supposedly attributed to the Chinese government ([1]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0006", "tokens": ["In", "this", "report", "is", "shown", "how", "involved", "the", "cyber", "threat", "groups", "are", "in", "the", "geostrategy", "of", "countries", "."], "text": "In this report is shown how involved the cyber threat groups are in the geostrategy of countries.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0007", "tokens": ["China", "is", "the", "main", "supplier", "of", "Europe", "in", "several", "products", "."], "text": "China is the main supplier of Europe in several products.", "ne_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0008", "tokens": ["Approximately", "since", "2009", ",", "China", "has", "aimed", "to", "build", "up", "a", "maritime", "route", "known", "as", "OBOR", "(", "One", "Belt", ",", "One", "Road", ")", "."], "text": "Approximately since 2009, China has aimed to build up a maritime route known as OBOR (One Belt, One Road).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0009", "tokens": ["The", "main", "goal", "of", "this", "project", "is", "to", "develop", "a", "safe", "trading", "corridor", "to", "export", "Chinese", "products", "to", "all", "European", "countries", "in", "a", "fluid", "way", "with", "lower", "international", "tax", "."], "text": "The main goal of this project is to develop a safe trading corridor to export Chinese products to all European countries in a fluid way with lower international tax.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0010", "tokens": ["However", ",", "the", "geostrategic", "trouble", "begins", "in", "the", "South", "Chinese", "Sea", "as", "there", "are", "many", "bordering", "countries", "which", "are", "trying", "to", "control", "the", "area", "by", "carrying", "out", "military", "operations", "with", "their", "navy", "forces", "."], "text": "However, the geostrategic trouble begins in the South Chinese Sea as there are many bordering countries which are trying to control the area by carrying out military operations with their navy forces.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0011", "tokens": ["This", "fact", "poses", "a", "major", "threat", "for", "the", "effectiveness", "of", "the", "OBOR", "route", "."], "text": "This fact poses a major threat for the effectiveness of the OBOR route.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0012", "tokens": ["Presumably", ",", "to", "afford", "the", "conflict", "China", "has", "designed", "a", "strategic", "plan", "to", "quickly", "develop", "its", "navy", "to", "become", "one", "of", "the", "most", "important", "in", "the", "world", "."], "text": "Presumably, to afford the conflict China has designed a strategic plan to quickly develop its navy to become one of the most important in the world.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0013", "tokens": ["Leviathan", "has", "carried", "out", "several", "cyberattacks", "against", "the", "following", "countries", ":", "Cambodia", ",", "Belgium", ",", "Germany", ",", "Hong", "Kong", ",", "Phillipine", "Islands", ",", "Malaysia", ",", "Norway", ",", "Saudi", "Arabia", ",", "Switzerland", "and", "the", "United", "States", "."], "text": "Leviathan has carried out several cyberattacks against the following countries: Cambodia, Belgium, Germany, Hong Kong, Phillipine Islands, Malaysia, Norway, Saudi Arabia, Switzerland and the United States.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0014", "tokens": ["All", "of", "these", "countries", "are", "involved", "in", "the", "OBOR", "route", "."], "text": "All of these countries are involved in the OBOR route.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0015", "tokens": ["The", "fields", "of", "the", "organizations", "which", "have", "been", "cyber", "attacked", "by", "Leviathan", "belong", "to", "the", "logistic", ",", "engineering", ",", "naval", "technology", "and", "naval", "defense", "industry", "(", "[", "1", "]", ")", "."], "text": "The fields of the organizations which have been cyber attacked by Leviathan belong to the logistic, engineering, naval technology and naval defense industry ([1]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0016", "tokens": ["*", "*", "Geostratic", "analysis", "of", "the", "APT", "40", "campaign", ":", "*", "*"], "text": "**Geostratic analysis of the APT 40 campaign:**", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "I-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "I-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0017", "tokens": ["-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-", "-"], "text": "-----------------------------------------------", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0018", "tokens": ["Currently", ",", "there", "are", "relevant", "military", "tensions", "at", "the", "beginning", "of", "the", "route", "."], "text": "Currently, there are relevant military tensions at the beginning of the route.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0019", "tokens": ["In", "geostrategic", "terms", ",", "the", "Paracelso", "and", "Spratlkly", "Islands", "are", "key", "points", "for", "China", "and", "the", "surrounding", "countries", "to", "guarantee", "the", "normal", "vessel", "traffic", "inside", "the", "OBOR", "route", "(", "[", "11", "]", ")", "."], "text": "In geostrategic terms, the Paracelso and Spratlkly Islands are key points for China and the surrounding countries to guarantee the normal vessel traffic inside the OBOR route ([11]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0020", "tokens": ["If", "a", "country", "blocked", "the", "traffic", "of", "this", "area", ",", "the", "negative", "consequences", "for", "the", "Chinese", "and", "the", "world", "’", "s", "economy", "would", "be", "considerably", "dangerous", "."], "text": "If a country blocked the traffic of this area, the negative consequences for the Chinese and the world’s economy would be considerably dangerous.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0021", "tokens": ["A", "general", "map", "of", "the", "whole", "OBOR", "route", "and", "all", "the", "ports", "involved", "is", "shown", "below", "(", "[", "9", "]", ")", "."], "text": "A general map of the whole OBOR route and all the ports involved is shown below ([9]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0022", "tokens": ["As", "can", "be", "seenin", "the", "graph", "above", ",", "currently", "the", "most", "desired", "route", "for", "the", "Chinese", "government", "is", "by", "crossing", "the", "South", "Sea", "through", "the", "Malacca", "Channel", ",", "Arabic", "Sea", "to", "the", "Suez", "Canal", "to", "end", "in", "the", "Port", "of", "Piraeus", "."], "text": "As can be seenin the graph above, currently the most desired route for the Chinese government is by crossing the South Sea through the Malacca Channel, Arabic Sea to the Suez Canal to end in the Port of Piraeus.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0023", "tokens": ["The", "main", "diplomatic", "conflicts", "in", "the", "OBOR", "route", "are", "among", "United", "States", ",", "Malaysia", ",", "Taiwan", ",", "Vietnam", ",", "Japan", ",", "Indonesia", "and", "the", "Philippine", "Islands", "(", "[", "12", "]", ")", "."], "text": "The main diplomatic conflicts in the OBOR route are among United States, Malaysia, Taiwan, Vietnam, Japan, Indonesia and the Philippine Islands ([12]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0024", "tokens": ["The", "following", "map", "shows", "the", "specific", "areas", "that", "are", "diplomatically", "confronted", "with", "China", "and", "the", "rest", "of", "the", "countries", "mentioned", "before", "."], "text": "The following map shows the specific areas that are diplomatically confronted with China and the rest of the countries mentioned before.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0025", "tokens": ["!", "[", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "lab52", ".", "es", "/", "blog", "/", "wp-content", "/", "uploads", "/", "2019", "/", "05", "/", "cao", "-", "2", ".", "jpg", ")"], "text": "![](https://lab52.es/blog/wp-content/uploads/2019/05/cao-2.jpg)", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0026", "tokens": ["*", "Illustration", "1", ":", "OBOR", "Route", "*"], "text": "*Illustration 1: OBOR Route*", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0027", "tokens": ["!", "[", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "lab52", ".", "es", "/", "blog", "/", "wp-content", "/", "uploads", "/", "2019", "/", "05", "/", "cao", "-", "3", "-", "1", ".", "jpg", ")"], "text": "![](https://lab52.es/blog/wp-content/uploads/2019/05/cao-3-1.jpg)", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0028", "tokens": ["*", "Illustration", "2", ":", "International", "waters", "claimed", "by", "countries", ".", "*"], "text": "*Illustration 2: International waters claimed by countries.*", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0029", "tokens": ["In", "this", "APT", "40", "or", "Leviathan", "campaign", ",", "the", "countries", "that", "received", "cyberattacks", "were", "USA", ",", "Malaysia", ",", "Cambodia", ",", "Brunei", ",", "Philippine", "Islands", "and", "Hong", "Kong", "."], "text": "In this APT 40 or Leviathan campaign, the countries that received cyberattacks were USA, Malaysia, Cambodia, Brunei, Philippine Islands and Hong Kong.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "B-GROUP", "I-GROUP", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "B-GROUP", "I-GROUP", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0030", "tokens": ["The", "relation", "among", "the", "States", "involved", "in", "this", "geostrategic", "conflict", "in", "the", "Chinese", "Sea", "and", "the", "organizations", "that", "have", "been", "targeted", "by", "APT", "40", "is", "highly", "strong", "."], "text": "The relation among the States involved in this geostrategic conflict in the Chinese Sea and the organizations that have been targeted by APT 40 is highly strong.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "I-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "I-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0031", "tokens": ["Moreover", ",", "it", "is", "important", "to", "mention", "that", "Saudi", "Arabia", ",", "Germany", ",", "Norway", "and", "UK", "has", "been", "targeted", "by", "Leviathan", "(", "[", "1", "]", ")", "."], "text": "Moreover, it is important to mention that Saudi Arabia, Germany, Norway and UK has been targeted by Leviathan ([1]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0032", "tokens": ["!", "[", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "lab52", ".", "es", "/", "blog", "/", "wp-content", "/", "uploads", "/", "2019", "/", "05", "/", "cao", "-", "414", ".", "png", ")"], "text": "![](https://lab52.es/blog/wp-content/uploads/2019/05/cao-414.png)", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0033", "tokens": ["*", "Illustration", "3", ":", "SouthEast", "countries", "targeted", "by", "Leviathan", "*"], "text": "*Illustration 3: SouthEast countries targeted by Leviathan*", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0034", "tokens": ["APT", "40", "has", "designed", "and", "carried", "out", "this", "campaign", "with", "the", "main", "goal", "of", "collecting", "classified", "information", "from", "navy", "and", "defense", "organizations", "."], "text": "APT 40 has designed and carried out this campaign with the main goal of collecting classified information from navy and defense organizations.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["B-GROUP", "I-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-GROUP", "I-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0035", "tokens": ["With", "this", "classified", "information", ",", "China", ",", "supposedly", "expects", "to", "develop", "its", "navy", "infrastructure", "to", "reach", "its", "aim", "of", "becoming", "a", "significant", "military", "power", "with", "high", "competencies", "in", "“", "blue", "waters", "”", "or", "oceanic", "waters", "(", "[", "13", "]", ")", "."], "text": "With this classified information, China, supposedly expects to develop its navy infrastructure to reach its aim of becoming a significant military power with high competencies in “blue waters” or oceanic waters ([13]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0036", "tokens": ["The", "following", "graph", "shows", "the", "evolution", "of", "the", "Chinese", "naval", "military", "development", "."], "text": "The following graph shows the evolution of the Chinese naval military development.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0037", "tokens": ["As", "it", "is", "shown", ",", "in", "the", "last", "20", "years", "the", "Chinese", "Army", "has", "exponentially", "developed", "their", "military", "tools", "and", "navy", "resources", "(", "[", "10", "]", ")", "."], "text": "As it is shown, in the last 20 years the Chinese Army has exponentially developed their military tools and navy resources ([10]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0038", "tokens": ["China", "is", "trying", "to", "be", "efficient", "and", "competitive", "in", "military", "terms", "as", "the", "United", "States", "."], "text": "China is trying to be efficient and competitive in military terms as the United States.", "ne_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0039", "tokens": ["!", "[", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "lab52", ".", "es", "/", "blog", "/", "wp-content", "/", "uploads", "/", "2019", "/", "05", "/", "cao", "-", "5", "-", "2", "-", "1024x538", ".", "png", ")"], "text": "![](https://lab52.es/blog/wp-content/uploads/2019/05/cao-5-2-1024x538.png)", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0040", "tokens": ["*", "Illustration", "4", ":", "Comparison", "between", "the", "US", "military", "resources", "and", "the", "Chinese", "military", "resources", ".", "*"], "text": "*Illustration 4: Comparison between the US military resources and the Chinese military resources.*", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0041", "tokens": ["FireEye", "considers", "that", "presumably", ",", "Leviathan", "is", "an", "APT", "associated", "to", "the", "Chinese", "government", "and", "its", "main", "task", "and", "duties", "are", "focused", "on", "carrying", "out", "cyber-attacks", "to", "collect", "classified", "information", "."], "text": "FireEye considers that presumably, Leviathan is an APT associated to the Chinese government and its main task and duties are focused on carrying out cyber-attacks to collect classified information.", "ne_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0042", "tokens": ["Among", "some", "of", "the", "evidence", "collected", "to", "conclude", "the", "attribution", "of", "this", "campaign", "was", "the", "Chinese", "time", "zone", "(", "UTC", "+", "8", ")", ",", "as", "the", "majority", "of", "the", "operations", "were", "executed", "in", "this", "gap", "of", "time", "."], "text": "Among some of the evidence collected to conclude the attribution of this campaign was the Chinese time zone (UTC+8), as the majority of the operations were executed in this gap of time.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0043", "tokens": ["Whois", "”", "data", "has", "also", "been", "collected", "from", "the", "domains", "suggesting", "that", "the", "infrastructure", "is", "located", "in", "China", "."], "text": "Whois” data has also been collected from the domains suggesting that the infrastructure is located in China.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0044", "tokens": ["Futhermore", ",", "some", "APT", "40", "IP", "have", "been", "identified", "and", "localized", "in", "China", "as", "112.66.188", "[", ".", "]", "28", "which", "is", "associated", "with", "a", "Chinese", "VPN", "."], "text": "Futhermore, some APT 40 IP have been identified and localized in China as 112.66.188[.]28 which is associated with a Chinese VPN.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "I-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "I-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0045", "tokens": ["As", "can", "be", "seen", "in", "the", "following", "graph", ",", "this", "address", "is", "connected", "to", "a", "Chinese", "server", "from", "Telecom", "located", "in", "Haian", "."], "text": "As can be seen in the following graph, this address is connected to a Chinese server from Telecom located in Haian.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0046", "tokens": ["Although", "the", "geolocation", "of", "that", "kind", "of", "service", "and", "the", "location", "of", "an", "IP", "is", "not", "a", "determinant", "element", "to", "get", "an", "attribution", ",", "in", "this", "case", "there", "is", "another", "fact", "that", "reinforces", "the", "theory", "that", "China", "carried", "out", "the", "cyberattacks", "."], "text": "Although the geolocation of that kind of service and the location of an IP is not a determinant element to get an attribution, in this case there is another fact that reinforces the theory that China carried out the cyberattacks.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0047", "tokens": ["It", "is", "important", "to", "mention", "that", "the", "Command", "and", "Control", "that", "was", "intercepted", "by", "FireEye", "was", "configured", "in", "Chinese", "."], "text": "It is important to mention that the Command and Control that was intercepted by FireEye was configured in Chinese.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0048", "tokens": ["!", "[", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "lab52", ".", "es", "/", "blog", "/", "wp-content", "/", "uploads", "/", "2019", "/", "05", "/", "8682AAB1", "-", "416D", "-", "4FB6", "-", "B739", "-", "89D65CE1008B.jpg", ")"], "text": "![](https://lab52.es/blog/wp-content/uploads/2019/05/8682AAB1-416D-4FB6-B739-89D65CE1008B.jpg)", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0049", "tokens": ["*", "Illustration", "5", ":", "Análisis", "con", "maltego", "de", "la", "IP", "112.66.160.20", "*"], "text": "*Illustration 5: Análisis con maltego de la IP 112.66.160.20*", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0050", "tokens": ["LIFE", "CYCLE"], "text": "LIFE CYCLE", "ne_tags": ["O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0051", "tokens": ["In", "the", "following", "part", ",", "there", "is", "a", "brief", "description", "about", "each", "stage", "followed", "by", "this", "threat", "group", "(", "[", "1", "]", ")", "."], "text": "In the following part, there is a brief description about each stage followed by this threat group ([1]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0052", "tokens": ["First", "part", "of", "the", "cyberattack", ":"], "text": "First part of the cyberattack:", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0053", "tokens": ["Several", "techniques", "used", "in", "this", "phase", "have", "been", "identified", "."], "text": "Several techniques used in this phase have been identified.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0054", "tokens": ["However", ",", "there", "are", "some", "techniques", "that", "have", "been", "used", "in", "the", "majority", "of", "this", "campaign", "’", "s", "cases", "."], "text": "However, there are some techniques that have been used in the majority of this campaign’s cases.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0055", "tokens": ["*", "Web", "Shells", ":", "In", "organizations", "that", "were", "previously", "compromised", ",", "usually", "the", "threat", "actors", "leavesleft", "the", "servers", "infected", ",", "just", "in", "case", "they", "want", "to", "exfiltrate", "more", "information", "in", "the", "future", ",", "as", "they", "still", "guarantee", "access", "to", "the", "system", "."], "text": "* Web Shells: In organizations that were previously compromised, usually the threat actors leavesleft the servers infected, just in case they want to exfiltrate more information in the future, as they still guarantee access to the system.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0056", "tokens": ["*", "Spear", "Phishing", ":", "The", "threat", "group", "uses", "phishing", "emails", "to", "targeted", "organizations", "."], "text": "* Spear Phishing: The threat group uses phishing emails to targeted organizations.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0057", "tokens": ["In", "these", "campaigns", "they", "made", "use", "of", "links", "to", "Google", "drive", "to", "download", "the", "malware", "in", "their", "spear", "phishing", "emails", "with", "malicious", "attachments", "."], "text": "In these campaigns they made use of links to Google drive to download the malware in their spear phishing emails with malicious attachments.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0058", "tokens": ["In", "their", "campaigns", "they", "mostly", "exploited", "the", "following", "vulnerabilities", ":"], "text": "In their campaigns they mostly exploited the following vulnerabilities:", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0059", "tokens": ["*"], "text": "*", "ne_tags": ["O"], "nc_tags": ["O"], "te_tags": ["O"], "ce_tags": ["O"], "ci_tags": ["O"], "all_tags": ["O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0060", "tokens": ["o", "   ", "CVE", "-", "2012", "-", "0158", "[", "2", "]"], "text": "o    CVE-2012-0158 [2]", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0061", "tokens": ["o", "   ", "CVE", "-", "2017", "-", "0199", "[", "3", "]"], "text": "o    CVE-2017-0199 [3]", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0062", "tokens": ["o", "   ", "CVE", "-", "2017", "-", "8759", "[", "5", "]"], "text": "o    CVE-2017-8759 [5]", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0063", "tokens": ["o", "   ", "CVE", "-", "2017", "-", "11882", "[", "6", "]"], "text": "o    CVE-2017-11882 [6]", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0064", "tokens": ["Process", "to", "compromise"], "text": "Process to compromise", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0065", "tokens": ["When", "the", "threat", "actor", "has", "been", "able", "to", "access", "the", "systems", "they", "would", "try", "to", "get", "alternative", "points", " ", "of", "access", "to", "the", "organization", "by", "expanding", "new", "backdoors", "or", "collecting", "user", "credentials", "."], "text": "When the threat actor has been able to access the systems they would try to get alternative points  of access to the organization by expanding new backdoors or collecting user credentials.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0066", "tokens": ["Specifically", ",", "the", "new", "backdoors", "used", "in", "the", "organization", "(", "[", "8", "]", ")", ":"], "text": "Specifically, the new backdoors used in the organization ([8]):", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0067", "tokens": ["China", "Chopper", ":", "Web", "Shell", "that", "is", "able", "to", "execute", "code", "on", "compromised", "computers", "."], "text": "China Chopper: Web Shell that is able to execute code on compromised computers.", "ne_tags": ["B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["B-MALWARE", "I-MALWARE", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "all_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-MALWARE", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0068", "tokens": ["This", "way", ",", "attackers", "can", "send", "commands", "via", "HTTP", "POST", "to", "infect", "servers", "."], "text": "This way, attackers can send commands via HTTP POST to infect servers.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0069", "tokens": ["The", "web", "Shell", "is", "able", "to", ":", "list", "directories", ",", "access", "databases", "and", "in", "general", "any", "action", "allowed", "by", ".", "NET", "."], "text": "The web Shell is able to: list directories, access databases and in general any action allowed by .NET.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0070", "tokens": ["Photo", "(", "also", "called", ":", "“", "dersubi", "”", ")", ":", "A", "DLL", "that", "is", "the", "backdoor", ",", "this", "one", "has", "the", "following", "capabilities", ":"], "text": "Photo (also called: “dersubi”): A DLL that is the backdoor, this one has the following capabilities:", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0071", "tokens": ["▪", "Listing", "directories", ",", "files", "and", "storage", "."], "text": "▪ Listing directories, files and storage.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0072", "tokens": ["▪", "Opening", "of", "reverse", "shells", "."], "text": "▪ Opening of reverse shells.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0073", "tokens": ["▪", "Taking", "screenshots", ",", "video", "and", "audio", "recording", "."], "text": "▪ Taking screenshots, video and audio recording.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0074", "tokens": ["▪", "Processing", "creation"], "text": "▪ Processing creation", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0075", "tokens": ["▪", "Modifying", "registry", "keys", "."], "text": "▪ Modifying registry keys.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0076", "tokens": ["▪", "Keylogging"], "text": "▪ Keylogging", "ne_tags": ["O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE"], "all_tags": ["O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0077", "tokens": ["▪", "Modifying", "files", "."], "text": "▪ Modifying files.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0078", "tokens": ["Badflick", ":", "Backdoor", "with", "the", "ability", "to", "modify", "the", "file", "system", ",", "open", "reverse", "shells", "and", "modify", "the", "configuration", "of", "the", "C2", "."], "text": "Badflick: Backdoor with the ability to modify the file system, open reverse shells and modify the configuration of the C2.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0079", "tokens": ["Airbreak", "(", "also", "called", "“", "Orz", "”", ")", ":", "Malware", "which", "was", "programmed", "in", "JavaScript", ",", "with", "the", "capability", "to", "receive", "commands", "to", "execute", "from", "legitimate", "pages", "(", "[", "7", "]", ")", "."], "text": "Airbreak (also called “Orz”): Malware which was programmed in JavaScript, with the capability to receive commands to execute from legitimate pages ([7]).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["B-MALWARE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-MALWARE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0080", "tokens": ["Beacon", ":", "It", "is", "a", "malware", "distributed", "by", "the", "Cobalt", "Strike", "platform", "."], "text": "Beacon: It is a malware distributed by the Cobalt Strike platform.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["B-MALWARE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "I-MALWARE", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-MALWARE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "I-MALWARE", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0081", "tokens": ["This", "malware", "is", "able", "to", "inject", "and", "execute", "codes", "and", "exfiltrate", "files", "."], "text": "This malware is able to inject and execute codes and exfiltrate files.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0082", "tokens": ["The", "group", "usually", "collects", "corporate", "VPN", "credentials", ",", "as", "well", "as", "other", "remote", "administration", "services", "(", "see", ":", "SSH", ",", "RDP", ",", "etc", "."], "text": "The group usually collects corporate VPN credentials, as well as other remote administration services (see: SSH, RDP, etc.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0083", "tokens": ["Escalation", "of", "privileges", ":"], "text": "Escalation of privileges:", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0084", "tokens": ["As", "in", "the", "previous", "stage", ",", "the", "group", "uses", "different", "tools", "and", "techniques", "to", "carry", "out", " ", "the", "privilege", "escalation", "."], "text": "As in the previous stage, the group uses different tools and techniques to carry out  the privilege escalation.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0085", "tokens": ["In", "this", "stage", ",", "the", "group", "mainly", "focuses", "on", "collecting", "credentials", "from", "both", "open", "and", "private", "sources", ",", "passwords", "and", "hashes", "."], "text": "In this stage, the group mainly focuses on collecting credentials from both open and private sources, passwords and hashes.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0086", "tokens": ["We", "could", "expect", "the", "use", "of", "tools", "like", "HOMEFRY", ",", "a", "tool", "based", "on", "Badflick", "and", "Airbreak", "with", "the", "ability", "to", "obtain", "and", "crack", "passwords", "."], "text": "We could expect the use of tools like HOMEFRY, a tool based on Badflick and Airbreak with the ability to obtain and crack passwords.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0087", "tokens": ["As", "well", "as", "the", "use", "of", "native", "legitimate", "tools", "such", "as", "Windows", "Credential", "Editor", "or", "ProcDump", "."], "text": "As well as the use of native legitimate tools such as Windows Credential Editor or ProcDump.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TOOL", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TOOL", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0088", "tokens": ["Internal", "recognition", ":"], "text": "Internal recognition:", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0089", "tokens": ["Leviathan", "collects", "passwords", "to", "access", "other", "computers", "in", "the", "network", "."], "text": "Leviathan collects passwords to access other computers in the network.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["B-GROUP", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC"], "all_tags": ["B-GROUP", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0090", "tokens": ["Moreover", ",", "the", "attackers", "take", "advantage", "of", "the", "native", "services", "of", "the", "system", "that", "would", "be", "activated", "by", "(", "RDP", ",", "SSH", ",", "etc", ".", ")", "."], "text": "Moreover, the attackers take advantage of the native services of the system that would be activated by (RDP, SSH, etc.).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0091", "tokens": ["Specifically", ",", "some", "of", "the", "TTPs", "associated", "with", "this", "stage", "would", "be", ":"], "text": "Specifically, some of the TTPs associated with this stage would be:", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0092", "tokens": ["•", "MURKYSHELL", ":", "malware", "capable", "of", "scanning", "ports", "and", "network", "enumerations", "."], "text": "• MURKYSHELL: malware capable of scanning ports and network enumerations.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "B-MALWARE", "O", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-MALWARE", "O", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0093", "tokens": ["•", "Use", "of", "native", "Windows", "tools", "such", "as", "net.exe"], "text": "• Use of native Windows tools such as net.exe", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TOOL"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TOOL"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0094", "tokens": ["•", "Use", "of", "web", "shells", "in", "the", "internal", "network", ",", "as", "internal", "servers", "usually", "are", "less", "secure", "than", "external", "servers", "."], "text": "• Use of web shells in the internal network, as internal servers usually are less secure than external servers.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-05-30_leviathan-geostrategy-and-ttp-technical__s0095", "tokens": ["Lateral", "movement", ":"], "text": "Lateral movement:", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "O"]}
