{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0000", "tokens": ["WIRTE", "Group", "attacking", "the", "Middle", "East"], "text": "WIRTE Group attacking the Middle East", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0001", "tokens": ["April", "02", ",", "2019"], "text": "April 02, 2019", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0002", "tokens": ["The", "Intelligence", "Development", "Group", "of", "[", "S2", "Grupo", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "s2grupo.es", "/", "en", "/", "home", "/", ")", "has", "carried", "out", "an", "investigation", "on", "an", "actor", "from", "whom", "LAB52", "has", "not", "been", "able", "to", "find", "references", "or", "similarities", "in", "open", "sources", "and", "who", "has", "been", "identified", "as", "*", "*", "WIRTE", "*", "*", "."], "text": "The Intelligence Development Group of [S2 Grupo](https://s2grupo.es/en/home/) has carried out an investigation on an actor from whom LAB52 has not been able to find references or similarities in open sources and who has been identified as **WIRTE**.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0003", "tokens": ["The", "DFIR", "(", "Digital", "Forensics", "and", "Incident", "Response", ")", "team", "of", "S2", "Grupo", "first", "identified", "this", "actor", "in", "August", "2018", "and", "since", "then", "the", "follow-up", "has", "been", "carried", "out", "during", "the", "last", "few", "months", "."], "text": "The DFIR (Digital Forensics and Incident Response) team of S2 Grupo first identified this actor in August 2018 and since then the follow-up has been carried out during the last few months.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0004", "tokens": ["This", "group", "attacks", "the", "Middle", "East", "and", "does", "not", "use", "very", "sophisticated", "mechanisms", ",", "at", "least", "in", "the", "campaign", "started", "in", "August", "2018", "which", "was", "monitored", "."], "text": "This group attacks the Middle East and does not use very sophisticated mechanisms, at least in the campaign started in August 2018 which was monitored.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0005", "tokens": ["It", "is", "considered", "unsophisticated", "by", "the", "fact", "that", "the", "scripts", "are", "unobtrusive", ",", "communications", "go", "unencrypted", "by", "HTTP", ",", "they", "use", "Powershell", "(", "increasingly", "monitored", ")", ",", "and", "so", "on", "."], "text": "It is considered unsophisticated by the fact that the scripts are unobtrusive, communications go unencrypted by HTTP, they use Powershell (increasingly monitored), and so on.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0006", "tokens": ["Despite", "this", "apparently", "unsophisticated", "modus", "operandi", "compared", "to", "other", "actors", ",", "they", "manage", "to", "infect", "their", "victims", "and", "carry", "out", "their", "objectives", "."], "text": "Despite this apparently unsophisticated modus operandi compared to other actors, they manage to infect their victims and carry out their objectives.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0007", "tokens": ["In", "addition", ",", "as", "will", "be", "seen", "during", "the", "report", ",", "the", "detection", "rate", "of", "some", "of", "the", "scripts", "in", "December", "2018", "by", "the", "main", "antivirus", "manufacturers", "is", "low", ",", "an", "aspect", "that", "must", "be", "highlighted", "."], "text": "In addition, as will be seen during the report, the detection rate of some of the scripts in December 2018 by the main antivirus manufacturers is low, an aspect that must be highlighted.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0008", "tokens": ["We", "must", "be", "aware", "that", "once", "these", "scripts", "are", "executed", ",", "it", "is", "when", "the", "behavior", "analysis", "of", "many", "solutions", "will", "detect", "them", ",", "but", "this", "fact", "has", "not", "been", "studied", "by", "LAB52", "."], "text": "We must be aware that once these scripts are executed, it is when the behavior analysis of many solutions will detect them, but this fact has not been studied by LAB52.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0009", "tokens": ["This", "actor", "in", "all", "the", "artifacts", "analyzed", "shows", "his", "victims", "a", "decoy", "document", "in", "Arabic", "with", "different", "themes", "."], "text": "This actor in all the artifacts analyzed shows his victims a decoy document in Arabic with different themes.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0010", "tokens": ["During", "the", "report", "these", "documents", "will", "be", "analyzed", "and", "who", "could", "be", "the", "objectives", "depending", "on", "the", "topic", "dealt", "with", "in", "the", "document", "."], "text": "During the report these documents will be analyzed and who could be the objectives depending on the topic dealt with in the document.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0011", "tokens": ["#", "#", "#", "Technical", "analysis"], "text": "### Technical analysis", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0012", "tokens": ["As", "indicated", "above", ",", "during", "the", "month", "of", "August", "2018", "S2", "Grupo", "CERT", "we", "managed", "an", "incident", "aimed", "at", "the", "diplomacy", "of", "different", "Middle", "Eastern", "countries", "."], "text": "As indicated above, during the month of August 2018 S2 Grupo CERT we managed an incident aimed at the diplomacy of different Middle Eastern countries.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0013", "tokens": ["The", "attackers", "used", "a", "malware", "made", "in", "Visual", "Basic", "Script", "(", "VBS", ")", "as", "a", "tool", "to", "control", "the", "victim", "."], "text": "The attackers used a malware made in Visual Basic Script (VBS) as a tool to control the victim.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0014", "tokens": ["Starting", "from", "the", "study", "of", "this", "VBS", "from", "S2", "Grupo", "CERT", ",", "the", "monitoring", "of", "this", "group", "was", "started", ",", "finding", "in", "other", "sources", "other", "artifacts", "from", "the", "same", "group", "but", "with", "different", "decoy", "documents", "and", "with", "different", "strategies", "of", "execution", ",", "persistence", ",", "and", "so", "on", "."], "text": "Starting from the study of this VBS from S2 Grupo CERT, the monitoring of this group was started, finding in other sources other artifacts from the same group but with different decoy documents and with different strategies of execution, persistence, and so on.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0015", "tokens": ["S2", "Grupo", "does", "not", "have", "enough", "information", "to", "make", "any", "type", "of", "attribution", "or", "authorship", "."], "text": "S2 Grupo does not have enough information to make any type of attribution or authorship.", "ne_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0016", "tokens": ["It", "is", "associated", "that", "these", "artifacts", "are", "related", "because", "they", "reflect", "similarities", "from", "a", "technical", "and", "temporal", "point", "of", "view", "and", "because", "of", "the", "decoy", "documents", "used", ",", "since", "sometimes", "they", "are", "identical", "."], "text": "It is associated that these artifacts are related because they reflect similarities from a technical and temporal point of view and because of the decoy documents used, since sometimes they are identical.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0017", "tokens": ["One", "aspect", "observed", "during", "the", "investigation", "is", "that", "the", "attackers", "after", "running", "the", "VBS", "used", "it", "as", "an", "Empire", "post-exploitation", "framework", "(", "<", "https", ":", "/", "/", "github.com", "/", "EmpireProject", "/", "Empire", ">", ")", "."], "text": "One aspect observed during the investigation is that the attackers after running the VBS used it as an Empire post-exploitation framework (<https://github.com/EmpireProject/Empire>).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0018", "tokens": ["A", "total", "of", "five", "scripts", "plus", "the", "one", "involved", "in", "the", "incident", "could", "be", "collected", "."], "text": "A total of five scripts plus the one involved in the incident could be collected.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0019", "tokens": ["Below", "we", "detail", "the", "main", "characteristics", "of", "each", "."], "text": "Below we detail the main characteristics of each.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0020", "tokens": ["#", "#", "#", "#", "Script", "1", ":", "617bbc71e5f0a645cbb8eeb6d4a1ece96ba0860c8ab5deda6a795e6ad244607a"], "text": "#### Script 1: 617bbc71e5f0a645cbb8eeb6d4a1ece96ba0860c8ab5deda6a795e6ad244607a", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0021", "tokens": ["This", "first", "file", "can", "be", "seen", "in", "Virus", "Total", "and", "has", "a", "low", "detection", "(", "4", "/", "58", ")", "."], "text": "This first file can be seen in Virus Total and has a low detection (4/58).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0022", "tokens": ["The", "last", "analysis", "took", "place", "on", "12", "/", "12", "/", "2018", "."], "text": "The last analysis took place on 12/12/2018.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0023", "tokens": ["!", "[", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "lab52", ".", "es", "/", "blog", "/", "wp-content", "/", "uploads", "/", "2019", "/", "04", "/", "wirte_img01", ".", "png", ")"], "text": "![](https://lab52.es/blog/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/wirte_img01.png)", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0024", "tokens": ["In", "this", "case", "the", "file", "was", "uploaded", "from", "Palestine", "to", "Virus", "Total", ":"], "text": "In this case the file was uploaded from Palestine to Virus Total:", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0025", "tokens": ["!", "[", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "lab52", ".", "es", "/", "blog", "/", "wp-content", "/", "uploads", "/", "2019", "/", "04", "/", "wirte_img02", "-", "1", ".", "png", ")"], "text": "![](https://lab52.es/blog/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/wirte_img02-1.png)", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0026", "tokens": ["In", "the", "image", "you", "can", "see", "that", "it", "was", "uploaded", "through", "the", "web", ",", "from", "PS", "(", "Palestine", ")", "and", "also", "that", "it", "was", "uploaded", "for", "the", "first", "time", "on", "*", "*", "5", "Aug", ".", "2018", "*", "*", "."], "text": "In the image you can see that it was uploaded through the web, from PS (Palestine) and also that it was uploaded for the first time on **5 Aug. 2018**.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0027", "tokens": ["Network", "communication", "occurs", "over", "HTTP", "to", "the", "*", "*", "micorsoft", "[", ".", "]", "store", "*", "*", "domain", "to", "TCP", "/", "2082", "port", "."], "text": "Network communication occurs over HTTP to the **micorsoft[.]store** domain to TCP/2082 port.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0028", "tokens": ["This", "domain", "since", "it", "exists", "has", "resolved", "to", "the", "following", "ip", "addresses", ":"], "text": "This domain since it exists has resolved to the following ip addresses:", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0029", "tokens": ["*", "104.31.78.17"], "text": "* 104.31.78.17", "ne_tags": ["O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0030", "tokens": ["*", "104.31.79.17"], "text": "* 104.31.79.17", "ne_tags": ["O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0031", "tokens": ["*", "185.86.79.243"], "text": "* 185.86.79.243", "ne_tags": ["O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0032", "tokens": ["Currently", "resolves", "to", "a", "Cloudflare", "address", "."], "text": "Currently resolves to a Cloudflare address.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0033", "tokens": ["Port", "2082", "is", "one", "of", "the", "ports", "allowed", "by", "Cloudflare", "for", "HTTP", "traffic", "."], "text": "Port 2082 is one of the ports allowed by Cloudflare for HTTP traffic.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0034", "tokens": ["It", "should", "be", "noted", "that", "the", "first", "IP", "address", "185.86.79.243", "is", "geolocated", "in", "Ukraine", "."], "text": "It should be noted that the first IP address 185.86.79.243 is geolocated in Ukraine.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0035", "tokens": ["This", "IP", "address", "has", "been", "assigned", "to", "different", "domains", ",", "among", "them", "the", "malicious", "one", "."], "text": "This IP address has been assigned to different domains, among them the malicious one.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0036", "tokens": ["Apparently", "the", "attackers", "changed", "their", "IP", "address", "and", "hid", "behind", "Cloudflare", "at", "some", "point", "."], "text": "Apparently the attackers changed their IP address and hid behind Cloudflare at some point.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0037", "tokens": ["In", "this", "script", "this", "communication", "information", "is", "all", "in", "the", "*", "*", "RunPld", "(", ")", "function", "*", "*", "."], "text": "In this script this communication information is all in the **RunPld() function**.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0038", "tokens": ["This", "function", "aims", "to", "download", "the", "powershell", "code", "from", "the", "command", "and", "control", "server", "and", "execute", "it", ":"], "text": "This function aims to download the powershell code from the command and control server and execute it:", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0039", "tokens": ["!", "[", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "lab52", ".", "es", "/", "blog", "/", "wp-content", "/", "uploads", "/", "2019", "/", "04", "/", "wirte_cod01", ".", "png", ")"], "text": "![](https://lab52.es/blog/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/wirte_cod01.png)", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0040", "tokens": ["Another", "common", "function", "in", "these", "scripts", "is", "the", "writeDOC", "function", "."], "text": "Another common function in these scripts is the writeDOC function.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0041", "tokens": ["This", "function", "decodes", "the", "decoy", "document", ",", "write", "it", "to", "disk", "and", "show", "it", "to", "the", "victim", "."], "text": "This function decodes the decoy document, write it to disk and show it to the victim.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0042", "tokens": ["This", "document", "is", "encoded", "in", "base64", "and", "embedded", "in", "the", "script", "itself", "in", "a", "variable", "."], "text": "This document is encoded in base64 and embedded in the script itself in a variable.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0043", "tokens": ["!", "[", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "lab52", ".", "es", "/", "blog", "/", "wp-content", "/", "uploads", "/", "2019", "/", "04", "/", "wirte_cod02", ".", "png", ")"], "text": "![](https://lab52.es/blog/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/wirte_cod02.png)", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0044", "tokens": ["The", "VBS", "script", "copies", "itself", "to", "APPDATA", "through", "the", "*", "*", "copyVBS", "(", ")", "*", "*", "function", ":"], "text": "The VBS script copies itself to APPDATA through the **copyVBS()** function:", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0045", "tokens": ["!", "[", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "lab52", ".", "es", "/", "blog", "/", "wp-content", "/", "uploads", "/", "2019", "/", "04", "/", "wirte_cod03", ".", "png", ")"], "text": "![](https://lab52.es/blog/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/wirte_cod03.png)", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0046", "tokens": ["*", "*", "The", "script", "itself", "does", "not", "establish", "persistence", "*", "*", "in", "its", "first", "execution", ",", "so", "either", "the", "attackers", "deploy", "it", "later", "when", "they", "execute", "powershell", "or", "fix", "it", "by", "transporting", "this", "script", "."], "text": "**The script itself does not establish persistence** in its first execution, so either the attackers deploy it later when they execute powershell or fix it by transporting this script.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0047", "tokens": ["The", "script", "once", "copied", "to", "APPDATA", "will", "have", "the", "following", "name", ":", "*", "*", "Update.vbs", "*", "*", "."], "text": "The script once copied to APPDATA will have the following name: **Update.vbs**.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0048", "tokens": ["On", "the", "other", "hand", ",", "if", "the", "script", "is", "running", "from", "APPDATA", "it", "does", "not", "show", "the", "document", "and", "only", "executes", "the", "RunPld", "(", ")", "function", "which", "is", "the", "backdoor", "in", "powershell", "and", "that", "has", "been", "detailed", "previously", "."], "text": "On the other hand, if the script is running from APPDATA it does not show the document and only executes the RunPld() function which is the backdoor in powershell and that has been detailed previously.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0049", "tokens": ["If", "it", "is", "not", "being", "executed", "from", "APPDATA", "it", "shows", "the", "DOC", "file", "", "decoy", "", ",", "it", "copies", "and", "executes", "the", "backdoor", "(", "script", "in", "powershell", ")", "."], "text": "If it is not being executed from APPDATA it shows the DOC file decoy, it copies and executes the backdoor (script in powershell).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0050", "tokens": ["When", "the", "victim", "executes", "the", "VBS", "file", ",", "a", "Word", "document", "will", "be", "opened", "with", "the", "following", "content", "(", "you", "can", "see", "on", "the", "left", "in", "Arabic", "and", "next", "to", "it", "the", "translation", "made", "by", "Google", "Translate", ")", ":"], "text": "When the victim executes the VBS file, a Word document will be opened with the following content (you can see on the left in Arabic and next to it the translation made by Google Translate):", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0051", "tokens": ["!", "[", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "lab52", ".", "es", "/", "blog", "/", "wp-content", "/", "uploads", "/", "2019", "/", "04", "/", "wirte_en_img01", ".", "png", ")"], "text": "![](https://lab52.es/blog/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/wirte_en_img01.png)", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0052", "tokens": ["The", "document", "we", "have", "shown", "is", "intended", "to", "simulate", "that", "it", "was", "sent", "from", "the", "Ministry", "of", "Foreign", "Affairs", "of", "Saudi", "Arabia", "."], "text": "The document we have shown is intended to simulate that it was sent from the Ministry of Foreign Affairs of Saudi Arabia.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0053", "tokens": ["Presumably", ",", "it", "seems", "that", "the", "addressee", "was", "the", "Ministry", "of", "Awqaf", "and", "Islamic", "Affairs", "of", "Kuwait", ",", "since", "(", "Kuwait", "", "Jeddah", ")", "appears", "in", "the", "very", "signature", "of", "the", "document", "."], "text": "Presumably, it seems that the addressee was the Ministry of Awqaf and Islamic Affairs of Kuwait, since (Kuwait  Jeddah) appears in the very signature of the document.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0054", "tokens": ["It", "was", "also", "apparently", "addressed", "to", "the", "Kuwaiti", "Consulate", "of", "the", "Cooperation", "Council", "of", "the", "Arab", "States", "of", "the", "Gulf", ",", "a", "highly", "important", "body", "within", "the", "countries", "of", "the", "Persian", "Gulf", "."], "text": "It was also apparently addressed to the Kuwaiti Consulate of the Cooperation Council of the Arab States of the Gulf, a highly important body within the countries of the Persian Gulf.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0055", "tokens": ["The", "text", "mentions", "that", "attached", ",", "the", "recipient", "will", "find", "a", "document", "from", "the", "Saudi", "Ministry", "of", "Foreign", "Affairs", "called", "", "Hajj", "affairs", "", ",", "which", "is", "of", "interest", "to", "all", "those", "Arab", "countries", "that", "have", "citizens", "who", "have", "interests", "in", "carrying", "out", "the", "pilgrimage", "to", "the", "Mecca", "."], "text": "The text mentions that attached, the recipient will find a document from the Saudi Ministry of Foreign Affairs called Hajj affairs, which is of interest to all those Arab countries that have citizens who have interests in carrying out the pilgrimage to the Mecca.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0056", "tokens": ["In", "addition", ",", "it", "encourages", "recipients", "to", "forward", "the", "document", "to", "other", "government", "organizations", "in", "countries", "with", "interests", "linked", "to", "the", "", "Hajj", "", "that", "have", "been", "approved", "by", "the", "same", "Ministry", "of", "Culture", "of", "Saudi", "Arabia", "."], "text": "In addition, it encourages recipients to forward the document to other government organizations in countries with interests linked to the Hajj that have been approved by the same Ministry of Culture of Saudi Arabia.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0057", "tokens": ["Presumably", ",", "the", "author", "intends", "to", "generate", "an", "infection", "among", "the", "", "partner", "states", "", "of", "Saudi", "Arabia", ";", "*", "*", "the", "", "target", "", "of", "the", "issuer", "could", "be", "the", "members", "of", "the", "diplomatic", "corps", "of", "countries", "with", "interest", "in", "the", "", "Hajj", "", "*", "*", "and", "especially", "the", "diplomats", "who", "are", "part", "of", "the", "Cooperation", "Council", "of", "the", "Arab", "States", "of", "the", "Gulf", ",", "since", "the", "issuer", "promotes", "the", "forwarding", "of", "the", "document", "to", "all", "interested", "parties", "."], "text": "Presumably, the author intends to generate an infection among the partner states of Saudi Arabia; **the target of the issuer could be the members of the diplomatic corps of countries with interest in the Hajj** and especially the diplomats who are part of the Cooperation Council of the Arab States of the Gulf, since the issuer promotes the forwarding of the document to all interested parties.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0058", "tokens": ["There", "are", "five", "fundamental", "pillars", "within", "the", "religion", "of", "Islam", "."], "text": "There are five fundamental pillars within the religion of Islam.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0059", "tokens": ["One", "of", "them", "is", "the", "", "Hajj", "", ",", "which", "implies", "that", "all", "Muslims", "must", "visit", "Mecca", "at", "least", "once", "in", "their", "lifetime", "."], "text": "One of them is the Hajj, which implies that all Muslims must visit Mecca at least once in their lifetime.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0060", "tokens": ["This", "monument", "is", "located", "in", "the", "Jeddah", "region", "within", "Saudi", "Arabia", "."], "text": "This monument is located in the Jeddah region within Saudi Arabia.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0061", "tokens": ["*", "*", "The", "", "Hajj", "", "is", "significantly", "relevant", "to", "Muslims", "around", "the", "world", "*", "*", "."], "text": "**The Hajj is significantly relevant to Muslims around the world**.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0062", "tokens": ["Consequently", ",", "this", "text", "is", "attractive", "and", "of", "interest", "to", "both", "Shi", "", "ite", "and", "Sunni", "Muslims", "."], "text": "Consequently, this text is attractive and of interest to both Shiite and Sunni Muslims.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0063", "tokens": ["*", "*", "The", "date", "of", "issuance", "of", "the", "document", "is", "relevant", "*", "*", "as", "it", "was", "held", "in", "August", ",", "approximately", "two", "weeks", "before", "the", "great", "pilgrimage", ",", "just", "when", "thousands", "of", "people", "of", "Muslim", "faith", "would", "begin", "the", "pilgrimage", "to", "Jeddah", "in", "Saudi", "Arabia", "."], "text": "**The date of issuance of the document is relevant** as it was held in August, approximately two weeks before the great pilgrimage, just when thousands of people of Muslim faith would begin the pilgrimage to Jeddah in Saudi Arabia.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0064", "tokens": ["Consequently", ",", "the", "chances", "of", "a", "possible", "victim", "opening", "the", "document", "increase", "significantly", "."], "text": "Consequently, the chances of a possible victim opening the document increase significantly.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0065", "tokens": ["#", "#", "#", "#", "Script", "2", ":", "b4c20b56059a6c6762b4c99d04eb9177cb0a4707c58ef575817fb8b702f162aa"], "text": "#### Script 2: b4c20b56059a6c6762b4c99d04eb9177cb0a4707c58ef575817fb8b702f162aa", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0066", "tokens": ["This", "file", "in", "Virus", "Total", "has", "a", "low", "detection", ",", "2", "/", "56", ",", "and", "the", "last", "analysis", "took", "place", "on", "1", "Dec", ".", "2018", "."], "text": "This file in Virus Total has a low detection, 2/56, and the last analysis took place on 1 Dec. 2018.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0067", "tokens": ["!", "[", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "lab52", ".", "es", "/", "blog", "/", "wp-content", "/", "uploads", "/", "2019", "/", "04", "/", "wirte_img04", ".", "png", ")"], "text": "![](https://lab52.es/blog/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/wirte_img04.png)", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0068", "tokens": ["In", "this", "case", "the", "file", "has", "been", "uploaded", "from", "Palestine", "to", "Virus", "Total", ":"], "text": "In this case the file has been uploaded from Palestine to Virus Total:", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0069", "tokens": ["!", "[", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "lab52", ".", "es", "/", "blog", "/", "wp-content", "/", "uploads", "/", "2019", "/", "04", "/", "wirte_img05", ".", "png", ")"], "text": "![](https://lab52.es/blog/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/wirte_img05.png)", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0070", "tokens": ["In", "the", "image", "you", "can", "see", "that", "it", "was", "uploaded", "through", "the", "web", ",", "from", "PS", "(", "Palestine", ")", "and", "also", "that", "it", "has", "been", "uploaded", "for", "the", "first", "time", "on", "*", "*", "08", "/", "25", "/", "2018", "*", "*", "."], "text": "In the image you can see that it was uploaded through the web, from PS (Palestine) and also that it has been uploaded for the first time on **08/25/2018**.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0071", "tokens": ["The", "network", "communication", "in", "this", "case", "is", "also", "produced", "by", "HTTP", "to", "the", "domain", "*", "*", "micorsoft", "[", ".", "]", "store", "*", "*", "to", "the", "port", "tcp", "/", "2082", "."], "text": "The network communication in this case is also produced by HTTP to the domain **micorsoft[.]store** to the port tcp/2082.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "B-ORG", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0072", "tokens": ["In", "this", "case", "the", "script", "has", "exactly", "the", "same", "code", "as", "the", "hash", "", "617bbc71e5f0a645cbb8eeb6d4a1ece96ba0860c8ab5deda6a795e6ad244607a", "", "."], "text": "In this case the script has exactly the same code as the hash 617bbc71e5f0a645cbb8eeb6d4a1ece96ba0860c8ab5deda6a795e6ad244607a.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0073", "tokens": ["The", "only", "thing", "that", "varies", "is", "the", "decoy", "document", "that", "we", "can", "see", "below", ":"], "text": "The only thing that varies is the decoy document that we can see below:", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0074", "tokens": ["!", "[", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "lab52", ".", "es", "/", "blog", "/", "wp-content", "/", "uploads", "/", "2019", "/", "04", "/", "wirte_img06", ".", "png", ")"], "text": "![](https://lab52.es/blog/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/wirte_img06.png)", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0075", "tokens": ["The", "information", "presented", "in", "the", "document", "is", "directly", "related", "to", "security", "issues", "and", "internal", "political", "affairs", "of", "Palestine", "."], "text": "The information presented in the document is directly related to security issues and internal political affairs of Palestine.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0076", "tokens": ["The", "main", "actors", "mentioned", "in", "the", "text", "are", "Hamas", ",", "Al", "Fatah", "and", "the", "Palestinian", "government", "."], "text": "The main actors mentioned in the text are Hamas, Al Fatah and the Palestinian government.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0077", "tokens": ["The", "information", "is", "an", "analytical", "summary", "of", "the", "current", "political", "situation", "in", "Palestine", "and", "even", "analyzes", "in", "geostrategic", "terms", "some", "current", "aspects", "."], "text": "The information is an analytical summary of the current political situation in Palestine and even analyzes in geostrategic terms some current aspects.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0078", "tokens": ["In", "addition", ",", "the", "document", "informs", "about", "the", "potential", "political", "strategies", "that", "the", "previously", "mentioned", "actors", "could", "undertake", "in", "the", "future", "."], "text": "In addition, the document informs about the potential political strategies that the previously mentioned actors could undertake in the future.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0079", "tokens": ["This", "type", "of", "information", "is", "highly", "relevant", "for", "*", "*", "diplomats", "with", "political", "interests", "in", "the", "geographical", "area", "of", "Gaza", "and", "Palestine", "*", "*", "."], "text": "This type of information is highly relevant for **diplomats with political interests in the geographical area of Gaza and Palestine**.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0080", "tokens": ["Consequently", ",", "it", "might", "be", "feasible", "for", "the", "document", "", "s", "target", "audience", "to", "be", "diplomats", ",", "politicians", "and", "professionals", "from", "the", "defense", "sector", "."], "text": "Consequently, it might be feasible for the documents target audience to be diplomats, politicians and professionals from the defense sector.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "lab52_2019-04-02_wirte-group-attacking-the-middle__s0081", "tokens": ["#", "#", "#", "#", "Script", "3", ":", "b906f3c19c19e1b20b2d00bfb82b5453d5386d63b4db901ecade0f33dd38326a"], "text": "#### Script 3: b906f3c19c19e1b20b2d00bfb82b5453d5386d63b4db901ecade0f33dd38326a", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
