{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0000", "tokens": ["Ugg", "Boots", "4", "Sale", ":", "A", "Tale", "of", "Palestinian-Aligned", "Espionage"], "text": "Ugg Boots 4 Sale: A Tale of Palestinian-Aligned Espionage", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0001", "tokens": ["February", "08", ",", "2022"], "text": "February 08, 2022", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0002", "tokens": ["#", "#", "#", "Key", "Takeaways"], "text": "### Key Takeaways", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0003", "tokens": ["*", "TA402", ",", "a", "likely", "Palestinian-aligned", "advance", "persistent", "threat", "actor", ",", "has", "recently", "engaged", "in", "campaigns", "leveraging", "a", "new", "implant", ",", "dubbed", "by", "Proofpoint", "analysts", "as", "NimbleMamba", "."], "text": "* TA402, a likely Palestinian-aligned advance persistent threat actor, has recently engaged in campaigns leveraging a new implant, dubbed by Proofpoint analysts as NimbleMamba.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0004", "tokens": ["*", "NimbleMamba", "is", "likely", "a", "replacement", "for", "the", "group", "’", "s", "previously", "used", "LastConn", "implant", "."], "text": "* NimbleMamba is likely a replacement for the group’s previously used LastConn implant.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0005", "tokens": ["*", "These", "campaigns", "have", "a", "complex", "attack", "chain", "that", "leverages", "geofencing", "and", "URL", "redirects", "to", "legitimate", "sites", "in", "order", "to", "bypass", "detection", "efforts", "."], "text": "* These campaigns have a complex attack chain that leverages geofencing and URL redirects to legitimate sites in order to bypass detection efforts.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0006", "tokens": ["#", "#", "#", "Overview"], "text": "### Overview", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0007", "tokens": ["In", "late", "2021", ",", "Proofpoint", "analysts", "identified", "a", "complex", "attack", "chain", "targeting", "Middle", "Eastern", "governments", ",", "foreign", "policy", "think", "tanks", ",", "and", "a", "state-affiliated", "airline", "."], "text": "In late 2021, Proofpoint analysts identified a complex attack chain targeting Middle Eastern governments, foreign policy think tanks, and a state-affiliated airline.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "B-DATE", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0008", "tokens": ["Over", "three", "months", ",", "Proofpoint", "observed", "three", "subtle", "variations", "of", "this", "attack", "chain", "."], "text": "Over three months, Proofpoint observed three subtle variations of this attack chain.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0009", "tokens": ["Proofpoint", "attributes", "these", "campaigns", "to", "TA402", ",", "an", "actor", "commonly", "tracked", "as", " ", "[", "Molerats", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "www.proofpoint.com", "/", "us", "/", "blog", "/", "threat-insight", "/", "new-ta402", "-", "molerats-malware-targets-governments-middle-east", ")", " ", "and", "believed", "to", "be", "operating", "in", "the", "interest", "of", "the", "Palestinian", "Territories", "."], "text": "Proofpoint attributes these campaigns to TA402, an actor commonly tracked as [Molerats](https://www.proofpoint.com/us/blog/threat-insight/new-ta402-molerats-malware-targets-governments-middle-east) and believed to be operating in the interest of the Palestinian Territories.", "ne_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0010", "tokens": ["Based", "on", "Proofpoint", "’", "s", "research", ",", "TA402", "is", "a", "persistent", "threat", "to", "organizations", "and", "governments", "in", "the", "Middle", "East", ",", "routinely", "updating", "not", "only", "their", "malware", "implants", ",", "but", "also", "their", "delivery", "methods", "."], "text": "Based on Proofpoint’s research, TA402 is a persistent threat to organizations and governments in the Middle East, routinely updating not only their malware implants, but also their delivery methods.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0011", "tokens": ["After", "publication", "of", "Proofpoint", "’", "s", "TA402", "research", "in", "June", "2021", ",", "TA402", "appeared", "to", "halt", "its", "activities", "for", "a", "short", "period", "of", "time", ",", "almost", "certainly", "to", "retool", "."], "text": "After publication of Proofpoint’s TA402 research in June 2021, TA402 appeared to halt its activities for a short period of time, almost certainly to retool.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0012", "tokens": ["Proofpoint", "researchers", "believe", "they", "used", "that", "time", "to", "update", "their", "implants", "and", "delivery", "mechanisms", ",", "using", "malware", "dubbed", "NimbleMamba", "and", "BrittleBush", "."], "text": "Proofpoint researchers believe they used that time to update their implants and delivery mechanisms, using malware dubbed NimbleMamba and BrittleBush.", "ne_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0013", "tokens": ["TA402", "also", "regularly", "uses", "geofencing", "techniques", "and", "varied", "attack", "chains", "which", "complicate", "detection", "efforts", "for", "defenders", "."], "text": "TA402 also regularly uses geofencing techniques and varied attack chains which complicate detection efforts for defenders.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0014", "tokens": ["#", "#", "#", "Campaign", "Details"], "text": "### Campaign Details", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0016", "tokens": ["*", "Figure", "1", ".", "TA402", "attack", "chain", "November", "2021", "to", "January", "2022", ".", "*"], "text": "*Figure 1. TA402 attack chain November 2021 to January 2022.*", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0017", "tokens": ["In", "the", "recently", "observed", "campaigns", ",", "TA402", "used", "spear", "phishing", "emails", "containing", "links", "that", "often", "lead", "to", "malicious", "files", "."], "text": "In the recently observed campaigns, TA402 used spear phishing emails containing links that often lead to malicious files.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0018", "tokens": ["Proofpoint", "observed", "three", "different", "URL", "types", "in", "those", "campaigns", "."], "text": "Proofpoint observed three different URL types in those campaigns.", "ne_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0019", "tokens": ["*", "*", "Variation", "1", ":", "Actor-Controlled", "Domain", "(", "November", "2021", ")", "*", "*"], "text": "**Variation 1: Actor-Controlled Domain (November 2021)**", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0020", "tokens": ["In", "a", "November", "2021", "campaign", ",", "TA402", "masqueraded", "as", "the", "Quora", "website", "while", "using", "an", "actor-controlled", "Gmail", "account", "with", "an", "actor-controlled", "domain", "."], "text": "In a November 2021 campaign, TA402 masqueraded as the Quora website while using an actor-controlled Gmail account with an actor-controlled domain.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0021", "tokens": ["The", "malicious", "URL", ",", "such", "as", "https", "[", ":", "]", "/", "/", "www", "[", ".", "]", "uggboots4sale", "[", ".", "]", "com", "/", "news15112021", ".", "php", ",", "in", "the", "phishing", "email", "was", "geofenced", "to", "the", "targeted", "countries", "."], "text": "The malicious URL, such as https[:]//www[.]uggboots4sale[.]com/news15112021.php, in the phishing email was geofenced to the targeted countries.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0022", "tokens": ["If", "the", "target's", "IP", "address", "fits", "into", "the", "targeted", "region", ",", "the", "user", "would", "be", "redirected", "to", "the", "RAR", "file", "download", "containing", "the", "latest", "TA402", "implant", ",", "NimbleMamba", "."], "text": "If the target's IP address fits into the targeted region, the user would be redirected to the RAR file download containing the latest TA402 implant, NimbleMamba.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0023", "tokens": ["If", "outside", "the", "target", "area", ",", "the", "user", "would", "be", "redirected", "to", "a", "legitimate", "news", "site", ",", "Figure", "2", "."], "text": "If outside the target area, the user would be redirected to a legitimate news site, Figure 2.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0025", "tokens": ["*", "Figure", "2", ".", "Benign", "redirect", "to", "legitimate", "news", "site", "https", "[", ":", "]", "www", "[", ".", "]", "emaratalyoum", "[", ".", "]", "com", ".", "*"], "text": "*Figure 2. Benign redirect to legitimate news site https[:]www[.]emaratalyoum[.]com.*", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0026", "tokens": ["*", "*", "Variation", "2", ":", "Dropbox", "URL", "(", "December", "2021", ")", "*", "*"], "text": "**Variation 2: Dropbox URL (December 2021)**", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0027", "tokens": ["In", "December", "2021", ",", "TA402", "used", "multiple", "phishing", "pretenses", ",", "including", "clickbait", "medical", "lures", "and", "ones", "allegedly", "sharing", "confidential", "geopolitical", "information", "."], "text": "In December 2021, TA402 used multiple phishing pretenses, including clickbait medical lures and ones allegedly sharing confidential geopolitical information.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0028", "tokens": ["TA402", "continued", "to", "use", "an", "actor-controlled", "Gmail", "account", "but", "shifted", "to", "Dropbox", "URLs", "to", "deliver", "the", "malicious", "RAR", "files", "containing", "NimbleMamba", "."], "text": "TA402 continued to use an actor-controlled Gmail account but shifted to Dropbox URLs to deliver the malicious RAR files containing NimbleMamba.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0029", "tokens": ["This", "shift", "away", "from", "actor-controlled", "domains", "meant", "that", "TA402", "could", "no", "longer", "geofence", "their", "payloads", "."], "text": "This shift away from actor-controlled domains meant that TA402 could no longer geofence their payloads.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0030", "tokens": ["Proofpoint", "discovered", "that", "TA402", "is", "not", "only", "abusing", "Dropbox", "services", "for", "delivery", "of", "NimbleMamba", ",", "but", "also", "for", "malware", "command", "and", "control", "(", "C2", ")", "."], "text": "Proofpoint discovered that TA402 is not only abusing Dropbox services for delivery of NimbleMamba, but also for malware command and control (C2).", "ne_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0031", "tokens": ["Proofpoint", "has", "shared", "our", "investigation", "and", "analysis", "with", "Dropbox", "prior", "to", "publication", ",", "and", "they", "took", "the", "needed", "actions", "for", "neutralizing", "the", "activity", "within", "their", "organization", "."], "text": "Proofpoint has shared our investigation and analysis with Dropbox prior to publication, and they took the needed actions for neutralizing the activity within their organization.", "ne_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0032", "tokens": ["*", "*", "Variation", "3", ":", "WordPress", "Redirect", "Actor-Controlled", "Domain", "(", "December", "2021", "/", "January", "2022", ")", "*", "*"], "text": "**Variation 3: WordPress Redirect Actor-Controlled Domain (December 2021/January 2022)**", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0033", "tokens": ["In", "their", "latest", "campaigns", ",", "TA402", "continued", "to", "use", "lure", "content", "customized", "for", "each", "of", "their", "targets", "but", "slightly", "adjusted", "their", "attack", "chain", "by", "inserting", "an", "additional", "actor-controlled", "WordPress", "URL", ".", "That", "WordPress", "site", "(", "Figure", "3", ")", ",", "which", "impersonates", "a", "news", "aggregator", "of", "the", "legitimate", "news", "site", "from", "Variation", "1", ",", "likely", "redirects", "to", "the", "download", "site", "of", "the", "malicious", "RAR", "files", "containing", "NimbleMamba", "if", "the", "visitor", "is", "coming", "from", "an", "IP", "within", "the", "targeted", "region", "."], "text": "In their latest campaigns, TA402 continued to use lure content customized for each of their targets but slightly adjusted their attack chain by inserting an additional actor-controlled WordPress URL. That WordPress site (Figure 3), which impersonates a news aggregator of the legitimate news site from Variation 1, likely redirects to the download site of the malicious RAR files containing NimbleMamba if the visitor is coming from an IP within the targeted region.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0034", "tokens": ["If", "the", "source", "IP", "address", "does", "not", "align", "with", "the", "target", "region", ",", "the", "URL", "will", "redirect", "the", "recipient", "to", "a", "benign", "website", ",", "typically", "an", "Arabic", "language", "news", "website", "(", "Figure", "2", ")", "."], "text": "If the source IP address does not align with the target region, the URL will redirect the recipient to a benign website, typically an Arabic language news website (Figure 2).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0036", "tokens": ["*", "Figure", "3", ".", "Example", "WordPress", "site", "(", "https", "[", ":", "]", "/", "/", "emaratalyoumcom", "[", ".", "]", "wordpress", "[", ".", "]", "com", "/", ")", "impersonating", "an", "Arabic", "language", "news", "aggregator", ".", "*"], "text": "*Figure 3. Example WordPress site (https[:]//emaratalyoumcom[.]wordpress[.]com/) impersonating an Arabic language news aggregator.*", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0037", "tokens": ["The", "use", "of", "geofenced", "URLs", ",", "Dropbox", "URLs", "and", "then", "redirect", "URLs", "demonstrate", "TA402", "’", "s", "determination", "to", "blend", "in", "with", "legitimate", "email", "traffic", "and", "infect", "targets", "with", "NimbleMamba", "."], "text": "The use of geofenced URLs, Dropbox URLs and then redirect URLs demonstrate TA402’s determination to blend in with legitimate email traffic and infect targets with NimbleMamba.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0038", "tokens": ["#", "#", "#", "Malware", "Analysis", ":", "NimbleMamba"], "text": "### Malware Analysis: NimbleMamba", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0039", "tokens": ["Each", "variant", "of", "TA402", "’", "s", "attack", "chain", "led", "to", "a", "RAR", "file", "containing", "one", "or", "multiple", "malicious", "compressed", "executables", "."], "text": "Each variant of TA402’s attack chain led to a RAR file containing one or multiple malicious compressed executables.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0040", "tokens": ["These", "executables", "include", "a", "TA402", "implant", "Proofpoint", "dubbed", "NimbleMamba", "and", "oftentimes", "an", "additional", "trojan", "Proofpoint", "named", "BrittleBush", "."], "text": "These executables include a TA402 implant Proofpoint dubbed NimbleMamba and oftentimes an additional trojan Proofpoint named BrittleBush.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0041", "tokens": ["NimbleMamba", "is", "almost", "certainly", "meant", "to", "replace", "LastConn", ",", "which", "Proofpoint", " ", "[", "reported", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "www.proofpoint.com", "/", "us", "/", "blog", "/", "threat-insight", "/", "new-ta402", "-", "molerats-malware-targets-governments-middle-east", ")", " ", "about", "in", "June", "2021", "."], "text": "NimbleMamba is almost certainly meant to replace LastConn, which Proofpoint [reported](https://www.proofpoint.com/us/blog/threat-insight/new-ta402-molerats-malware-targets-governments-middle-east) about in June 2021.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0042", "tokens": ["LastConn", "was", "likely", "an", "updated", "version", "of", "the", "SharpStage", "malware", ",", " ", "[", "reported", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "www.cybereason.com", "/", "hubfs", "/", "dam", "/", "collateral", "/", "reports", "/", "Molerats-in-the-Cloud-New-Malware-Arsenal-Abuses-Cloud-Platforms-in-Middle-East-Espionage-Campaign.pdf", ")", " ", "by", "Cybereason", "in", "December", "2020", "."], "text": "LastConn was likely an updated version of the SharpStage malware, [reported](https://www.cybereason.com/hubfs/dam/collateral/reports/Molerats-in-the-Cloud-New-Malware-Arsenal-Abuses-Cloud-Platforms-in-Middle-East-Espionage-Campaign.pdf) by Cybereason in December 2020.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0043", "tokens": ["While", "NimbleMamba", "and", "LastConn", "have", "some", "similarities", ",", "such", "as", "being", "written", "in", "C", "#", ",", "base64", "encoding", "within", "the", "C2", "framework", ",", "and", "use", "of", "the", "Dropbox", "API", "for", "C2", "communication", ",", "there", "appears", "to", "be", "little", "code", "overlap", "between", "the", "two", "."], "text": "While NimbleMamba and LastConn have some similarities, such as being written in C#, base64 encoding within the C2 framework, and use of the Dropbox API for C2 communication, there appears to be little code overlap between the two.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0044", "tokens": ["NimbleMamba", "uses", "guardrails", "to", "ensure", "that", "all", "infected", "victims", "are", "within", "TA402", "’", "s", "target", "region", "."], "text": "NimbleMamba uses guardrails to ensure that all infected victims are within TA402’s target region.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0045", "tokens": ["NimbleMamba", "uses", "the", "Dropbox", "API", "for", "both", "command", "and", "control", "as", "well", "as", "exfiltration", "."], "text": "NimbleMamba uses the Dropbox API for both command and control as well as exfiltration.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0046", "tokens": ["The", "malware", "also", "contains", "multiple", "capabilities", "designed", "to", "complicate", "both", "automated", "and", "manual", "analysis", "."], "text": "The malware also contains multiple capabilities designed to complicate both automated and manual analysis.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0047", "tokens": ["Based", "on", "this", ",", "Proofpoint", "assesses", "NimbleMamba", "is", "actively", "being", "developed", ",", "is", "well-maintained", ",", "and", "designed", "for", "use", "in", "highly", "targeted", "intelligence", "collection", "campaigns", "."], "text": "Based on this, Proofpoint assesses NimbleMamba is actively being developed, is well-maintained, and designed for use in highly targeted intelligence collection campaigns.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0048", "tokens": ["For", "this", "malware", "analysis", ",", "Proofpoint", "researchers", "analyzed", "the", "following", "two", "samples", ":", " "], "text": "For this malware analysis, Proofpoint researchers analyzed the following two samples: ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0049", "tokens": ["|", " ", "|", "*", "*", "SHA256", "*", "*", "|", "*", "*", "Compile", "time", "*", "*", "|", "*", "*", "Activity", "*", "*", "|"], "text": "|   | **SHA256** | **Compile time** | **Activity** |", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0050", "tokens": ["|", "Sample", "1", " ", "|", "c61fcd8bed15414529959e8b5484b2c559ac597143c1775b1cec7d493a40369d", " "], "text": "| Sample 1  | c61fcd8bed15414529959e8b5484b2c559ac597143c1775b1cec7d493a40369d ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0051", "tokens": [" ", "|", "2021", "-", "11", "-", "07", "00", ":", "02", ":", "28", " ", "|", "Used", "in", "an", "email-based", "campaign", "in", "November", "2021", " "], "text": "  | 2021-11-07 00:02:28  | Used in an email-based campaign in November 2021 ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0052", "tokens": [" ", "|"], "text": "  |", "ne_tags": ["O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0053", "tokens": ["|", "Sample", "2", " ", "|", "430c12393a1714e3f5087e1338a3e3846ab62b18d816cc4916749a935f8dab44", " "], "text": "| Sample 2  | 430c12393a1714e3f5087e1338a3e3846ab62b18d816cc4916749a935f8dab44 ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0054", "tokens": [" ", "|", "2021", "-", "11", "-", "20", "23", ":", "13", ":", "29", " ", "|", "Used", "in", "email-based", "campaigns", "in", "December", "2021", "and", "January", "2022", " "], "text": "  | 2021-11-20 23:13:29  | Used in email-based campaigns in December 2021 and January 2022 ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0055", "tokens": [" ", "|"], "text": "  |", "ne_tags": ["O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0056", "tokens": ["NimbleMamba", "is", "written", "in", "C", "#", "and", "delivered", "as", "an", "obfuscated", ".", "NET", "executable", "using", "third-party", "obfuscators", "."], "text": "NimbleMamba is written in C# and delivered as an obfuscated .NET executable using third-party obfuscators.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0057", "tokens": ["Both", "samples", "analyzed", "used", "the", " ", "[", "SmartAssembly", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "www.red-gate.com", "/", "products", "/", "dotnet-development", "/", "smartassembly", "/", ")", " ", "obfuscator", "."], "text": "Both samples analyzed used the [SmartAssembly](https://www.red-gate.com/products/dotnet-development/smartassembly/) obfuscator.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0058", "tokens": ["Additionally", ",", "the", "malware", "does", "basic", "virtual", "machine", "checks", "to", "avoid", "detection", "by", "looking", "for", "common", "strings", "that", "indicate", "a", "sample", "is", "running", "in", "a", "virtual", "environment", "."], "text": "Additionally, the malware does basic virtual machine checks to avoid detection by looking for common strings that indicate a sample is running in a virtual environment.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0059", "tokens": ["#", "#", "#", "Guardrails"], "text": "### Guardrails", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0060", "tokens": ["NimbleMamba", "contains", "multiple", "guardrails", "to", "ensure", "that", "the", "malware", "only", "executes", "on", "targeted", "machines", "."], "text": "NimbleMamba contains multiple guardrails to ensure that the malware only executes on targeted machines.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0061", "tokens": ["It", "uses", "the", "following", "IP", "resolving", "web", "services", "to", "check", "the", "user", "’", "s", "IP", "address", "and", "determine", "if", "it", "fits", "into", "the", "target", "region", "."], "text": "It uses the following IP resolving web services to check the user’s IP address and determine if it fits into the target region.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0062", "tokens": ["This", "is", "done", "to", "avoid", "detection", "and", "analysis", "."], "text": "This is done to avoid detection and analysis.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0063", "tokens": ["*", "api", "[", ".", "]", "ipify", "[", ".", "]", "com", "(", "[", "https", ":", "/", "/", "www.ipify.org", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "www.ipify.org", "/", ")", ")"], "text": "* api[.]ipify[.]com ([https://www.ipify.org](https://www.ipify.org/))", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0064", "tokens": ["*", "myexternalip", "[", ".", "]", "com", "(", "[", "https", ":", "/", "/", "myexternalip.com", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "myexternalip.com", "/", ")", ")"], "text": "* myexternalip[.]com ([https://myexternalip.com](https://myexternalip.com/))", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0065", "tokens": ["*", "ip-api", "[", ".", "]", "com", "(", "[", "https", ":", "/", "/", "ip-api.com", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "ip-api.com", "/", ")", ")"], "text": "* ip-api[.]com ([https://ip-api.com](https://ip-api.com/))", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0066", "tokens": ["*", "api", "[", ".", "]", "ipstack", "[", ".", "]", "com", "(", "[", "https", ":", "/", "/", "ipstack.com", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "ipstack.com", "/", ")", ")"], "text": "* api[.]ipstack[.]com ([https://ipstack.com](https://ipstack.com/))", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0067", "tokens": ["If", "the", "machine", "is", "unable", "to", "connect", "to", "those", "services", ",", "the", "malware", "will", "keep", "calling", "the", "addresses", "in", "random", "order", ",", "thus", "putting", "the", "execution", "in", "an", "endless", "loop", "in", "closed", "network", "environments", "."], "text": "If the machine is unable to connect to those services, the malware will keep calling the addresses in random order, thus putting the execution in an endless loop in closed network environments.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0068", "tokens": ["The", "malware", "will", "only", "continue", "executing", "if", "the", "country", "of", "the", "resolved", "IP", "address", "country", "code", "matches", "one", "from", "the", "following", "table", "or", "if", "the", "host", "computer", "has", "an", "Arabic", "language", "pack", "(", "code", "“", "AR", "”", ")", "installed", "."], "text": "The malware will only continue executing if the country of the resolved IP address country code matches one from the following table or if the host computer has an Arabic language pack (code “AR”) installed.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0069", "tokens": ["|", "*", "*", "Code", "*", "*", "|", "*", "*", "Country", "*", "*", "|"], "text": "| **Code** | **Country** |", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0070", "tokens": ["|", "KW", " ", "|", "Kuwait", " ", "|"], "text": "| KW  | Kuwait  |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0071", "tokens": ["|", "EG", " ", "|", "Egypt", " ", "|"], "text": "| EG  | Egypt  |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0072", "tokens": ["|", "IL", " ", "|", "Israel", " ", "|"], "text": "| IL  | Israel  |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0073", "tokens": ["|", "SA", " ", "|", "Saudi", "Arabia", " ", "|"], "text": "| SA  | Saudi Arabia  |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0074", "tokens": ["|", "IR", " ", "|", "Iran", " ", "|"], "text": "| IR  | Iran  |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0075", "tokens": ["|", "AE", " ", "|", "United", "Arab", "Emirates", " ", "|"], "text": "| AE  | United Arab Emirates  |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0076", "tokens": ["|", "TN", " ", "|", "Tunisia", " ", "|"], "text": "| TN  | Tunisia  |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0077", "tokens": ["|", "DZ", " ", "|", "Algeria", " ", "|"], "text": "| DZ  | Algeria  |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0078", "tokens": ["|", "SY", " ", "|", "Syria", " ", "|"], "text": "| SY  | Syria  |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0079", "tokens": ["|", "QA", " ", "|", "Qatar", " ", "|"], "text": "| QA  | Qatar  |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0080", "tokens": ["|", "JO", " ", "|", "Jordan", " ", "|"], "text": "| JO  | Jordan  |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0081", "tokens": ["|", "OM", " ", "|", "Oman", " ", "|"], "text": "| OM  | Oman  |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0082", "tokens": ["|", "PS", " ", "|", "Palestine", " ", "|"], "text": "| PS  | Palestine  |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0083", "tokens": ["|", "LB", " ", "|", "Lebanon", " ", "|"], "text": "| LB  | Lebanon  |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0084", "tokens": ["|", "LY", " ", "|", "Libya", " ", "|"], "text": "| LY  | Libya  |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0085", "tokens": ["|", "SS", " ", "|", "South", "Sudan", " ", "|"], "text": "| SS  | South Sudan  |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0086", "tokens": ["|", "SSD", " ", "|", "Soud", "Sudan", "(", "Alpha", "-", "3", "code", ",", "probably", "added", "by", "accident", ")", " ", "|"], "text": "| SSD  | Soud Sudan (Alpha-3 code, probably added by accident)  |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0087", "tokens": ["|", "IQ", " ", "|", "Iraq", " ", "|"], "text": "| IQ  | Iraq  |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0088", "tokens": ["|", "YE", " ", "|", "Yemen", " ", "|"], "text": "| YE  | Yemen  |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0089", "tokens": ["|", "MA", " ", "|", "Morocco", " ", "|"], "text": "| MA  | Morocco  |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0090", "tokens": ["|", "BH", " ", "|", "Bahrain", " ", "|"], "text": "| BH  | Bahrain  |", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0091", "tokens": ["#", "#", "#", "Configuration"], "text": "### Configuration", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0092", "tokens": ["NimbleMamba", "’", "s", "configuration", "is", "retrieved", "from", "a", "paste", "on", "the", "website", " ", "[", "JustPasteIt", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "justpaste.it", "/", ")", "."], "text": "NimbleMamba’s configuration is retrieved from a paste on the website [JustPasteIt](https://justpaste.it/).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0093", "tokens": ["NimbleMamba", "takes", "the", "current", "timestamp", "from", "an", "online", "real-time", "service", "to", "ensure", "that", "the", "timestamp", "matches", "the", "current", "time", "."], "text": "NimbleMamba takes the current timestamp from an online real-time service to ensure that the timestamp matches the current time.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0094", "tokens": ["Some", "computers", "may", "have", "modified", "time", "settings", "and", "this", "method", "ensures", "that", "the", "time", "is", "standardized", "across", "infections", "."], "text": "Some computers may have modified time settings and this method ensures that the time is standardized across infections.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0095", "tokens": ["The", "obtained", "timestamp", "is", "then", "used", "to", "generate", "a", "JustPasteIt", "URL", "with", "the", "algorithm", "in", "Figure", "4", "."], "text": "The obtained timestamp is then used to generate a JustPasteIt URL with the algorithm in Figure 4.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0097", "tokens": ["*", "Figure", "4", ".", "Python", "implementation", "of", "NimbleMamba", "’", "s", "JustPasteIt", "algorithm", ".", "*"], "text": "*Figure 4. Python implementation of NimbleMamba’s JustPasteIt algorithm.*", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0098", "tokens": ["When", "there", "is", "an", "active", "paste", "under", "the", "generated", "URL", ",", "it", "should", "look", "like", "this", ":", " "], "text": "When there is an active paste under the generated URL, it should look like this: ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2022-02-08_ugg-boots-4-sale-tale__s0100", "tokens": ["*", "Figure", "5", ".", "Example", "of", "JustePasteIt", "paste", "content", ".", "*"], "text": "*Figure 5. Example of JustePasteIt paste content.*", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
