{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0000", "tokens": ["New", "Threat", "Actor", "Spoofs", "Philippine", "Government", ",", "COVID", "-", "19", "Health", "Data", "in", "Widespread", "RAT", "Campaigns"], "text": "New Threat Actor Spoofs Philippine Government, COVID-19 Health Data in Widespread RAT Campaigns", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CON", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CON", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0001", "tokens": ["October", "27", ",", "2021"], "text": "October 27, 2021", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0002", "tokens": ["#", "#", "#", "Key", "Findings"], "text": "### Key Findings", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0003", "tokens": ["*", "Proofpoint", "identified", "a", "new", "cybercriminal", "threat", "actor", ",", "TA2722", "."], "text": "* Proofpoint identified a new cybercriminal threat actor, TA2722.", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0004", "tokens": ["*", "This", "group", "impersonates", "Philippine", "health", ",", "labor", ",", "and", "customs", "organizations", "as", "well", "as", "other", "entities", "based", "in", "the", "Philippines", "."], "text": "* This group impersonates Philippine health, labor, and customs organizations as well as other entities based in the Philippines.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0005", "tokens": ["*", "TA2722", "typically", "targets", "Shipping", "/", "Logistics", ",", "Manufacturing", ",", "Business", "Services", ",", "Pharmaceutical", ",", "and", "Energy", "entities", ",", "among", "others", "."], "text": "* TA2722 typically targets Shipping/Logistics, Manufacturing, Business Services, Pharmaceutical, and Energy entities, among others.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0006", "tokens": ["Geographic", "targeting", "includes", "North", "America", ",", "Europe", ",", "and", "Southeast", "Asia", "."], "text": "Geographic targeting includes North America, Europe, and Southeast Asia.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0007", "tokens": ["*", "TA2722", "distributes", "Remcos", "and", "NanoCore", "remote", "access", "trojans", "(", "RATs", ")", "."], "text": "* TA2722 distributes Remcos and NanoCore remote access trojans (RATs).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "B-GROUP", "O", "B-MALWARE", "O", "B-MALWARE", "B-CON", "I-CON", "I-CON", "O", "B-CON", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-GROUP", "O", "B-MALWARE", "O", "B-ORG", "B-CON", "I-CON", "I-CON", "O", "B-CON", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0008", "tokens": ["#", "#", "#", "Overview"], "text": "### Overview", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0009", "tokens": ["Proofpoint", "identified", "a", "new", "and", "highly", "active", "cybercriminal", "threat", "actor", ",", "TA2722", ",", "colloquially", "referred", "to", "by", "Proofpoint", "threat", "researchers", "as", "the", "Balikbayan", "Foxes", "."], "text": "Proofpoint identified a new and highly active cybercriminal threat actor, TA2722, colloquially referred to by Proofpoint threat researchers as the Balikbayan Foxes.", "ne_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-GROUP", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0010", "tokens": ["Throughout", "2021", ",", "a", "series", "of", "campaigns", "impersonated", "multiple", "Philippine", "government", "entities", "including", "the", "Department", "of", "Health", ",", "the", "Philippine", "Overseas", "Employment", "Administration", "(", "POEA", ")", ",", "and", "the", "Bureau", "of", "Customs", "."], "text": "Throughout 2021, a series of campaigns impersonated multiple Philippine government entities including the Department of Health, the Philippine Overseas Employment Administration (POEA), and the Bureau of Customs.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0011", "tokens": ["Other", "related", "campaigns", "masqueraded", "as", "the", "Manila", "embassy", "for", "the", "Kingdom", "of", "Saudi", "Arabia", "(", "KSA", ")", "and", "DHL", "Philippines", "."], "text": "Other related campaigns masqueraded as the Manila embassy for the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia (KSA) and DHL Philippines.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "B-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0012", "tokens": ["The", "messages", "were", "intended", "for", "a", "variety", "of", "industries", "in", "North", "America", ",", "Europe", ",", "and", "Southeast", "Asia", ",", "with", "the", "top", "sectors", "including", "Shipping", ",", "Logistics", ",", "Manufacturing", ",", "Business", "Services", ",", "Pharmaceutical", ",", "Energy", ",", "and", "Finance", "."], "text": "The messages were intended for a variety of industries in North America, Europe, and Southeast Asia, with the top sectors including Shipping, Logistics, Manufacturing, Business Services, Pharmaceutical, Energy, and Finance.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0013", "tokens": ["Proofpoint", "assesses", "this", "actor", "is", "targeting", "organizations", "directly", "or", "indirectly", "engaged", "with", "the", "Philippine", "government", "based", "on", "a", "continuous", "pattern", "of", "spoofing", "email", "addresses", "and", "delivering", "lures", "designed", "to", "impersonate", "government", "entities", "."], "text": "Proofpoint assesses this actor is targeting organizations directly or indirectly engaged with the Philippine government based on a continuous pattern of spoofing email addresses and delivering lures designed to impersonate government entities.", "ne_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0014", "tokens": ["For", "example", ",", "the", "shipping", ",", "transportation", ",", "and", "logistics", "companies", "would", "frequently", "engage", "with", "customs", "officials", "at", "ports", "of", "call", "."], "text": "For example, the shipping, transportation, and logistics companies would frequently engage with customs officials at ports of call.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0015", "tokens": ["Additionally", ",", "the", "manufacturing", "and", "energy", "companies", "support", "and", "maintain", "large", "supply", "chain", "operations", ",", "likely", "requiring", "correspondence", "with", "both", "labor", "and", "customs", "organizations", "."], "text": "Additionally, the manufacturing and energy companies support and maintain large supply chain operations, likely requiring correspondence with both labor and customs organizations.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0016", "tokens": ["All", "the", "campaigns", "distributed", "either", "Remcos", "or", "NanoCore", "remote", "access", "trojans", "(", "RATs", ")", "."], "text": "All the campaigns distributed either Remcos or NanoCore remote access trojans (RATs).", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "O", "B-MALWARE", "B-CON", "I-CON", "I-CON", "O", "B-CON", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "O", "B-ORG", "B-CON", "I-CON", "I-CON", "O", "B-CON", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0017", "tokens": ["Remcos", "and", "NanoCore", "are", "typically", "used", "for", "information", "gathering", ",", "data", "theft", "operations", ",", "monitoring", "and", "control", "of", "compromised", "computers", "."], "text": "Remcos and NanoCore are typically used for information gathering, data theft operations, monitoring and control of compromised computers.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["B-MALWARE", "O", "B-MALWARE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-MALWARE", "O", "B-MALWARE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0018", "tokens": ["While", "the", "malware", "’", "s", "associated", "infrastructure", "changed", "over", "time", ",", "the", "sender", "emails", "were", "reused", "for", "a", "long", "period", "of", "time", "."], "text": "While the malware’s associated infrastructure changed over time, the sender emails were reused for a long period of time.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0019", "tokens": ["In", "2020", ",", "Philippine", "government", "entities", "issued", " ", "[", "multiple", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "www.pna.gov.ph", "/", "articles", "/", "1106814", ")", " ", "[", "alerts", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "www.facebook.com", "/", "poea.gov.ph", "/", "photos", "/", "a", ".1107908212635101", "/", "3058798210879415", "/", "?", "type", "=", "3&", "eid", "=", "ARCpTFz5", "-", "C3KmQZ8DMVUnTnjAkPOm_VCzTfBt9uHyAKa3", "_", "C22vS4RQYTsD78jkLIG28G_MVS8VDFNtJc", ")", " ", "warning", "users", "of", "the", "activity", "related", "to", "lures", "using", "themes", "such", "as", "COVID", "-", "19", "infection", "information", "in", "the", "Philippines", "and", "the", "POEA", "labor", "information", "."], "text": "In 2020, Philippine government entities issued [multiple](https://www.pna.gov.ph/articles/1106814) [alerts](https://www.facebook.com/poea.gov.ph/photos/a.1107908212635101/3058798210879415/?type=3&eid=ARCpTFz5-C3KmQZ8DMVUnTnjAkPOm_VCzTfBt9uHyAKa3_C22vS4RQYTsD78jkLIG28G_MVS8VDFNtJc)  warning users of the activity related to lures using themes such as COVID-19 infection information in the Philippines and the POEA labor information.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "B-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-DATE", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0020", "tokens": ["#", "#", "#", "Campaign", "Details"], "text": "### Campaign Details", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0021", "tokens": ["Proofpoint", "researchers", "identified", "a", "series", "of", "campaigns", "distributing", "Remcos", "and", "NanoCore", "RATs", "masquerading", "as", "the", "Kingdom", "of", "Saudi", "Arabia", "(", "KSA", ")", "embassy", "in", "Manila", "and", "the", "Philippine", "Overseas", "Employment", "Administration", "(", "POEA", ")", "in", "mid", "-", "2021", "."], "text": "Proofpoint researchers identified a series of campaigns distributing Remcos and NanoCore RATs masquerading as the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia (KSA) embassy in Manila and the Philippine Overseas Employment Administration (POEA) in mid-2021.", "ne_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "O", "B-MALWARE", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "O", "B-ORG", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "I-DATE", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0022", "tokens": ["Upon", "further", "investigation", ",", "Proofpoint", "identified", "additional", ",", "separate", "campaigns", "distributing", "the", "same", "malware", "masquerading", "as", "the", "Philippine", "Department", "of", "Health", "and", "Bureau", "of", "Customs", "."], "text": "Upon further investigation, Proofpoint identified additional, separate campaigns distributing the same malware masquerading as the Philippine Department of Health and Bureau of Customs.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0023", "tokens": ["Proofpoint", "separated", "campaigns", "into", "two", "distinct", "threat", "activity", "clusters", "."], "text": "Proofpoint separated campaigns into two distinct threat activity clusters.", "ne_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0024", "tokens": ["In", "all", "cases", ",", "message", "lures", "were", "in", "English", "."], "text": "In all cases, message lures were in English.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0025", "tokens": ["They", "contained", "multiple", "threat", "distribution", "mechanisms", "including", ":", " "], "text": "They contained multiple threat distribution mechanisms including: ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0026", "tokens": ["*", "OneDrive", "URLs", "linking", "to", "RAR", "files", "with", "embedded", "UUE", "files"], "text": "* OneDrive URLs linking to RAR files with embedded UUE files", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0027", "tokens": ["*", "PDF", "email", "attachment", "with", "an", "embedded", "OneDrive", "link", "or", "other", "malicious", "URL", "leading", "to", "compressed", "executables", "(", ".", "iso", "files", ")", "that", "download", "and", "run", "malware"], "text": "* PDF email attachment with an embedded OneDrive link or other malicious URL leading to compressed executables (.iso files) that download and run malware", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CON"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CON"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0028", "tokens": ["*", "Compressed", "MS", "Excel", "documents", "containing", "macros", "which", ",", "if", "enabled", ",", "download", "malware"], "text": "* Compressed MS Excel documents containing macros which, if enabled, download malware", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CON"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CON"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0029", "tokens": ["Remcos", "is", "a", "commodity", "remote", "access", "tool", "available", "for", "purchase", "online", "."], "text": "Remcos is a commodity remote access tool available for purchase online.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["B-MALWARE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-MALWARE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0030", "tokens": ["NanoCore", "is", "also", "commodity", "malware", "and", "written", "in", ".", "NET", "by", "\"", "Aeonhack", "\"", "."], "text": "NanoCore is also commodity malware and written in .NET by \"Aeonhack\".", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["B-MALWARE", "O", "O", "O", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-MALWARE", "O", "O", "O", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0031", "tokens": ["The", "code", "is", "obfuscated", "with", "Eazfuscator.NET", "3.3", ".", "NanoCore", "RAT", "is", "sold", "on", "various", "hack", "forums", "."], "text": "The code is obfuscated with Eazfuscator.NET 3.3. NanoCore RAT is sold on various hack forums.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "B-MALWARE", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "B-MALWARE", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0032", "tokens": ["NanoCore", "includes", "many", "features", "and", "plugins", "."], "text": "NanoCore includes many features and plugins.", "ne_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["B-MALWARE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0033", "tokens": ["Both", "Remcos", "and", "NanoCore", "RAT", "are", "distributed", "by", "numerous", "cybercrime", "threat", "actors", "with", "many", "different", "delivery", "techniques", "and", "lures", "."], "text": "Both Remcos and NanoCore RAT are distributed by numerous cybercrime threat actors with many different delivery techniques and lures.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "B-MALWARE", "O", "B-MALWARE", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-MALWARE", "O", "B-MALWARE", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0034", "tokens": ["#", "#", "#", "#", "Threat", "Cluster", "Shahzad73"], "text": "#### Threat Cluster Shahzad73", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0035", "tokens": ["Proofpoint", "named", "the", "first", "identified", "cluster", "Shahzad73", "based", "on", "the", "command", "and", "control", "(", "C2", ")", "domains", "used", "by", "the", "threat", "actor", ":", " "], "text": "Proofpoint named the first identified cluster Shahzad73 based on the command and control (C2) domains used by the threat actor: ", "ne_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "O", "B-TACTIC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "I-TACTIC", "O", "B-TACTIC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0036", "tokens": ["       ", "shahzad73", "[", ".", "]", "ddns", "[", ".", "]", "net", " "], "text": "       shahzad73[.]ddns[.]net ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0037", "tokens": ["       ", "shahzad73", "[", ".", "]", "casacam", "[", ".", "]", "net", " "], "text": "       shahzad73[.]casacam[.]net ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0038", "tokens": ["Although", "Proofpoint", "began", "regularly", "tracking", "this", "activity", "cluster", "in", "April", "2021", ",", "historic", "data", "suggests", "the", "activity", "dates", "as", "far", "back", "as", "August", "2020", "."], "text": "Although Proofpoint began regularly tracking this activity cluster in April 2021, historic data suggests the activity dates as far back as August 2020.", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0039", "tokens": ["The", "threat", "actor", "generally", "leverages", "themes", "purporting", "to", "be", "labor-related", "messages", ",", "including", "spoofing", "the", "Philippine", "Overseas", "Employment", "Administration", "(", "POEA", ")", "and", "the", "Saudi", "Arabian", "consulate", "in", "Manila", "."], "text": "The threat actor generally leverages themes purporting to be labor-related messages, including spoofing the Philippine Overseas Employment Administration (POEA) and the Saudi Arabian consulate in Manila.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0040", "tokens": ["Other", ",", "less", "frequent", "threats", "observed", "in", "Shahzad73", "campaigns", "were", "associated", "with", "billing", "/", "invoice", "lures", "."], "text": "Other, less frequent threats observed in Shahzad73 campaigns were associated with billing/invoice lures.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0041", "tokens": ["The", "messages", "impacted", "hundreds", "of", "customers", "globally", "including", "entities", "in", "the", "Transportation", ",", "Energy", ",", "Construction", ",", "Manufacturing", ",", "Finance", ",", "and", "Business", "Services", "industries", "."], "text": "The messages impacted hundreds of customers globally including entities in the Transportation, Energy, Construction, Manufacturing, Finance, and Business Services industries.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0042", "tokens": ["Messages", "purported", "to", "be", ",", "for", "example", ":", "  "], "text": "Messages purported to be, for example:  ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0043", "tokens": ["       ", "From", ":", "POEA", "<", "info1", "@", "poea.gov.ph", ">", " "], "text": "       From: POEA <info1@poea.gov.ph> ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0044", "tokens": ["       ", "Subject", ":", "\"", "POEA", "ADVISORY", "ON", "DELISTED", "AGENCIES", "."], "text": "       Subject: \"POEA ADVISORY ON DELISTED AGENCIES.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0046", "tokens": ["*", "Figure", "1", ":", "Email", "sample", "purporting", "to", "be", "from", "Philippine", "Overseas", "Employment", "Administration", "(", "POEA", ")", ".", "*"], "text": "*Figure 1: Email sample purporting to be from Philippine Overseas Employment Administration (POEA).*", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0047", "tokens": ["Additional", "samples", "include", ":", "  "], "text": "Additional samples include:  ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0048", "tokens": ["       ", "From", ":", "\"", "ksa.Consulate", "manila", "\"", "<", "consulate", "\\", "_", "ksa", "\\", "_", "emb", "@", "gmail.com", ">", " "], "text": "       From: \"ksa.Consulate manila \" <consulate\\_ksa\\_emb@gmail.com> ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0049", "tokens": ["       ", "Subject", ":", "\"", "Memorandum", "from", "the", "Saudi", "Embassy", "\"", " "], "text": "       Subject: \"Memorandum from the Saudi Embassy\" ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0051", "tokens": ["*", "Figure", "2", ":", "Email", "sample", "purporting", "to", "be", "from", "the", " ", "Kingdom", "of", "Saudi", "Arabia", "(", "KSA", ")", " ", "consulate", ".", "*"], "text": "*Figure 2: Email sample purporting to be from the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia (KSA) consulate.*", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0052", "tokens": ["Saudi", "Arabia", "is", " ", "[", "reportedly", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "www.reuters.com", "/", "world", "/", "asia-pacific", "/", "philippines-halts-deployment-workers-saudi-arabia", "-", "2021", "-", "05", "-", "28", "/", ")", " ", "one", "of", "the", "most", "popular", "destinations", "for", "the", "country", "’", "s", "overseas", "workers", ",", "with", "over", "one", "million", "Filipinos", "working", "there", "."], "text": "Saudi Arabia is [reportedly](https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/philippines-halts-deployment-workers-saudi-arabia-2021-05-28/)  one of the most popular destinations for the country’s overseas workers, with over one million Filipinos working there.", "ne_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0053", "tokens": ["In", "May", "2021", ",", "the", "Philippines", " ", "[", "temporarily", "]", "(", "https", ":", "/", "/", "www.reuters.com", "/", "world", "/", "asia-pacific", "/", "philippines-lifts-ban-workers-deploying-saudi-arabia", "-", "2021", "-", "05", "-", "29", "/", ")", " ", "suspended", "sending", "workers", "to", "the", "Kingdom", "after", "receiving", "reports", "Filipino", "workers", "were", "being", "charged", "for", "COVID", "-", "19", "testing", "and", "quarantine", "."], "text": "In May 2021, the Philippines [temporarily](https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/philippines-lifts-ban-workers-deploying-saudi-arabia-2021-05-29/)  suspended sending workers to the Kingdom after receiving reports Filipino workers were being charged for COVID-19 testing and quarantine.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0054", "tokens": ["Proofpoint", "identified", "a", "campaign", "spoofing", "the", "KSA", "embassy", "in", "Manila", "targeting", "transportation", "entities", ",", "among", "others", ",", "around", "the", "same", "time", "."], "text": "Proofpoint identified a campaign spoofing the KSA embassy in Manila targeting transportation entities, among others, around the same time.", "ne_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0055", "tokens": ["Most", "of", "these", "messages", "contain", "either", "UUE", "or", "RAR", "attachments", "ultimately", "leading", "to", "the", "installation", "of", "Remcos", "remote", "access", "trojan", "(", "RAT", ")", "or", "NanoCore", "RAT", "."], "text": "Most of these messages contain either UUE or RAR attachments ultimately leading to the installation of Remcos remote access trojan (RAT) or NanoCore RAT.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "B-CON", "I-CON", "I-CON", "O", "B-CON", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "B-CON", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "B-CON", "I-CON", "I-CON", "O", "B-CON", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "B-CON", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0056", "tokens": ["Each", "campaign", "featured", "a", "dynamic", "DNS", "C2", "domain", "containing", "the", "keyword", "shahzad73", "."], "text": "Each campaign featured a dynamic DNS C2 domain containing the keyword shahzad73.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TACTIC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0057", "tokens": ["Example", "attachment", "file", "names", ":", " "], "text": "Example attachment file names: ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0058", "tokens": ["       ", "memorandum", "from", "the", "saudi", "embassy.pdf.uue.rar", " "], "text": "       memorandum from the saudi embassy.pdf.uue.rar ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0059", "tokens": ["       ", "Memorandum", "from", "the", "Saudi", "Embassy.pdf.uue", " "], "text": "       Memorandum from the Saudi Embassy.pdf.uue ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0060", "tokens": ["       ", "POEA", "Memo-Circular", "No", "019", "-", "22", ".", "pdf.uue", " "], "text": "       POEA Memo-Circular No 019-22.pdf.uue ", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0061", "tokens": ["       ", "POEA", "Memo-Circular", "No", "002", "-", "06", ".", "pdf.exe", " "], "text": "       POEA Memo-Circular No 002-06.pdf.exe ", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0062", "tokens": ["       ", "poea", "memo", "on", "delisted", "agencies", "."], "text": "       poea memo on delisted agencies .", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0063", "tokens": ["reminder.uue.rar", " "], "text": "reminder.uue.rar ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0064", "tokens": ["       ", "poea", "advisory", "on", "delisted", "agencies.pdf.uue", " "], "text": "       poea advisory on delisted agencies.pdf.uue ", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0065", "tokens": ["       ", "swiftusd33,980", "\\", "_", "soa005673452425", ".", "uue.rar", " "], "text": "       swiftusd33,980\\_soa005673452425.uue.rar ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0066", "tokens": ["The", "observed", "Remcos", "samples", "included", "the", "following", "example", "configuration", ":", "  "], "text": "The observed Remcos samples included the following example configuration:  ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0067", "tokens": ["       ", "C2", ":", "shahzad73", "[", ".", "]", "casacam", "[", ".", "]", "net", ":", "2404", " "], "text": "       C2: shahzad73[.]casacam[.]net:2404 ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "B-TACTIC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-TACTIC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0068", "tokens": ["       ", "C2", ":", "shahzad73", "[", ".", "]", "ddns", "[", ".", "]", "net", ":", "2404", " "], "text": "       C2: shahzad73[.]ddns[.]net:2404 ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "B-TACTIC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-TACTIC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0069", "tokens": ["       ", "license", ":", "9C98D5D48F9EA32282C07700F23815A0", " "], "text": "       license: 9C98D5D48F9EA32282C07700F23815A0 ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0070", "tokens": ["       ", "version", ":", "2.7.2", "Pro", " "], "text": "       version: 2.7.2 Pro ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0071", "tokens": ["Observed", "NanoCore", "RAT", "samples", "included", "the", "following", "example", "configuration", ":", " "], "text": "Observed NanoCore RAT samples included the following example configuration: ", "ne_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "B-MALWARE", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "B-ORG", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0072", "tokens": ["       ", "GCThreshold", ":", "10485760", " "], "text": "       GCThreshold: 10485760 ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0073", "tokens": ["       ", "KeyboardLogging", ":", "True", " "], "text": "       KeyboardLogging: True ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0074", "tokens": ["       ", "WanTimeout", ":", "8000", " "], "text": "       WanTimeout: 8000 ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0075", "tokens": ["       ", "Version", ":", "1.2.2.0", " "], "text": "       Version: 1.2.2.0 ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0076", "tokens": ["       ", "Mutex", ":", "Global", "\\", "{", "a58bb08a", "-", "85df", "-", "4191", "-", "824c", "-", "1b90cbce1024", "}", " "], "text": "       Mutex: Global\\{a58bb08a-85df-4191-824c-1b90cbce1024} ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0077", "tokens": ["       ", "RestartDelay", ":", "5000", " "], "text": "       RestartDelay: 5000 ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0078", "tokens": ["       ", "BackupDnsServer", ":", "8.8.4.4", " "], "text": "       BackupDnsServer: 8.8.4.4 ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0079", "tokens": ["       ", "PrimaryDnsServer", ":", "8.8.8.8", " "], "text": "       PrimaryDnsServer: 8.8.8.8 ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0080", "tokens": ["       ", "ConnectionPort", ":", "9036", " "], "text": "       ConnectionPort: 9036 ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0081", "tokens": ["       ", "MaxPacketSize", ":", "10485760", " "], "text": "       MaxPacketSize: 10485760 ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0082", "tokens": ["       ", "BufferSize", ":", "65535", " "], "text": "       BufferSize: 65535 ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0083", "tokens": ["       ", "ClearZoneIdentifier", ":", "True", " "], "text": "       ClearZoneIdentifier: True ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0084", "tokens": ["       ", "DefaultGroup", ":", "ENDING-JUNE", " "], "text": "       DefaultGroup: ENDING-JUNE ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0085", "tokens": ["       ", "LanTimeout", ":", "2500", " "], "text": "       LanTimeout: 2500 ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0086", "tokens": ["       ", "BackupConnectionHost", ":", "shahzad73", "[", ".", "]", "ddns", "[", ".", "]", "net", " "], "text": "       BackupConnectionHost: shahzad73[.]ddns[.]net ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0087", "tokens": ["       ", "BuildTime", ":", "2021", "-", "07", "-", "26", "13", ":", "34", ":", "18", "UTC", " "], "text": "       BuildTime: 2021-07-26 13:34:18 UTC ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0088", "tokens": ["       ", "UseCustomDnsServer", ":", "True", " "], "text": "       UseCustomDnsServer: True ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0089", "tokens": ["       ", "MutexTimeout", ":", "5000", " "], "text": "       MutexTimeout: 5000 ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0090", "tokens": ["       ", "KeepAliveTimeout", ":", "30000", " "], "text": "       KeepAliveTimeout: 30000 ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0091", "tokens": ["       ", "PrimaryConnectionHost", ":", "shahzad73", "[", ".", "]", "casacam", "[", ".", "]", "net", " "], "text": "       PrimaryConnectionHost: shahzad73[.]casacam[.]net ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0092", "tokens": ["       ", "TimeoutInterval", ":", "5000", " "], "text": "       TimeoutInterval: 5000 ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0093", "tokens": ["       ", "PreventSystemSleep", ":", "True", " "], "text": "       PreventSystemSleep: True ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0094", "tokens": ["       ", "ConnectDelay", ":", "4000"], "text": "       ConnectDelay: 4000", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0095", "tokens": ["#", "#", "#", "#", "Threat", "Cluster", "CPRS"], "text": "#### Threat Cluster CPRS", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0096", "tokens": ["Proofpoint", "named", "the", "second", "identified", "threat", "cluster", "CPRS", "based", "on", "the", "actor", "regularly", "spoofing", "the", "Philippines", "Bureau", "of", "Customs", "-", "Client", "Profile", "Registration", "System", "(", "CPRS", ")", "in", "ongoing", "campaigns", "."], "text": "Proofpoint named the second identified threat cluster CPRS based on the actor regularly spoofing the Philippines Bureau of Customs - Client Profile Registration System (CPRS) in ongoing campaigns.", "ne_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0097", "tokens": ["The", "identified", "Remcos", "RAT", "campaigns", "impacted", "nearly", "150", "customers", "globally", ",", "with", "a", "focus", "on", "Shipping", "and", "Logistics", ",", "Manufacturing", ",", "Industry", ",", "and", "Energy", "sectors", "."], "text": "The identified Remcos RAT campaigns impacted nearly 150 customers globally, with a focus on Shipping and Logistics, Manufacturing, Industry, and Energy sectors.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "B-MALWARE", "B-CON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "I-SECTOR", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0098", "tokens": ["Proofpoint", "began", "tracking", "this", "activity", "cluster", "in", "December", "2019", "."], "text": "Proofpoint began tracking this activity cluster in December 2019.", "ne_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0099", "tokens": ["The", "actor", "appeared", "to", "conduct", "multiple", "campaigns", "per", "month", "through", "October", "2020", "."], "text": "The actor appeared to conduct multiple campaigns per month through October 2020.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0100", "tokens": ["Activity", "restarted", "again", "in", "September", "2021", "."], "text": "Activity restarted again in September 2021.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "I-DATE", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0101", "tokens": ["Historic", "data", "suggests", "the", "activity", "dates", "as", "far", "back", "as", "2018", "."], "text": "Historic data suggests the activity dates as far back as 2018.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-DATE", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0102", "tokens": ["The", "threat", "actor", "generally", "leverages", "themes", "purporting", "to", "be", "entities", "related", "to", "the", "Philippine", "government", ",", "most", "frequently", "the", "Bureau", "of", "Customs", "CPRS", ".", "Other", "emails", "masqueraded", "as", "the", "country", "’", "s", "Department", "of", "Health", "distributing", "COVID", "-", "19", "information", "."], "text": "The threat actor generally leverages themes purporting to be entities related to the Philippine government, most frequently the Bureau of Customs CPRS. Other emails masqueraded as the country’s Department of Health distributing COVID-19 information.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "I-TECHNIQUE", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0103", "tokens": ["Other", ",", "less", "frequently", "observed", "threats", "in", "related", "campaigns", "were", "associated", "invoice", ",", "shipping", ",", "or", "Finance", "/", "Treasury", "themes", "."], "text": "Other, less frequently observed threats in related campaigns were associated invoice, shipping, or Finance/Treasury themes.", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "B-SECTOR", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0104", "tokens": ["Messages", "purported", "to", "be", ",", "for", "example", ":", " "], "text": "Messages purported to be, for example: ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0105", "tokens": ["       ", "From", ":", "cprs", "@", "customs", "[", ".", "]", "gov", "[", ".", "]", "ph", " "], "text": "       From: cprs@customs[.]gov[.]ph ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0106", "tokens": ["       ", "Subject", ":", "\"", "E-Mail", "Alert", "for", "Status", ":", "PROVISIONAL", "GOODS", "DECLARATION", "REFERENCE", "NO.C", "-", "1075027", "-", "21", "\"", " "], "text": "       Subject: \"E-Mail Alert for Status: PROVISIONAL GOODS DECLARATION REFERENCE NO.C-1075027-21\" ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0108", "tokens": ["*", "Figure", "3", ":", "Email", "purporting", "to", "be", "a", "Bureau", "of", "Customs", "declaration", ".", "*"], "text": "*Figure 3: Email purporting to be a Bureau of Customs declaration.*", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0109", "tokens": ["Other", "message", "samples", "include", ":", " "], "text": "Other message samples include: ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"id": "proofpoint_2021-10-27_new-threat-actor-spoofs-philippine__s0110", "tokens": ["       ", "From", ":", "COVID", "-", "19", "@", "doh.gov.ph", " "], "text": "       From: COVID-19@doh.gov.ph ", "ne_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "nc_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "te_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ce_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "ci_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "all_tags": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
