<DOCSTART>	O	O	O	O	O	O

Cybercriminals	O	O	O	O	O	O
cash	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
black	O	O	O	O	O	O
market	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
schemes	O	O	O	O	O	O

Oct	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
20	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2021	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE

If	O	O	O	O	O	O
you	O	O	O	O	O	O
look	O	O	O	O	O	O
back	O	O	O	O	O	O
through	O	O	O	O	O	O
all	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
research	O	O	O	O	O	O
Intel	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
471	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
released	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
cybercriminals	O	O	O	O	O	O
making	O	O	O	O	O	O
money	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
stolen	O	O	O	O	O	O
digital	O	O	O	O	O	O
assets	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
major	O	O	O	O	O	O
takeaway	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyber	O	O	O	O	O	O
underground	O	O	O	O	O	O
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
adopt	O	O	O	O	O	O
any	O	O	O	O	O	O
scheme	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
long	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
results	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
money	O	O	O	O	O	O
being	O	O	O	O	O	O
made	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

With	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
world	O	O	O	O	O	O
trying	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
move	O	O	O	O	O	O
past	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
global	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
pandemic	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
another	O	O	O	O	O	O
opportunity	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
illegal	O	O	O	O	O	O
gains	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
struck	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Intel	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
471	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
numerous	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
various	O	O	O	O	O	O
underground	O	O	O	O	O	O
forums	O	O	O	O	O	O
selling	O	O	O	O	O	O
fake	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
certifications	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
well	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
several	O	O	O	O	O	O
forums	O	O	O	O	O	O
hosting	O	O	O	O	O	O
advertisements	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccines	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

While	O	O	O	O	O	O
these	O	O	O	O	O	O
advertisements	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
proliferated	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
months	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
these	O	O	O	O	O	O
schemes	O	O	O	O	O	O
growing	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
underground	O	O	O	O	O	O
forums	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
rooted	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
cybercrime	O	O	O	O	O	O
ecosystem	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Of	O	O	O	O	O	O
those	O	O	O	O	O	O
fake	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
passes	O	O	O	O	O	O
being	O	O	O	O	O	O
advertised	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
concentration	O	O	O	O	O	O
placed	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
United	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
Centers	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
Disease	O	O	O	O	O	O
Control	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Prevention	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccination	O	O	O	O	O	O
card	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
paper	O	O	O	O	O	O
form	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
European	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Union	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
’	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
s	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
passport	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
issued	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
both	O	O	O	O	O	O
digital	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
paper	O	O	O	O	O	O
forms	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

On	O	O	O	O	O	O
one	O	O	O	O	O	O
particular	O	O	O	O	O	O
cybercrime	O	O	O	O	O	O
forum	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
listed	O	O	O	O	O	O
several	O	O	O	O	O	O
advertisements	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
fake	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccination	O	O	O	O	O	O
cards	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
parrots	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
lot	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
misinformation	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
surround	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
various	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccines	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

“	O	O	O	O	O	O
We	O	O	O	O	O	O
do	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
help	O	O	O	O	O	O
people	O	O	O	O	O	O
who	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
critical	O	O	O	O	O	O
situations	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
want	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
travel	O	O	O	O	O	O
urgently	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
advertisement	O	O	O	O	O	O
reads	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

“	O	O	O	O	O	O
Watch	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
stay	O	O	O	O	O	O
away	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
poisonous	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Kindly	O	O	O	O	O	O
pass	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
message	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
those	O	O	O	O	O	O
who	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
still	O	O	O	O	O	O
blind	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O
there	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
so	O	O	O	O	O	O
many	O	O	O	O	O	O
secrets	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
hidden	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
us	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
minority	O	O	O	O	O	O
ruling	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
trying	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
destroy	O	O	O	O	O	O
mankind	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
set	O	O	O	O	O	O
up	O	O	O	O	O	O
several	O	O	O	O	O	O
communication	O	O	O	O	O	O
channels	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
anyone	O	O	O	O	O	O
interested	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
potential	O	O	O	O	O	O
customers	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
reach	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O
via	O	O	O	O	O	O
encrypted	O	O	O	O	O	O
messaging	O	O	O	O	O	O
services	O	O	O	O	O	O
Telegram	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
WhatsApp	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Wickr	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
encrypted	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
service	O	O	O	O	O	O
ProtonMail	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Another	O	O	O	O	O	O
advertisement	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
same	O	O	O	O	O	O
forum	O	O	O	O	O	O
offers	O	O	O	O	O	O
fake	O	O	O	O	O	O
CDC	O	O	O	O	O	O
cards	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

These	O	O	O	O	O	O
falsified	O	O	O	O	O	O
documents	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
focused	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
European	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
French	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
documents	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
associated	O	O	O	O	O	O
false	O	O	O	O	O	O
QR	O	O	O	O	O	O
codes	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
website	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
accessible	O	O	O	O	O	O
via	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
TOR	O	O	O	O	O	O
browser	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
shows	O	O	O	O	O	O
what	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
final	O	O	O	O	O	O
QR	O	O	O	O	O	O
code	O	O	O	O	O	O
product	O	O	O	O	O	O
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
look	O	O	O	O	O	O
like	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
Screen	O	O	O	O	O	O
Shot	O	O	O	O	O	O
2021	O	O	O	O	O	O
10	O	O	O	O	O	O
08	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
10	O	O	O	O	O	O
46	O	O	O	O	O	O
30	O	O	O	O	O	O
AM	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

An	O	O	O	O	O	O
example	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
fake	O	O	O	O	O	O
French	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
digital	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
passport	O	O	O	O	O	O
taken	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
underground	O	O	O	O	O	O
website	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

(	O	O	O	O	O	O
Intel	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
471	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

With	O	O	O	O	O	O
regards	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
actual	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
advertisement	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
Intel	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
471	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
claimed	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
able	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
send	O	O	O	O	O	O
potential	O	O	O	O	O	O
buyers	O	O	O	O	O	O
numerous	O	O	O	O	O	O
different	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccines	O	O	O	O	O	O
currently	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
market	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
AstraZeneca	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Johnson	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
&	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Johnson	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Moderna	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pfizer	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Sputnik	O	O	O	O	O	O
V	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
Buyers	O	O	O	O	O	O
were	O	O	O	O	O	O
then	O	O	O	O	O	O
directed	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
visit	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
particular	O	O	O	O	O	O
website	O	O	O	O	O	O
set	O	O	O	O	O	O
up	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
sales	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

However	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
e-commerce	O	O	O	O	O	O
website	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
working	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
time	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
post	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
published	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

There	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
numerous	O	O	O	O	O	O
reports	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
falsified	O	O	O	O	O	O
document	O	O	O	O	O	O
practice	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
going	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
months	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

However	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
market	O	O	O	O	O	O
change	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
virus	O	O	O	O	O	O
causes	O	O	O	O	O	O
different	O	O	O	O	O	O
issues	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
various	O	O	O	O	O	O
parts	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
world	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Read	O	O	O	O	O	O
open-source	O	O	O	O	O	O
news	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
determine	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
countries	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
getting	O	O	O	O	O	O
enough	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
any	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
deliveries	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Market	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
illegal	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
these	O	O	O	O	O	O
developing	O	O	O	O	O	O
countries	O	O	O	O	O	O
since	O	O	O	O	O	O
these	O	O	O	O	O	O
nations	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
no	O	O	O	O	O	O
private	O	O	O	O	O	O
way	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
obtaining	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccines	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
must	O	O	O	O	O	O
instead	O	O	O	O	O	O
rely	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVAX	O	O	O	O	O	O
distribution	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Undermine	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
pharmaceutical	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
companies	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
efforts	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
distribute	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
putting	O	O	O	O	O	O
people	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
danger	O	O	O	O	O	O
since	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
very	O	O	O	O	O	O
little	O	O	O	O	O	O
recourse	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
determine	O	O	O	O	O	O
if	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccines	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
legitimate	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Be	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
underground	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
sales	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
counterfeit	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
passes	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
monetizing	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
fear	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
misinformation	O	O	O	O	O	O
around	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
creating	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
new	O	O	O	O	O	O
market	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
constructed	O	O	O	O	O	O
partly	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
pushing	O	O	O	O	O	O
people	O	O	O	O	O	O
who	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
never	O	O	O	O	O	O
purchased	O	O	O	O	O	O
anything	O	O	O	O	O	O
illicit	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
buy	O	O	O	O	O	O
things	O	O	O	O	O	O
off	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
underground	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

While	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
schemes	O	O	O	O	O	O
carried	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
do	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
directly	O	O	O	O	O	O
impact	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
organization	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
cybersecurity	O	O	O	O	O	O
defenses	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
hurt	O	O	O	O	O	O
pharmaceutical	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
companies	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
robbing	O	O	O	O	O	O
them	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
consumers	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
damaging	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
brand	O	O	O	O	O	O
reputations	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
addition	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
fake	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
passports	O	O	O	O	O	O
harm	O	O	O	O	O	O
healthcare	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
erodes	O	O	O	O	O	O
government	O	O	O	O	O	O
trust	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
false	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
disrupt	O	O	O	O	O	O
local	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
national	O	O	O	O	O	O
economies	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

No	O	O	O	O	O	O
matter	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
damage	O	O	O	O	O	O
wrought	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
shows	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
cybercriminals	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
forums	O	O	O	O	O	O
where	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
gather	O	O	O	O	O	O
online	O	O	O	O	O	O
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
take	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
any	O	O	O	O	O	O
scheme	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
no	O	O	O	O	O	O
matter	O	O	O	O	O	O
how	O	O	O	O	O	O
technical	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
order	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
make	O	O	O	O	O	O
money	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

