<DOCSTART>	O	O	O	O	O	O

No	O	O	O	O	O	O
pandas	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
just	O	O	O	O	O	O
people	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
The	O	O	O	O	O	O
current	O	O	O	O	O	O
state	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
cybercrime	O	O	O	O	O	O
underground	O	O	O	O	O	O

Dec	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
10	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE

China's	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
internet	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
lot	O	O	O	O	O	O
different	O	O	O	O	O	O
than	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
rest	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
world	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Yet	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
hasn't	O	O	O	O	O	O
stopped	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
population	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
engaging	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
cybercrime	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Despite	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
various	O	O	O	O	O	O
measures	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
government	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
taken	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
censor	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
surveil	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
residents	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
internet	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
significant	O	O	O	O	O	O
cybercrime	O	O	O	O	O	O
underground	O	O	O	O	O	O
full	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
financially	O	O	O	O	O	O
motivated	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
exists	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Efforts	O	O	O	O	O	O
like	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
The	O	O	O	O	O	O
Great	O	O	O	O	O	O
Firewall	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
government	O	O	O	O	O	O
crackdowns	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
content	O	O	O	O	O	O
related	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
cybercrime	O	O	O	O	O	O
force	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
put	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
remarkable	O	O	O	O	O	O
effort	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
maneuver	O	O	O	O	O	O
around	O	O	O	O	O	O
those	O	O	O	O	O	O
roadblocks	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
order	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
create	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
participate	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
criminal	O	O	O	O	O	O
marketplaces	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
mirror	O	O	O	O	O	O
those	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
commonly	O	O	O	O	O	O
known	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
rest	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
world	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Data	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
Intel	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
471	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
show	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
cybercrime	O	O	O	O	O	O
underground	O	O	O	O	O	O
proliferates	O	O	O	O	O	O
through	O	O	O	O	O	O
use	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
common	O	O	O	O	O	O
methods	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
platforms	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
but	O	O	O	O	O	O
behaves	O	O	O	O	O	O
differently	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
large	O	O	O	O	O	O
part	O	O	O	O	O	O
due	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
caution	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
take	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
regard	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
identity	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

While	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
average	O	O	O	O	O	O
citizen	O	O	O	O	O	O
must	O	O	O	O	O	O
follow	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
heavy	O	O	O	O	O	O
handed	O	O	O	O	O	O
nature	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
government's	O	O	O	O	O	O
surveillance	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyberspace	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
take	O	O	O	O	O	O
special	O	O	O	O	O	O
precautions	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
protect	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
forums	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
TTPs	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
themselves	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
leads	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
cybercrime	O	O	O	O	O	O
underground	O	O	O	O	O	O
being	O	O	O	O	O	O
disorderly	O	O	O	O	O	O
when	O	O	O	O	O	O
compared	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
others	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
particularly	O	O	O	O	O	O
Russia	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
tend	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
much	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
organized	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Where	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Underground	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O

Forums	O	O	O	O	O	O
hosted	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tor	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
network	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
barriers	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
entry	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
most	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
users	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
government	O	O	O	O	O	O
blocks	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tor	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
internet	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
order	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
operating	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
mainland	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
these	O	O	O	O	O	O
services	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
need	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
VPN	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
similar	O	O	O	O	O	O
measure	O	O	O	O	O	O
capable	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
evading	O	O	O	O	O	O
government	O	O	O	O	O	O
detection	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Guides	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
toolkits	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
allow	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
user	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
accomplish	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
task	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
often	O	O	O	O	O	O
available	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
underground	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

However	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
if	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
do	O	O	O	O	O	O
break	O	O	O	O	O	O
through	O	O	O	O	O	O
—	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
operating	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
other	O	O	O	O	O	O
popular	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
cybercriminal	O	O	O	O	O	O
hubs	O	O	O	O	O	O
like	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hong	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Kong	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Malaysia	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Myanmar	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
The	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Philippines	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Taiwan	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
—	O	O	O	O	O	O
there	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
host	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
forums	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
cybercriminals	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
DeepMix	O	O	O	O	O	O
Market	O	O	O	O	O	O

DeepMix	O	O	O	O	O	O
Market	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
one	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
most	O	O	O	O	O	O
well-known	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
underground	O	O	O	O	O	O
marketplaces	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
even	O	O	O	O	O	O
after	O	O	O	O	O	O
disappearing	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
several	O	O	O	O	O	O
weeks	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
2019	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
after	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
sustained	O	O	O	O	O	O
DDoS	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
attack	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
eventually	O	O	O	O	O	O
resurfaced	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
December	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
2019	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
enhanced	O	O	O	O	O	O
protections	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
users	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
marketplace's	O	O	O	O	O	O
offerings	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
categorized	O	O	O	O	O	O
into	O	O	O	O	O	O
several	O	O	O	O	O	O
sections	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
including	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
data-information	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
service-orders	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
virtual	O	O	O	O	O	O
resources	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
physical	O	O	O	O	O	O
goods	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
techniques	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
tutorials	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
carding	O	O	O	O	O	O
materials	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
CVVs	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
among	O	O	O	O	O	O
others	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
uses	O	O	O	O	O	O
heightened	O	O	O	O	O	O
measures	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
ensure	O	O	O	O	O	O
anonymity	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
discouraging	O	O	O	O	O	O
users	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
post	O	O	O	O	O	O
contact	O	O	O	O	O	O
details	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
encouraging	O	O	O	O	O	O
users	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
buy	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
sell	O	O	O	O	O	O
things	O	O	O	O	O	O
via	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
in-forum	O	O	O	O	O	O
system	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
forcing	O	O	O	O	O	O
users	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
use	O	O	O	O	O	O
small	O	O	O	O	O	O
numeric	O	O	O	O	O	O
handles	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
identify	O	O	O	O	O	O
accounts	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
DeepMix	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
same	O	O	O	O	O	O
handles	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
long	O	O	O	O	O	O
periods	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
time	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
order	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
build	O	O	O	O	O	O
brand	O	O	O	O	O	O
awareness	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
reflecting	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
reputation	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
still	O	O	O	O	O	O
paramount	O	O	O	O	O	O
even	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
identity	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
highly	O	O	O	O	O	O
sensitive	O	O	O	O	O	O
subject	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
United	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Escrow	O	O	O	O	O	O
Market	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
United	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Escrow	O	O	O	O	O	O
Market	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
UCEM	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
established	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
June	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
2018	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
sell	O	O	O	O	O	O
goods	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
services	O	O	O	O	O	O
like	O	O	O	O	O	O
those	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
DeepMix	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
but	O	O	O	O	O	O
differs	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
users	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
set	O	O	O	O	O	O
up	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
own	O	O	O	O	O	O
independent	O	O	O	O	O	O
shops	O	O	O	O	O	O
instead	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
relying	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
one	O	O	O	O	O	O
central	O	O	O	O	O	O
purchasing	O	O	O	O	O	O
hub	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Marketplace	O	O	O	O	O	O
postings	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
listed	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
U.S	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
dollars	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
but	O	O	O	O	O	O
bitcoin	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
only	O	O	O	O	O	O
accepted	O	O	O	O	O	O
currency	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
transactions	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
exchange	O	O	O	O	O	O
rate	O	O	O	O	O	O
determined	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
third-party	O	O	O	O	O	O
payment	O	O	O	O	O	O
service	O	O	O	O	O	O
provider	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
site	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
functions	O	O	O	O	O	O
similar	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
other	O	O	O	O	O	O
ecommerce	O	O	O	O	O	O
sites	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
including	O	O	O	O	O	O
sections	O	O	O	O	O	O
where	O	O	O	O	O	O
users	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
discuss	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
transaction	O	O	O	O	O	O
experience	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
internal	O	O	O	O	O	O
mailbox	O	O	O	O	O	O
function	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
communicate	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
other	O	O	O	O	O	O
members	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
bitcoin	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
wallet	O	O	O	O	O	O
management	O	O	O	O	O	O
section	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tea	O	O	O	O	O	O
Horse	O	O	O	O	O	O
Road	O	O	O	O	O	O

Established	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
June	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
2019	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tea	O	O	O	O	O	O
Horse	O	O	O	O	O	O
Road	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
similar	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
UCEM	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
DeepMix	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
allowing	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
trading	O	O	O	O	O	O
different	O	O	O	O	O	O
goods	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
services	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
but	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
site	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
includes	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
forum	O	O	O	O	O	O
where	O	O	O	O	O	O
users	O	O	O	O	O	O
discuss	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
sell	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
vulnerabilities	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
other	O	O	O	O	O	O
virtual	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
physical	O	O	O	O	O	O
goods	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Earlier	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
year	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Intel	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
471	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
saw	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
number	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
marketplace	O	O	O	O	O	O
users	O	O	O	O	O	O
spin	O	O	O	O	O	O
up	O	O	O	O	O	O
Telegram	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
channels	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
were	O	O	O	O	O	O
affiliated	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
site	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
made	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
order	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
provide	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
extra	O	O	O	O	O	O
layer	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
security	O	O	O	O	O	O
when	O	O	O	O	O	O
discussing	O	O	O	O	O	O
listings	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
other	O	O	O	O	O	O
site-related	O	O	O	O	O	O
matters	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

These	O	O	O	O	O	O
channels	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
very	O	O	O	O	O	O
active	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
users	O	O	O	O	O	O
heavily	O	O	O	O	O	O
engaged	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
discussions	O	O	O	O	O	O
while	O	O	O	O	O	O
being	O	O	O	O	O	O
careful	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
include	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
might	O	O	O	O	O	O
reveal	O	O	O	O	O	O
account	O	O	O	O	O	O
handles	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
actual	O	O	O	O	O	O
site	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
Free	O	O	O	O	O	O
City	O	O	O	O	O	O

Free	O	O	O	O	O	O
City	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
similar	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tea	O	O	O	O	O	O
Horse	O	O	O	O	O	O
Road	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
particularly	O	O	O	O	O	O
due	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
use	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Telegram	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
channels	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
marketplace	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
seven	O	O	O	O	O	O
sections	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
users	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
intel	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
services	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
order	O	O	O	O	O	O
replacement	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
virtual	O	O	O	O	O	O
resources	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
physical	O	O	O	O	O	O
goods	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
specialized	O	O	O	O	O	O
products	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
CVV	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
carding	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
private	O	O	O	O	O	O
escrow	O	O	O	O	O	O
transactions	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
Telegram	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
channels	O	O	O	O	O	O
allow	O	O	O	O	O	O
users	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
discuss	O	O	O	O	O	O
what's	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
sale	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
forums	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
while	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
hosting	O	O	O	O	O	O
tutorials	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
other	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
related	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
making	O	O	O	O	O	O
purchases	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
Open	O	O	O	O	O	O
Web	O	O	O	O	O	O
forums	O	O	O	O	O	O

Open	O	O	O	O	O	O
web	O	O	O	O	O	O
hacking	O	O	O	O	O	O
forums	O	O	O	O	O	O
where	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
cybercriminals	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
congregate	O	O	O	O	O	O
do	O	O	O	O	O	O
exist	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
but	O	O	O	O	O	O
often	O	O	O	O	O	O
get	O	O	O	O	O	O
shut	O	O	O	O	O	O
down	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
government	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

There	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
numerous	O	O	O	O	O	O
initiatives	O	O	O	O	O	O
launched	O	O	O	O	O	O
under	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
President	O	O	O	O	O	O
Xi	O	O	O	O	O	O
Jinping	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
led	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
crackdown	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
what	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
government	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
deemed	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
illicit	O	O	O	O	O	O
internet	O	O	O	O	O	O
content	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
April	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
China's	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Ministry	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Public	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Security	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
announced	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
punished	O	O	O	O	O	O
1,522	O	O	O	O	O	O
people	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
public	O	O	O	O	O	O
security	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
notified	O	O	O	O	O	O
other	O	O	O	O	O	O
departments	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
give	O	O	O	O	O	O
433	O	O	O	O	O	O
party	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
political	O	O	O	O	O	O
sanctions	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
matters	O	O	O	O	O	O
related	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
cybercrime	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Some	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
popular	O	O	O	O	O	O
open	O	O	O	O	O	O
web	O	O	O	O	O	O
forums	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
like	O	O	O	O	O	O
HLODAY	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
HZDG	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
华中帝国	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
known	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Central	O	O	O	O	O	O
Empire	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
gone	O	O	O	O	O	O
down	O	O	O	O	O	O
during	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
time	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

More	O	O	O	O	O	O
often	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
skilled	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
make	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
way	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
international	O	O	O	O	O	O
forums	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
Exploit	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hack	O	O	O	O	O	O
Forums	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Raid	O	O	O	O	O	O
Forums	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
XSS	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
These	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
advertise	O	O	O	O	O	O
tools	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
services	O	O	O	O	O	O
like	O	O	O	O	O	O
any	O	O	O	O	O	O
other	O	O	O	O	O	O
member	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
compromised	O	O	O	O	O	O
payment	O	O	O	O	O	O
cards	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
ransomware	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
cryptomining	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
malware	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
Messaging	O	O	O	O	O	O
Clients	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
Telegram	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
channels	O	O	O	O	O	O
tied	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tor	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
services	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
indicative	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
another	O	O	O	O	O	O
trend	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
like	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
use	O	O	O	O	O	O
messaging	O	O	O	O	O	O
clients	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
converse	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
each	O	O	O	O	O	O
other	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
underground	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
partly	O	O	O	O	O	O
due	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
familiarity	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
greater	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
population	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
messaging	O	O	O	O	O	O
platforms	O	O	O	O	O	O
like	O	O	O	O	O	O
WeChat	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
QQ	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
extremely	O	O	O	O	O	O
popular	O	O	O	O	O	O
among	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
internet	O	O	O	O	O	O
users	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

However	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
those	O	O	O	O	O	O
platforms	O	O	O	O	O	O
fall	O	O	O	O	O	O
under	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
same	O	O	O	O	O	O
government	O	O	O	O	O	O
restrictions	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
rest	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
country's	O	O	O	O	O	O
internet	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Therefore	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
move	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
non-native	O	O	O	O	O	O
messaging	O	O	O	O	O	O
services	O	O	O	O	O	O
like	O	O	O	O	O	O
Telegram	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Non-native	O	O	O	O	O	O
services	O	O	O	O	O	O
decrease	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
likelihood	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
linking	O	O	O	O	O	O
online	O	O	O	O	O	O
personas	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
real	O	O	O	O	O	O
offline	O	O	O	O	O	O
identities	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
well	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
provide	O	O	O	O	O	O
end-to-end	O	O	O	O	O	O
encryption	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
ensure	O	O	O	O	O	O
greater	O	O	O	O	O	O
anonymity	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

How	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
accessing	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
underground	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O

Because	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
anonymity	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
censorship	O	O	O	O	O	O
circumvention	O	O	O	O	O	O
needed	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
develop	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
sell	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
stolen	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
learned	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
extremely	O	O	O	O	O	O
adaptable	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
government's	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
efforts	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
watch	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
population's	O	O	O	O	O	O
internet	O	O	O	O	O	O
activity	O	O	O	O	O	O
means	O	O	O	O	O	O
there	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
no	O	O	O	O	O	O
anonymous	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
since	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
IP	O	O	O	O	O	O
address	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
tied	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
actual	O	O	O	O	O	O
person	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
results	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
anonymity	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
being	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
thinner	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
than	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
other	O	O	O	O	O	O
areas	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
world	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
order	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
evade	O	O	O	O	O	O
detection	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
change	O	O	O	O	O	O
IP	O	O	O	O	O	O
addresses	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
joining	O	O	O	O	O	O
different	O	O	O	O	O	O
WiFi	O	O	O	O	O	O
networks	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
getting	O	O	O	O	O	O
modems	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
request	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
new	O	O	O	O	O	O
dynamic	O	O	O	O	O	O
host	O	O	O	O	O	O
configuration	O	O	O	O	O	O
protocol	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
DHCP	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
addresses	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
use	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
TOR	O	O	O	O	O	O
network	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
leverage	O	O	O	O	O	O
VPN	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
proxy	O	O	O	O	O	O
services	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
bypass	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Great	O	O	O	O	O	O
Firewall	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
use	O	O	O	O	O	O
codewords	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
avoid	O	O	O	O	O	O
keyword	O	O	O	O	O	O
filters	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
tools	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
shadowsocks	O	O	O	O	O	O
relay	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
ssr	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
V2Ray	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Additionally	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
fact	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
some	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
do	O	O	O	O	O	O
manage	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
bypass	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
censorship	O	O	O	O	O	O
measures	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
international	O	O	O	O	O	O
sites	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
services	O	O	O	O	O	O
means	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
although	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
latest	O	O	O	O	O	O
tools	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
techniques	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
available	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
underground	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
everyone	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
them	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
led	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
trend	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
modifying	O	O	O	O	O	O
source	O	O	O	O	O	O
code	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
freeware	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
families	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
develop	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
own	O	O	O	O	O	O
versions	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
use	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
distribution	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
sale	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
using	O	O	O	O	O	O
popular	O	O	O	O	O	O
forums	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
GitHub	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
refine	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
skills	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
fine	O	O	O	O	O	O
tune	O	O	O	O	O	O
tools	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
latest	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

What	O	O	O	O	O	O
do	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
sell	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
underground	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O

Because	O	O	O	O	O	O
getting	O	O	O	O	O	O
around	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Great	O	O	O	O	O	O
Firewall	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
so	O	O	O	O	O	O
difficult	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
lot	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
being	O	O	O	O	O	O
pushed	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
cybercriminal	O	O	O	O	O	O
underground	O	O	O	O	O	O
forums	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
built	O	O	O	O	O	O
upon	O	O	O	O	O	O
existing	O	O	O	O	O	O
tools	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Intel	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
471	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
numerous	O	O	O	O	O	O
Remote	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
Access	O	O	O	I-CON	O	I-CON
Trojans	O	O	O	I-CON	O	I-CON
(	O	O	O	I-CON	O	I-CON
RATs	O	O	O	I-CON	O	I-CON
)	O	O	O	I-CON	O	I-CON
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
variants	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
already	O	O	O	O	O	O
known	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
pentesting	O	O	O	O	O	O
tools	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Anubis	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
AsyncRAT	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cobalt	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
Strike	O	O	O	I-MALWARE	O	I-MALWARE

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gh0st	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gray	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
Pigeon	O	O	O	I-MALWARE	O	I-MALWARE

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gray	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
Wolf	O	O	O	I-MALWARE	O	I-MALWARE

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
NjRAT	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Spynote	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE

We	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
popular	O	O	O	O	O	O
tools	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
worms	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
brute	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
forcers	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
DDoS	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
tools	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
post-exploitation	O	O	O	O	O	O
tools	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
well	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
exploits	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
for	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
vulnerabilities	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
in	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
web	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
servers	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
Apache	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Oracle	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Microsoft	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Windows	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

There	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
interest	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
software	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
that	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
mines	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
cryptocurrencies	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
while	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
attempting	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
steal	O	O	O	O	B-TACTIC	O
wallets	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
or	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
credentials	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
online	O	O	O	O	O	O
wallets	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Additionally	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
both	O	O	O	O	O	O
international	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
GandCrab	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
WannaCry	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
domestic	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
(	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
FilesLocker	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
)	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
variants	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
of	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
ransomware	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	I-TECHNIQUE	B-TECHNIQUE
were	O	O	O	O	O	O
placed	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
various	O	O	O	O	O	O
forums	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Specific	O	O	O	O	O	O
behavior	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
stood	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
these	O	O	O	O	O	O
forums	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
hacking	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
illegal	O	O	O	O	O	O
gambling	O	O	O	O	O	O
sites	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
QQ	O	O	O	O	O	O
tools	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
blackhat	O	O	O	O	O	O
search	O	O	O	O	O	O
engine	O	O	O	O	O	O
optimization	O	O	O	O	O	O
services	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
spamming	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
scamming	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
other	O	O	O	O	O	O
actions	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
lead	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
ripping	O	O	O	O	O	O
off	O	O	O	O	O	O
other	O	O	O	O	O	O
members	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
cybercriminal	O	O	O	O	O	O
underground	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

What	O	O	O	O	O	O
does	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
future	O	O	O	O	O	O
hold	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O

As	O	O	O	O	O	O
long	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
government	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
shows	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
ability	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
desire	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
crack	O	O	O	O	O	O
down	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
population's	O	O	O	O	O	O
internet	O	O	O	O	O	O
activity	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
highly-skilled	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
continue	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
closely	O	O	O	O	O	O
guard	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
skills	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
identity	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
effort	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
avoid	O	O	O	O	O	O
being	O	O	O	O	O	O
caught	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Petty	O	O	O	O	O	O
criminals	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
script	O	O	O	O	O	O
kiddies	O	O	O	O	O	O
may	O	O	O	O	O	O
thrive	O	O	O	O	O	O
while	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
proficient	O	O	O	O	O	O
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
continue	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
fly	O	O	O	O	O	O
under	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
radar	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
avoiding	O	O	O	O	O	O
public	O	O	O	O	O	O
posts	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
high-profile	O	O	O	O	O	O
breaches	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
custom	O	O	O	O	O	O
tools	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

With	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
censorship	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
surveillance	O	O	O	O	O	O
practices	O	O	O	O	O	O
carried	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
government	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
unlikely	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
stop	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
variety	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
forums	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
well	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
different	O	O	O	O	O	O
TTPs	O	O	O	O	O	O
employed	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
likely	O	O	O	O	O	O
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
continue	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
adapt	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
evolve	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
order	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
make	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
much	O	O	O	O	O	O
money	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
possible	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
above	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
pulled	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
Intel	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
471	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
whitepaper	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
further	O	O	O	O	O	O
in-depth	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
cybercrime	O	O	O	O	O	O
underground	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

To	O	O	O	O	O	O
inquire	O	O	O	O	O	O
about	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
whitepaper	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
how	O	O	O	O	O	O
Intel	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
471	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
enables	O	O	O	O	O	O
proactive	O	O	O	O	O	O
security	O	O	O	O	O	O
teams	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
get	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
contact	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
us	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
intel471	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
contact	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

