<DOCSTART>	O	O	O	O	O	O

Cybercriminals	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
interested	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
your	O	O	O	O	O	O
SCADA	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
systems	O	O	O	I-CON	O	I-CON

Feb	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
12	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2021	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
public	O	O	O	O	O	O
learned	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
week	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
alarming	O	O	O	O	O	O
cybersecurity	O	O	O	O	O	O
incident	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
could	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
physically	O	O	O	O	O	O
harmed	O	O	O	O	O	O
people	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
Someone	O	O	O	O	O	O
managed	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
system	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
controlled	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
Florida	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
city	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
’	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
s	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
water	O	O	O	O	O	O
treatment	O	O	O	O	O	O
plant	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
temporarily	O	O	O	O	O	O
adjusting	O	O	O	O	O	O
sodium	O	O	O	O	O	O
hydroxide	O	O	O	O	O	O
levels	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
amounts	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
could	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
made	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
population	O	O	O	O	O	O
sick	O	O	O	O	O	O
had	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
chemicals	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
introduced	O	O	O	O	O	O
into	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
water	O	O	O	O	O	O
supply	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

While	O	O	O	O	O	O
city	O	O	O	O	O	O
officials	O	O	O	O	O	O
caught	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
action	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
reversed	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
within	O	O	O	O	O	O
minutes	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
further	O	O	O	O	O	O
reporting	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
shown	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
plant	O	O	O	O	O	O
had	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
austere	O	O	O	O	O	O
cybersecurity	O	O	O	O	O	O
profile	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
sadly	O	O	O	O	O	O
familiar	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
public-sector	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
organizations	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
use	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
outdated	O	O	O	O	O	O
operating	O	O	O	O	O	O
systems	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.wfla.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
news	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
local-news	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
hacker-caught-altering-chemicals-in-oldsmar-water-supply-to-damaging-levels	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
disregard	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
best	O	O	O	O	O	O
practices	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
arstechnica.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
information-technology	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2021	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
02	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
breached-water-plant-employees-used-the-same-teamviewer-password-and-no-firewall	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
lack	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
budget	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
apnews.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
article	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
water-utilities-florida-coronavirus-pandemic-utilities	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
882ad1f6e9f80c053ef5f88a23b840f4	O	O	O	O	O	O
?	O	O	O	O	O	O
mid	O	O	O	O	O	O
=	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
cid	O	O	O	O	O	O
=	O	O	O	O	O	O
3510624	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
support	O	O	O	O	O	O
any	O	O	O	O	O	O
real	O	O	O	O	O	O
upgrade	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
staff	O	O	O	O	O	O
additions	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
cybercriminal	O	O	O	O	O	O
underground	O	O	O	O	O	O
understand	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
profile	O	O	O	O	O	O
fits	O	O	O	O	O	O
thousands	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
enterprises	O	O	O	O	O	O
around	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
world	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
gives	O	O	O	O	O	O
them	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
rich	O	O	O	O	O	O
target	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
set	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
sights	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Within	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
last	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
year	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Intel	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
471	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
financially-motivated	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
attempt	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
sell	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
SCADA	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
systems	O	O	O	I-CON	O	I-CON
tied	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
water	O	O	O	O	O	O
treatment	O	O	O	O	O	O
plants	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
May	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
likely	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iranian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
attempt	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
sell	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
U.S	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
hydroelectric	O	O	O	O	O	O
power	O	O	O	O	O	O
plant	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Further	O	O	O	O	O	O
investigation	O	O	O	O	O	O
found	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
what	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
actually	O	O	O	O	O	O
advertising	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
water	O	O	O	O	O	O
treatment	O	O	O	O	O	O
plant	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Florida	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
via	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
virtual	O	O	O	O	O	O
network	O	O	O	O	O	O
computing	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
VNC	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
permission	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
granted	O	O	O	O	O	O
system	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
Groundwater	O	O	O	O	O	O
Recovery	O	O	O	O	O	O
&	O	O	O	O	O	O
Treatment	O	O	O	O	O	O
System	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Additionally	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
one	O	O	O	O	O	O
screenshot	O	O	O	O	O	O
showed	O	O	O	O	O	O
levels	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
controls	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
sodium	O	O	O	O	O	O
hydroxide	O	O	O	O	O	O
pump	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

To	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
clear	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
Although	O	O	O	O	O	O
Intel	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
471	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
could	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
definitively	O	O	O	O	O	O
confirm	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
deny	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
link	O	O	O	O	O	O
between	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
offered	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Oldsmar	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Florida	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
incident	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
there	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
no	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
directly	O	O	O	O	O	O
tied	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
two	O	O	O	O	O	O
events	O	O	O	O	O	O
together	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
time	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
report	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
published	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
shared	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
Telegram	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
channel	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
known	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyberattacks	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
account	O	O	O	O	O	O
cracking	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
same	O	O	O	O	O	O
channel	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
tied	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
December	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
incident	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.securityweek.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
iranian-hackers-access-unprotected-ics-israeli-water-facility	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
where	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
allegedly	O	O	O	O	O	O
had	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
unprotected	O	O	O	O	O	O
human-machine	O	O	O	O	O	O
interface	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
HMI	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
system	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
Israeli	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
water	O	O	O	O	O	O
reservoir	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Although	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
do	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
often	O	O	O	O	O	O
openly	O	O	O	O	O	O
discuss	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
type	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
activity	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
there	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
those	O	O	O	O	O	O
who	O	O	O	O	O	O
seek	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
target	O	O	O	O	O	O
ICS	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
SCADA	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
systems	O	O	O	I-CON	O	I-CON
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
order	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
build	O	O	O	O	O	O
credibility	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
cybercriminal	O	O	O	O	O	O
underground	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
even	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
rudimentary	O	O	O	O	O	O
understanding	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
how	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
use	O	O	O	O	O	O
Shodan	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
search	O	O	O	O	O	O
engine	O	O	O	O	O	O
designed	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
find	O	O	O	O	O	O
internet-connected	O	O	O	O	O	O
systems	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
where	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
find	O	O	O	O	O	O
stolen	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
default	O	O	O	O	O	O
credentials	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
obtain	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
industrial	O	O	O	O	O	O
control	O	O	O	O	O	O
systems	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
could	O	O	O	O	O	O
lead	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
incidents	O	O	O	O	O	O
like	O	O	O	O	O	O
what	O	O	O	O	O	O
happened	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Oldsmar	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Florida	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Internet-connected	O	O	O	O	O	O
systems	O	O	O	O	O	O
like	O	O	O	O	O	O
those	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
power	O	O	O	O	O	O
critical	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
infrastructure	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
sectors	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
regarded	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
primary	O	O	O	O	O	O
target	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
financially-motivated	O	O	O	O	O	O
criminals	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

However	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
always	O	O	O	O	O	O
refining	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
methods	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
find	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
way	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
make	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
much	O	O	O	O	O	O
money	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
possible	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
boost	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
reputation	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
notoriety	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
cybercrime	O	O	O	O	O	O
ecosystem	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Given	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
wide	O	O	O	O	O	O
amount	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
poorly-guarded	O	O	O	O	O	O
systems	O	O	O	O	O	O
connected	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
internet	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
without	O	O	O	O	O	O
reason	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
suggest	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
only	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
matter	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
time	O	O	O	O	O	O
before	O	O	O	O	O	O
someone	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
cybercriminal	O	O	O	O	O	O
underground	O	O	O	O	O	O
turns	O	O	O	O	O	O
ICS	O	O	O	O	O	O
system	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
lucrative	O	O	O	O	O	O
pipeline	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

