<DOCSTART>	O	O	O	O	O	O

Criminals	O	O	O	O	O	O
posing	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lazarus	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
Group	O	O	O	O	O	O
threatened	O	O	O	O	O	O
Travelex	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bitcoin	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
DDoS	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE

Oct	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
13	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE

A	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
posing	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
notorious	O	O	O	O	O	O
nation-state-linked	O	O	O	O	O	O
hacking	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lazarus	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
Group	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
threatened	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
hit	O	O	O	O	O	O
British	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
foreign	O	O	O	O	O	O
exchange	O	O	O	O	O	O
company	O	O	O	O	O	O
Travelex	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
distributed-denial-of-service	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
DDoS	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
attack	O	O	O	O	O	O
unless	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
paid	O	O	O	O	O	O
20	O	O	O	O	O	O
bitcoins	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

According	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
discovered	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
Intel	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
471	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
researchers	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
attackers	O	O	O	O	O	O
threatened	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
hit	O	O	O	O	O	O
Travelex	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
extremely	O	O	O	O	O	O
powerful	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
attack	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
would	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
peak	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tbps	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
until	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
company	O	O	O	O	O	O
paid	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
ransom	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
demand	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
sent	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
late	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
August	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
asked	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
value	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
approximately	O	O	O	O	O	O
US	O	O	O	O	O	O
$213,000	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

“	O	O	O	O	O	O
It's	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
small	O	O	O	O	O	O
price	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
what	O	O	O	O	O	O
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
happen	O	O	O	O	O	O
when	O	O	O	O	O	O
your	O	O	O	O	O	O
whole	O	O	O	O	O	O
network	O	O	O	O	O	O
goes	O	O	O	O	O	O
down	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
read	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

“	O	O	O	O	O	O
Is	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
worth	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

You	O	O	O	O	O	O
decide	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Following	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
extortion	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
actor	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
conducted	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
a	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
volumetric	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
attack	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
on	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
a	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
custom	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
port	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
of	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
four	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
IP	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
addresses	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
serving	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
the	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
company	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
’	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
s	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
subdomains	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
.	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O

Two	O	O	O	O	O	O
days	O	O	O	O	O	O
later	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
attackers	O	O	O	O	O	O
carried	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O
another	O	O	O	O	O	O
DNS	O	O	O	O	O	O
amplification	O	O	O	O	O	O
attack	O	O	O	O	O	O
against	O	O	O	O	O	O
Travelex	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
using	O	O	O	O	O	O
Google	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
DNS	O	O	O	O	O	O
servers	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
said	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
if	O	O	O	O	O	O
Travelex	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
didn	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
t	O	O	O	O	O	O
comply	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
certain	O	O	O	O	O	O
date	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
ransom	O	O	O	O	O	O
would	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
increase	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
10	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bitcoin	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
each	O	O	O	O	O	O
day	O	O	O	O	O	O
after	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
deadline	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
passed	O	O	O	O	O	O
without	O	O	O	O	O	O
payment	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

A	O	O	O	O	O	O
bitcoin	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
wallet	O	O	O	O	O	O
address	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
shows	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
Travelex	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
did	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
pay	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
attackers	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
any	O	O	O	O	O	O
point	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

While	O	O	O	O	O	O
it's	O	O	O	O	O	O
unclear	O	O	O	O	O	O
whether	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
North	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Korea-backed	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
responsible	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
note	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Intel	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
471	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
VP	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Intelligence	O	O	O	O	O	O
Michael	O	O	O	O	O	O
DeBolt	O	O	O	O	O	O
says	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
unlikely	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
related	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
nation-state	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

"	O	O	O	O	O	O
We've	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
come	O	O	O	O	O	O
up	O	O	O	O	O	O
quite	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
few	O	O	O	O	O	O
times	O	O	O	O	O	O
recently	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
DeBolt	O	O	O	O	O	O
said	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

"	O	O	O	O	O	O
The	O	O	O	O	O	O
attackers	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
trying	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
capitalize	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
notoriety	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
well-known	O	O	O	O	O	O
groups	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
scare	O	O	O	O	O	O
tactic	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
pressure	O	O	O	O	O	O
victims	O	O	O	O	O	O
into	O	O	O	O	O	O
paying	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
true	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
groups	O	O	O	O	O	O
likely	O	O	O	O	O	O
possess	O	O	O	O	O	O
some	O	O	O	O	O	O
DDoS	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
capabilities	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
need	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
taken	O	O	O	O	O	O
seriously	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
so	O	O	O	O	O	O
organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
should	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
prepared	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
deal	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
sort	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
attack	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
part	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
cybersecurity	O	O	O	O	O	O
plan	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
Travelex	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
comes	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
company	O	O	O	O	O	O
underwent	O	O	O	O	O	O
one	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
most	O	O	O	O	O	O
notable	O	O	O	O	O	O
ransomware	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
attacks	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
past	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
year	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
January	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
company	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
hit	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
REvil	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
ransomware	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.cyberscoop.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
travelex-sodinokibi-ransomware	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
forcing	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
suspend	O	O	O	O	O	O
all	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
online	O	O	O	O	O	O
services	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
including	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
app	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
internal	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
systems	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
several	O	O	O	O	O	O
weeks	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Groups	O	O	O	O	O	O
posing	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
nation-state	O	O	O	O	O	O
hacking	O	O	O	O	O	O
groups	O	O	O	O	O	O
while	O	O	O	O	O	O
threatening	O	O	O	O	O	O
ransom-backed	O	O	O	O	O	O
DDoS	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
attacks	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
bubbling	O	O	O	O	O	O
up	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
past	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
year	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
November	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2019	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
New	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Zealand	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
cybersecurity	O	O	O	O	O	O
organization	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
CertNZ	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
issued	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
warning	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.cert.govt.nz	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
it-specialists	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
advisories	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
ddos-extortion-campaign-targeting-financial-sector	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
about	O	O	O	O	O	O
ongoing	O	O	O	O	O	O
extortion	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaigns	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeting	O	O	O	O	O	O
companies	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
financial	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
sector	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
claimed	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
represent	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Russian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
hacker	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
Fancy	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
Bear	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
demanded	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
ransom	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
avoid	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
DDoS	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
attack	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Additionally	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
New	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Jersey	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
Cybersecurity	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Communications	O	O	O	O	O	O
Integration	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cell	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
issued	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
advisory	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.cyber.nj.gov	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
alerts-advisories	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
extortionists-claiming-to-be-apt-groups-threaten-ddos-attacks	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
August	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
who	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeted	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
finance	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
retail	O	O	O	O	O	O
sectors	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
DDoS	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
attacks	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
claiming	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
members	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Fancy	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
Bear	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Armada	O	O	O	O	O	O
Collective	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

New	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Zealand-based	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
enterprises	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
rash	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
DDoS	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
attacks	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.stuff.co.nz	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
business	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
industries	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
122636840	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
metservice-anticipates-future-ddos-cyberattacks-in-coming-days	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
past	O	O	O	O	O	O
few	O	O	O	O	O	O
months	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
August	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
New	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Zealand	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
stock	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
exchange	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
hit	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
DDoS	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	B-TECHNIQUE	B-TECHNIQUE
attack	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
that	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
spanned	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
several	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
days	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
and	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
caused	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
a	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
disruption	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
of	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
some	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
services	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
.	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O

The	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
Meteorological	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
Service	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
of	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
New	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
Zealand	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
news	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
media	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
company	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
Stuff	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
public-service	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
radio	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
broadcaster	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
Radio	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
New	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
Zealand	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Australian	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
bank	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
Westpac	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
Banking	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
Corp	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
hit	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
DDoS	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
attacks	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
recent	O	O	O	O	O	O
weeks	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

