<DOCSTART>	O	O	O	O	O	O

That	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
quick	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
Trickbot	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
back	O	O	O	O	O	O
after	O	O	O	O	O	O
disruption	O	O	O	O	O	O
attempts	O	O	O	O	O	O

Oct	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
15	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
Trickbot	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
botnet	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
looks	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
working	O	O	O	O	O	O
once	O	O	O	O	O	O
again	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
despite	O	O	O	O	O	O
separate	O	O	O	O	O	O
efforts	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
past	O	O	O	O	O	O
few	O	O	O	O	O	O
weeks	O	O	O	O	O	O
aimed	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
disrupting	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
operation	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

On	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
October	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
14	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Emotet	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
spam	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
botnet	O	O	O	B-CON	I-TECHNIQUE	B-CON
—	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
often	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
precursor	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
to	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
TrickBot	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	I-TECHNIQUE	B-MALWARE
being	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
loaded	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
onto	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
a	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
system	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
—	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
began	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
receiving	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
spam	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
templates	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
intended	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
for	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
mass	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
distribution	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

These	O	O	O	O	O	O
spam	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
templates	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
contained	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
a	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Microsoft	B-ORG	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	B-TECHNIQUE	B-ORG
Word	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	I-TECHNIQUE	I-TECHNIQUE
document	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	I-TECHNIQUE	I-TECHNIQUE
attachment	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	I-TECHNIQUE	I-TECHNIQUE
with	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
malicious	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
macros	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
that	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
fetch	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
and	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
load	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
a	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
copy	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
of	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
Emotet	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	I-TECHNIQUE	B-MALWARE
onto	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
the	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
victim	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
machine	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
Emotet	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	B-TECHNIQUE	B-MALWARE
bots	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
reached	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
out	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
to	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
their	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
controllers	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
and	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
received	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
commands	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
to	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
download	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
and	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
execute	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
Trickbot	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	I-TECHNIQUE	B-MALWARE
on	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
victim	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
machines	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
.	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
Trickbot	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
tag	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
Intel	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
471	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
identified	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
tied	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
typical	O	O	O	O	O	O
infection	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
security	O	O	O	O	O	O
researchers	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
observing	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
past	O	O	O	O	O	O
6	O	O	O	O	O	O
months	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Additionally	O	O	O	O	O	O
Intel	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
471	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
researchers	O	O	O	O	O	O
saw	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
update	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Trickbot	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
plugin	O	O	O	O	O	O
server	O	O	O	O	O	O
configuration	O	O	O	O	O	O
file	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Fifteen	O	O	O	O	O	O
server	O	O	O	O	O	O
addresses	O	O	O	O	O	O
were	O	O	O	O	O	O
added	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
two	O	O	O	O	O	O
old	O	O	O	O	O	O
servers	O	O	O	O	O	O
were	O	O	O	O	O	O
retained	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
configuration	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
along	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
server	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
onion	O	O	O	O	O	O
address	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
likely	O	O	O	O	O	O
done	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
fix	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
would	O	O	O	O	O	O
help	O	O	O	O	O	O
operators	O	O	O	O	O	O
maintain	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
infrastructure	O	O	O	O	O	O
remains	O	O	O	O	O	O
operational	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
fix	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
another	O	O	O	O	O	O
round	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
back-and-forth	O	O	O	O	O	O
between	O	O	O	O	O	O
Trickbot	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
operators	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
separate	O	O	O	O	O	O
parties	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
attempted	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
disrupt	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
botnet	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
actions	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

On	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
Oct	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
.	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
10	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Washington	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Post	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
reported	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.washingtonpost.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
national-security	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyber-command-trickbot-disrupt	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2020	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
10	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
09	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
19587aae	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
0a32	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
11eb-a166	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
dc429b380d10	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
story.html	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
four	O	O	O	O	O	O
U.S	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
officials	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
claimed	O	O	O	O	O	O
U.S	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC

Cyber	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Command	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
conducting	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
operation	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
disrupt	O	O	O	O	O	O
Trickbot	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
action	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
first	O	O	O	O	O	O
reported	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
Brian	O	O	O	O	O	O
Krebs	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
krebsonsecurity.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2020	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
10	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
attacks-aimed-at-disrupting-the-trickbot-botnet	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
Oct	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
.	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
identified	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
Intel	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
471	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
Malware	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
Intelligence	O	O	O	O	O	O
systems	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
Sept	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
.	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
22	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Additionally	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Microsoft	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
issued	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
public	O	O	O	O	O	O
statement	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blogs.microsoft.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
on-the-issues	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2020	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
10	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
12	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
trickbot-ransomware-cyberthreat-us-elections	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
Oct	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
.	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
12	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
had	O	O	O	O	O	O
taken	O	O	O	O	O	O
legal	O	O	O	O	O	O
action	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
combat	O	O	O	O	O	O
ransomware	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
ahead	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
U.S	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
elections	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
legal	O	O	O	O	O	O
action	O	O	O	O	O	O
involved	O	O	O	O	O	O
Microsoft	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
attempting	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
disrupt	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
number	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Trickbot	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
command	O	O	O	B-TACTIC	O	B-TACTIC
and	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
control	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
server	O	O	O	O	O	O
IP	O	O	O	O	O	O
addresses	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
United	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
fact	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
Trickbot	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
resumed	O	O	O	O	O	O
normal	O	O	O	O	O	O
operations	O	O	O	O	O	O
despite	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
best	O	O	O	O	O	O
efforts	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
U.S	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC

Cyber	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Command	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Microsoft	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
shows	O	O	O	O	O	O
how	O	O	O	O	O	O
resilient	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
operation	O	O	O	O	O	O
Trickbot	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
how	O	O	O	O	O	O
much	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
effort	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
needed	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
fully	O	O	O	O	O	O
take	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
botnet	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
offline	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
good	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
botnet	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
operators	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
all	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
IT	O	O	O	O	O	O
support	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
legitimate	O	O	O	O	O	O
enterprises	O	O	O	O	O	O
—	O	O	O	O	O	O
continuity	O	O	O	O	O	O
planning	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
backups	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
automated	O	O	O	O	O	O
deployment	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
dedicated	O	O	O	O	O	O
workforce	O	O	O	O	O	O
—	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
allow	O	O	O	O	O	O
them	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
quickly	O	O	O	O	O	O
react	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
disruptive	O	O	O	O	O	O
measures	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

“	O	O	O	O	O	O
About	O	O	O	O	O	O
10	O	O	O	O	O	O
years	O	O	O	O	O	O
ago	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
much	O	O	O	O	O	O
easier	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
completely	O	O	O	O	O	O
take	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
significantly	O	O	O	O	O	O
disrupt	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
botnet	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
but	O	O	O	O	O	O
cybercriminals	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
students	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
takedowns	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
learned	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
make	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
operations	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
resilient	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
takedown	O	O	O	O	O	O
efforts	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
said	O	O	O	O	O	O
Intel	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
471	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
COO	O	O	O	O	O	O
Jason	O	O	O	O	O	O
Passwaters	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

“	O	O	O	O	O	O
That's	O	O	O	O	O	O
why	O	O	O	O	O	O
every	O	O	O	O	O	O
takedown	O	O	O	O	O	O
attempt	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
some	O	O	O	O	O	O
potential	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
giving	O	O	O	O	O	O
ground	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
adversary	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

You're	O	O	O	O	O	O
teaching	O	O	O	O	O	O
them	O	O	O	O	O	O
where	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
weaknesses	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
armor	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
team	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
developers	O	O	O	O	O	O
ready	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
act	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

So	O	O	O	O	O	O
unless	O	O	O	O	O	O
you	O	O	O	O	O	O
strike	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
killing	O	O	O	O	O	O
blow	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
you're	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
going	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
impact	O	O	O	O	O	O
them	O	O	O	O	O	O
long	O	O	O	O	O	O
term	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

While	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
actions	O	O	O	O	O	O
taken	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
past	O	O	O	O	O	O
week	O	O	O	O	O	O
let	O	O	O	O	O	O
Trickbot	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
operators	O	O	O	O	O	O
know	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
operating	O	O	O	O	O	O
free	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
consequence	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
multi-pronged	O	O	O	O	O	O
effort	O	O	O	O	O	O
needs	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
made	O	O	O	O	O	O
if	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
botnet	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
fully	O	O	O	O	O	O
knocked	O	O	O	O	O	O
offline	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Law	O	O	O	O	O	O
enforcement	O	O	O	O	O	O
efforts	O	O	O	O	O	O
should	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
multinational	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
focus	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
arresting	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
core	O	O	O	O	O	O
operators	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
botnet	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Any	O	O	O	O	O	O
further	O	O	O	O	O	O
efforts	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
disrupt	O	O	O	O	O	O
infrastructure	O	O	O	O	O	O
should	O	O	O	O	O	O
focus	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
main	O	O	O	O	O	O
infrastructure	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
just	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
countries	O	O	O	O	O	O
where	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
court	O	O	O	O	O	O
order	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
needed	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Governments	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
companies	O	O	O	O	O	O
should	O	O	O	O	O	O
work	O	O	O	O	O	O
together	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
mass	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
de-infection	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaigns	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
similar	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
those	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
eliminate	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bredolab	O	O	O	O	O	O
botnet	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
2010	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.zdnet.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
article	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
dutch-police-take-down-bredolab-botnet	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
Retadup	O	O	O	O	O	O
botnet	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
2019	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
decoded.avast.io	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
janvojtesek	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
putting-an-end-to-retadup-a-malicious-worm-that-infected-hundreds-of-thousands	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Whether	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
realistic	O	O	O	O	O	O
endeavor	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
today	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
world	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
another	O	O	O	O	O	O
question	O	O	O	O	O	O
altogether	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

