<DOCSTART>	O	O	O	O	O	O

Iran	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
’	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
s	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
domestic	O	O	O	O	O	O
espionage	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lessons	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
recent	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
leaks	O	O	O	O	O	O

Jul	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
08	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE

By	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Intel	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
471	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Global	O	O	O	O	O	O
Research	O	O	O	O	O	O
Team	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
last	O	O	O	O	O	O
decade	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iran	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
undergone	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
quiet	O	O	O	O	O	O
revolution	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Since	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
Green	O	O	O	O	O	O
Movement	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
uprising	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
2009	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iranians	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
dared	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
openly	O	O	O	O	O	O
oppose	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
regime	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
reasons	O	O	O	O	O	O
include	O	O	O	O	O	O
accusations	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
elections	O	O	O	O	O	O
tampering	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
global	O	O	O	O	O	O
sanctions	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
increased	O	O	O	O	O	O
inflation	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
heavy	O	O	O	O	O	O
investment	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
state	O	O	O	O	O	O
funds	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
nuclear	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
arming	O	O	O	O	O	O
programs	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
ambitious	O	O	O	O	O	O
regional	O	O	O	O	O	O
policies	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lebanon	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Syria	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iraq	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Yemen	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
others	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
amid	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
deteriorating	O	O	O	O	O	O
socioeconomic	O	O	O	O	O	O
situation	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
average	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iranian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

There	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
lot	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
talk	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
past	O	O	O	O	O	O
about	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iran	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
’	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
s	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
espionage	O	O	O	O	O	O
measures	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
offensive	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyber	O	O	O	O	O	O
activities	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeting	O	O	O	O	O	O
other	O	O	O	O	O	O
countries	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

However	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
growing	O	O	O	O	O	O
domestic	O	O	O	O	O	O
unrest	O	O	O	O	O	O
prompted	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iranian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
regime	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
invest	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
resources	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
developing	O	O	O	O	O	O
espionage	O	O	O	O	O	O
capabilities	O	O	O	O	O	O
aimed	O	O	O	O	O	O
against	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
own	O	O	O	O	O	O
citizens	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Additionally	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
regime	O	O	O	O	O	O
carried	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O
tough	O	O	O	O	O	O
measures	O	O	O	O	O	O
against	O	O	O	O	O	O
civil	O	O	O	O	O	O
uprisings	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
cutting	O	O	O	O	O	O
off	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
internet	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
country	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
long	O	O	O	O	O	O
periods	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
time	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
killing	O	O	O	O	O	O
hundreds	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
protestors	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

During	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
past	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
year	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
number	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
online	O	O	O	O	O	O
activists	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
leaked	O	O	O	O	O	O
what	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
claim	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
inside	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
about	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
regime	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
surveillance	O	O	O	O	O	O
methods	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
attempt	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
expose	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
unethical	O	O	O	O	O	O
tactics	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iranian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
security	O	O	O	O	O	O
forces	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Among	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
top	O	O	O	O	O	O
whistleblowers	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
operators	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lab	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dookhtegan	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
translated	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Persian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
stitched	O	O	O	O	O	O
lips	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
Telegram	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
channel	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
activist	O	O	O	O	O	O
named	O	O	O	O	O	O
Masoud	O	O	O	O	O	O
Molavi	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Molavi	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
assassinated	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iranian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
agents	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
November	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
2019	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
former	O	O	O	O	O	O
cybersecurity	O	O	O	O	O	O
official	O	O	O	O	O	O
behind	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Black	O	O	O	O	O	O
Box	O	O	O	O	O	O
Telegram	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
channel	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
responsible	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
many	O	O	O	O	O	O
notable	O	O	O	O	O	O
leaks	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iranian	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
government	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
series	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
leaks	O	O	O	O	O	O
uncovered	O	O	O	O	O	O
hundreds	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
documents	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
offer	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
glimpse	O	O	O	O	O	O
into	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
way	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iran	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
spying	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
own	O	O	O	O	O	O
people	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

According	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
leaked	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Islamic	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Revolutionary	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Guard	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Corps	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
IRGC	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iranian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Ministry	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Intelligence	O	O	O	O	O	O
Services	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
MOIS	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
developed	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
numerous	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
tools	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
,	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
malicious	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
software	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
surveillance	O	O	O	O	O	O
systems	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
analysis	O	O	O	O	O	O
platforms	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
order	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
control	O	O	O	O	O	O
citizens	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iran	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
abroad	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Much	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
activity	O	O	O	O	O	O
allegedly	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
conducted	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Rana	O	O	O	O	O	O
Intelligent	O	O	O	O	O	O
Computing	O	O	O	O	O	O
Institute	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
organization	O	O	O	O	O	O
working	O	O	O	O	O	O
under	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iranian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
MOIS	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
involved	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
internal	O	O	O	O	O	O
espionage	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
developing	O	O	O	O	O	O
unique	O	O	O	O	O	O
tools	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaining	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
variety	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
foreign	O	O	O	O	O	O
countries	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
infrastructure	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tools	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Techniques	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
Domestic	O	O	O	O	O	O
Espionage	O	O	O	O	O	O

According	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
shared	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
these	O	O	O	O	O	O
whistleblowers	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iran	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
heavily	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
investing	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
in	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
the	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
development	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
of	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
customized	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
tools	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
and	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
malicious	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
software	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
for	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
domestic	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
espionage	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
.	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O

For	O	O	O	O	O	O
example	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iranian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
regime	O	O	O	O	O	O
developed	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
surveillance	O	O	O	O	O	O
system	O	O	O	O	O	O
dubbed	O	O	O	O	O	O
Abi	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
allegedly	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
spy	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
political	O	O	O	O	O	O
activists	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
human	O	O	O	O	O	O
rights	O	O	O	O	O	O
lawyers	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
regime	O	O	O	O	O	O
opponents	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
protesters	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
intercepting	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bluetooth	O	O	O	O	O	O
communications	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

According	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iranian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
called	O	O	O	O	O	O
Arezooyenatamam	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
translated	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Persian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
‘	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
unfinished	O	O	O	O	O	O
dream	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
system	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
installed	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
pickup	O	O	O	O	O	O
trucks	O	O	O	O	O	O
posted	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
strategic	O	O	O	O	O	O
locations	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iran	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
university	O	O	O	O	O	O
campuses	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
protest	O	O	O	O	O	O
centers	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
d39ec1uo9ktrut.cloudfront.net	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
pasted-image	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
0	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

A	O	O	O	O	O	O
screenshot	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Abi	O	O	O	O	O	O
system	O	O	O	O	O	O
monitoring	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Sharif	O	O	O	O	O	O
UniversityThe	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iranian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
regime	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
developed	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
customized	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
malware	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
used	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
for	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
stealing	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
information	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
from	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
citizens	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

One	O	O	O	O	O	O
example	O	O	O	O	O	O
found	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
those	O	O	O	O	O	O
leaks	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
called	O	O	O	O	O	O
WinspySuite	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
remote	O	O	O	O	B-TACTIC	O
access	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
and	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
information	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
stealing	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
malware	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
reportedly	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
specifically	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
spy	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
suspects	O	O	O	O	O	O
arrested	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
regime	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Internally	O	O	O	O	O	O
referred	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
Peyvand	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
allegedly	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
was	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
loaded	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
onto	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
a	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
target	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
’	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
s	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
computer	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
via	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
a	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
USB	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
flash	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
drive	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
during	O	O	O	O	O	O
interrogations	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
sent	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
via	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
a	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
malicious	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
link	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
to	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
a	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
victim	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
’	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
s	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
email	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
address	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
.	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
regime	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
developed	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
a	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
remote	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
access	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
tool	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
Android	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
iPhone	O	O	O	O	O	O
mobile	O	O	O	O	O	O
devices	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
part	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
project	O	O	O	O	O	O
dubbed	O	O	O	O	O	O
Project	O	O	O	O	O	O
220	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
purportedly	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
able	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	B-TACTIC	O
steal	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
sensitive	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
data	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
from	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
a	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
victim	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
’	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
s	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
device	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
,	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
including	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
call	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
data	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
,	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
text	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
messages	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
,	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
contacts	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
and	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
locations	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
.	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
d39ec1uo9ktrut.cloudfront.net	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
pasted-image	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
0	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
3	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

A	O	O	O	O	O	O
screenshot	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Winspy	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
Suite	O	O	O	I-MALWARE	O	I-MALWARE
control	O	O	O	O	O	O
panelAnother	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
project	O	O	O	O	O	O
dubbed	O	O	O	O	O	O
Project	O	O	O	O	O	O
420	O	O	O	O	O	O
aka	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dolphin	O	O	O	O	O	O
developed	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
deployed	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
controlled	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
undisclosed	O	O	O	O	O	O
mobile	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
capable	O	O	O	O	B-TACTIC	O
of	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
collecting	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
and	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
analyzing	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
information	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
about	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
activities	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
individuals	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
groups	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
social	O	O	O	O	O	O
media	O	O	O	O	O	O
networks	O	O	O	O	O	O
including	O	O	O	O	O	O
Facebook	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Twitter	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Instagram	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
messaging	O	O	O	O	O	O
applications	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
Telegram	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

According	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
leaked	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
regime	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
only	O	O	O	O	O	O
developed	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
tools	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
for	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
stealing	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
sensitive	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
data	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
citizens	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
but	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
created	O	O	O	O	B-TACTIC	O
designated	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
platforms	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
for	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
the	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
collection	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
and	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
analysis	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
of	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
the	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
data	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

A	O	O	O	O	O	O
system	O	O	O	O	O	O
dubbed	O	O	O	O	O	O
Payamak	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
developed	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
store	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
analyze	O	O	O	O	O	O
text	O	O	O	O	O	O
messages	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeted	O	O	O	O	O	O
subjects	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

A	O	O	O	O	O	O
software	O	O	O	O	O	O
called	O	O	O	O	O	O
Seraj	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
analytical	O	O	O	O	O	O
search	O	O	O	O	O	O
engine	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
suspects	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
employees	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
intelligence	O	O	O	O	O	O
operations	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
arrests	O	O	O	O	O	O
related	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
MOIS	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Another	O	O	O	O	O	O
system	O	O	O	O	O	O
mentioned	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
reports	O	O	O	O	O	O
dubbed	O	O	O	O	O	O
Shojreh	O	O	O	O	O	O
includes	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
mapping	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
family	O	O	O	O	O	O
relations	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Jewish	O	O	O	O	O	O
people	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iran	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
abroad	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Additionally	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
IRGC	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
MOIS	O	O	O	O	O	O
gained	O	O	O	O	O	O
unauthorized	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
legitimate	O	O	O	O	O	O
services	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
websites	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
spy	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iranian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
citizens	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

For	O	O	O	O	O	O
example	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
MOIS	O	O	O	O	O	O
would	O	O	O	O	O	O
compromise	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iran	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
’	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
s	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
National	O	O	O	O	O	O
Library	O	O	O	O	O	O
computer	O	O	O	O	O	O
network	O	O	O	O	O	O
seeking	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
obtain	O	O	O	O	O	O
personal	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
about	O	O	O	O	O	O
users	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
mainly	O	O	O	O	O	O
students	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
political	O	O	O	O	O	O
prisoners	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
topics	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
interest	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
MOIS	O	O	O	O	O	O
allegedly	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
abused	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
send	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
phishing	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
emails	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
with	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
malicious	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
attachments	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
library	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
official	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
account	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tracking	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iranians	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Abroad	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
addition	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
all	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
above	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iranian	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
government	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
making	O	O	O	O	O	O
great	O	O	O	O	O	O
efforts	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
monitor	O	O	O	O	O	O
citizens	O	O	O	O	O	O
going	O	O	O	O	O	O
abroad	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
surveying	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
analyzing	O	O	O	O	O	O
location	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
obtained	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iranian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
cellular	O	O	O	O	O	O
operators	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
system	O	O	O	O	O	O
called	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pouya	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
compromising	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
infrastructure	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
foreign	O	O	O	O	O	O
companies	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
d39ec1uo9ktrut.cloudfront.net	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
pasted-image	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
0	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
4	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

A	O	O	O	O	O	O
screenshot	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pouya	O	O	O	O	O	O
systemIn	O	O	O	O	O	O
2019	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
unknown	O	O	O	O	O	O
activist	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
activists	O	O	O	O	O	O
launched	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
site	O	O	O	O	O	O
called	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vagheyatepenhaan	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
translated	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Persian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
‘	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
hidden	O	O	O	O	O	O
facts	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
expose	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iranian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
regime	O	O	O	O	O	O
espionage-related	O	O	O	O	O	O
activity	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
site	O	O	O	O	O	O
contains	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
large	O	O	O	O	O	O
section	O	O	O	O	O	O
about	O	O	O	O	O	O
espionage	O	O	O	O	O	O
enterprises	O	O	O	O	O	O
outside	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iran	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
conducted	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
monitor	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
movement	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iranians	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
traveling	O	O	O	O	O	O
abroad	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

According	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
regime	O	O	O	O	O	O
gained	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
computer	O	O	O	O	O	O
systems	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
numerous	O	O	O	O	O	O
airline	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
companies	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bahrain	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dubai	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
India	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Indonesia	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Malaysia	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pakistan	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Philippines	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Qatar	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Saudi	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Arabia	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Thailand	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
United	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Arab	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
Emirates	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
UAE	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	B-TACTIC	O
collection	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
on	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
flights	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
of	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
Iranian	B-LOC	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	B-LOC
citizens	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
.	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
another	O	O	O	O	O	O
case	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
leaked	O	O	O	O	O	O
documents	O	O	O	O	O	O
showed	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
government	O	O	O	O	O	O
worked	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
project	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
aimed	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
compromise	O	O	O	O	O	O
hotel	O	O	O	O	O	O
websites	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Republic	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
of	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
Georgia	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
neighboring	O	O	O	O	O	O
country	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
popular	O	O	O	O	O	O
holiday	O	O	O	O	O	O
destination	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iranians	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

While	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
considered	O	O	O	O	O	O
revealing	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
It	O	O	O	O	O	O
should	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
noted	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
these	O	O	O	O	O	O
leaks	O	O	O	O	O	O
provide	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
very	O	O	O	O	O	O
narrow	O	O	O	O	O	O
window	O	O	O	O	O	O
into	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
full	O	O	O	O	O	O
extent	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Iranian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
regime	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
priorities	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

However	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
disclosed	O	O	O	O	O	O
provides	O	O	O	O	O	O
evidence	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
time	O	O	O	O	O	O
goes	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
motivation	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
expose	O	O	O	O	O	O
these	O	O	O	O	O	O
activities	O	O	O	O	O	O
likely	O	O	O	O	O	O
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
remain	O	O	O	O	O	O
high	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

