<DOCSTART>	O	O	O	O	O	O

I	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
ll	O	O	O	O	O	O
preface	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
post	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
saying	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
I	O	O	O	O	O	O
possess	O	O	O	O	O	O
no	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
incident	O	O	O	O	O	O
beyond	O	O	O	O	O	O
what	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
mentioned	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
open	O	O	O	O	O	O
sources	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
post	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
my	O	O	O	O	O	O
personal	O	O	O	O	O	O
opinion	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
based	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
my	O	O	O	O	O	O
experience	O	O	O	O	O	O
researching	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
tracking	O	O	O	O	O	O
both	O	O	O	O	O	O
state	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
non-state	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyber	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

I	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
ll	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
add	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
Intel	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
471	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
intel471	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
com	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
does	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
actively	O	O	O	O	O	O
research	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
track	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
involved	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
espionage	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
focused	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
on	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
financially	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
motivated	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
cyber	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
criminals	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
hacktivists	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
politically	O	O	O	O	O	O
motivated	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

On	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
June	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
14	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Washington	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Post	O	O	O	O	O	O
published	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
story	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.washingtonpost.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
world	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
national-security	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
russian-government-hackers-penetrated-dnc-stole-opposition-research-on-trump	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2016	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
06	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
14	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
cf006cb4	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
316e	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
11e6	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
8ff7	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
7b6c1998b7a0	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
story.html	O	O	O	O	O	O
?	O	O	O	O	O	O
hpid	O	O	O	O	O	O
=	O	O	O	O	O	O
hp	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
hp-banner-main	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
dnc-hackers	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
1145a-banner	O	O	O	O	O	O
%	O	O	O	O	O	O
3Ahomepage	O	O	O	O	O	O
%	O	O	O	O	O	O
2Fstory	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
indicated	O	O	O	O	O	O
Russian	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
government	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
hackers	O	O	O	O	O	O
had	O	O	O	O	O	O
hacked	O	O	O	O	O	O
into	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Democratic	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
National	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Committee	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
DNC	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
specific	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
linking	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
hack	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Russian	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
government	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
came	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyber	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
security	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
company	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
CrowdStrike	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.crowdstrike.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

>	O	O	O	O	O	O
One	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
CrowdStrike	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
had	O	O	O	O	O	O
dubbed	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cozy	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
Bear	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
had	O	O	O	O	O	O
gained	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
last	O	O	O	O	O	O
summer	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
monitoring	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
DNC	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
chat	O	O	O	O	O	O
communications	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Alperovitch	O	O	O	O	O	O
said	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

>	O	O	O	O	O	O

>	O	O	O	O	O	O

>	O	O	O	O	O	O
The	O	O	O	O	O	O
other	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
firm	O	O	O	O	O	O
had	O	O	O	O	O	O
named	O	O	O	O	O	O
Fancy	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
Bear	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
broke	O	O	O	O	O	O
into	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
network	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
late	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
April	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeted	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
opposition	O	O	O	O	O	O
research	O	O	O	O	O	O
files	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

>	O	O	O	O	O	O

>	O	O	O	O	O	O

I	O	O	O	O	O	O
personally	O	O	O	O	O	O
know	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
number	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
smart	O	O	O	O	O	O
people	O	O	O	O	O	O
who	O	O	O	O	O	O
work	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
CrowdStrike	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
I	O	O	O	O	O	O
trust	O	O	O	O	O	O
them	O	O	O	O	O	O
when	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
say	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
specific	O	O	O	O	O	O
intrusion	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
incident	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
linked	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
specific	O	O	O	O	O	O
hacking	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

With	O	O	O	O	O	O
regards	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
linking	O	O	O	O	O	O
intrusion	O	O	O	O	O	O
sets	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
groups	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
CrowdStrike	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
uses	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
animal	O	O	O	O	O	O
naming	O	O	O	O	O	O
scheme	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
tie	O	O	O	O	O	O
intrusion	O	O	O	O	O	O
activity	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
intrusion	O	O	O	O	O	O
sets	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
groups	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
countries	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
case	O	O	O	O	O	O
CrowdStrike	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
said	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
intrusions	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
DNC	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
tied	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
groups	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
call	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cozy	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
Bear	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Fancy	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
Bear	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
where	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bear	O	O	O	O	O	O
signifies	O	O	O	O	O	O
Russia	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

I	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
no	O	O	O	O	O	O
doubts	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
all	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
CrowdStrike	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
indeed	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
intrusion	O	O	O	O	O	O
set	O	O	O	O	O	O
activity	O	O	O	O	O	O
within	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
DNC	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
environment	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
linked	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
these	O	O	O	O	O	O
groups	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
had	O	O	O	O	O	O
identified	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
were	O	O	O	O	O	O
almost	O	O	O	O	O	O
certainly	O	O	O	O	O	O
actively	O	O	O	O	O	O
tracking	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Guccifer	O	O	O	O	O	O
2.0	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
A	O	O	O	O	O	O
spanner	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
works	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

On	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
June	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
15	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
who	O	O	O	O	O	O
calls	O	O	O	O	O	O
himself	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Guccifer	O	O	O	O	O	O
2.0	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
created	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
Wordpress	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
guccifer2	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
wordpress.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
where	O	O	O	O	O	O
he	O	O	O	O	O	O
posted	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
number	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
claimed	O	O	O	O	O	O
confidential	O	O	O	O	O	O
reports	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
DNC	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
including	O	O	O	O	O	O
one	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
Donald	O	O	O	O	O	O
Trump	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
post	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
effort	O	O	O	O	O	O
appears	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
made	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
say	O	O	O	O	O	O
how	O	O	O	O	O	O
easy	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
hack	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
DNC	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
called	O	O	O	O	O	O
into	O	O	O	O	O	O
question	O	O	O	O	O	O
CrowdStrike	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
who	O	O	O	O	O	O
linked	O	O	O	O	O	O
two	O	O	O	O	O	O
intrusions	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
DNC	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Russian	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
government	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

For	O	O	O	O	O	O
those	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
aren	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
t	O	O	O	O	O	O
aware	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
handle	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Guccifer	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
en.wikipedia.org	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wiki	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
Guccifer	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
Romanian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
hacker	O	O	O	O	O	O
who	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
recently	O	O	O	O	O	O
extradited	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
United	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
involved	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
hacking	O	O	O	O	O	O
high	O	O	O	O	O	O
profile	O	O	O	O	O	O
people	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
politicians	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
celebrities	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
publicly	O	O	O	O	O	O
releasing	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
emails	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Guccifer	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
currently	O	O	O	O	O	O
sits	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
jail	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Virginia	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
awaiting	O	O	O	O	O	O
sentencing	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Russia	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Attribution	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
hard	O	O	O	O	O	O
right	O	O	O	O	O	O
?	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

When	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
comes	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
attribution	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
intrusions	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
groups	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
specific	O	O	O	O	O	O
people	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
really	O	O	O	O	O	O
talking	O	O	O	O	O	O
about	O	O	O	O	O	O
two	O	O	O	O	O	O
things	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Attribution	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
intrusion	O	O	O	O	O	O
sets	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
exploits	O	O	O	O	O	O
etc	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
known	O	O	O	O	O	O
intrusion	O	O	O	O	O	O
groups	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
where	O	O	O	O	O	O
CrowdStrike	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
tied	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
activity	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
groups	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
call	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cozy	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
Bear	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Fancy	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
Bear	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Attribution	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
grouping	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
specific	O	O	O	O	O	O
person	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
organization	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
nation	O	O	O	O	O	O
state	O	O	O	O	O	O
where	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
case	O	O	O	O	O	O
CrowdStrike	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
clearly	O	O	O	O	O	O
singled	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O
Russia	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
lot	O	O	O	O	O	O
harder	O	O	O	O	O	O
than	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
previous	O	O	O	O	O	O
point	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

On	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
first	O	O	O	O	O	O
point	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
I	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
complete	O	O	O	O	O	O
confidence	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
CrowdStrike	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
able	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
track	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
link	O	O	O	O	O	O
specific	O	O	O	O	O	O
intrusions	O	O	O	O	O	O
tools	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
known	O	O	O	O	O	O
groups	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
actively	O	O	O	O	O	O
track	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

On	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
second	O	O	O	O	O	O
point	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
little	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
unclear	O	O	O	O	O	O
whether	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
activity	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
tied	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Russian	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
government	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
I	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
t	O	O	O	O	O	O
really	O	O	O	O	O	O
comment	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
I	O	O	O	O	O	O
don	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
t	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
supports	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
type	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
attribution	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
done	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
number	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
ways	O	O	O	O	O	O
but	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
limited	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tracking	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
specific	O	O	O	O	O	O
targets	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
target	O	O	O	O	O	O
sectors	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
long	O	O	O	O	O	O
period	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
time	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
mapping	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
against	O	O	O	O	O	O
nation	O	O	O	O	O	O
state	O	O	O	O	O	O
objectives	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Confidential	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
internal	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
within	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
DNC	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
would	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
clear	O	O	O	O	O	O
interest	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Russian	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
government	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
other	O	O	O	O	O	O
governments	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
might	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
interest	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
politically	O	O	O	O	O	O
motivated	O	O	O	O	O	O
hacker	O	O	O	O	O	O
who	O	O	O	O	O	O
would	O	O	O	O	O	O
want	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
discredit	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
DNC	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
publishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
sensitive	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Researching	O	O	O	O	O	O
intrusion	O	O	O	O	O	O
activity	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
identifying	O	O	O	O	O	O
operational	O	O	O	O	O	O
security	O	O	O	O	O	O
failures	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
behalf	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
intrusion	O	O	O	O	O	O
operators	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

A	O	O	O	O	O	O
good	O	O	O	O	O	O
example	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
where	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
iSIGHT	O	O	O	O	O	O
Partners	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
isightpartners.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
able	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
tie	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
http	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
freebeacon.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
national-security	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyber-caliphate-hackers-not-linked-to-islamic-state	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
claimed	O	O	O	O	O	O
Islamic	O	O	O	O	O	O
State	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
ISIL	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
hacking	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
Russian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
track	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT28	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Guccifer	O	O	O	O	O	O
2.0	O	O	O	O	O	O
did	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
!	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

One	O	O	O	O	O	O
thing	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
sure	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Guccifer	O	O	O	O	O	O
2.0	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
he	O	O	O	O	O	O
clearly	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
demonstrated	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
internal	O	O	O	O	O	O
documents	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
DNC	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Given	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
I	O	O	O	O	O	O
believe	O	O	O	O	O	O
there	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
two	O	O	O	O	O	O
possibilities	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
One	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
both	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
groups	O	O	O	O	O	O
identified	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
CrowdStrike	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
tied	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Guccifer	O	O	O	O	O	O
2.0	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
disinformation	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
against	O	O	O	O	O	O
CrowdStrike	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
DNC	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Guccifer	O	O	O	O	O	O
2.0	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
distinct	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
who	O	O	O	O	O	O
had	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
DNC	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
systems	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
some	O	O	O	O	O	O
point	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

At	O	O	O	O	O	O
no	O	O	O	O	O	O
way	O	O	O	O	O	O
does	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
mean	O	O	O	O	O	O
CrowdStrike	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
wrong	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
linking	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
activity	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
saw	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
DNC	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
environment	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

I	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
ve	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
numerous	O	O	O	O	O	O
occasions	O	O	O	O	O	O
where	O	O	O	O	O	O
organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
compromised	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
multiple	O	O	O	O	O	O
different	O	O	O	O	O	O
intrusion	O	O	O	O	O	O
groups	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
evidence	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
one	O	O	O	O	O	O
intrusion	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
being	O	O	O	O	O	O
active	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
victim	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
environment	O	O	O	O	O	O
doesn	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
t	O	O	O	O	O	O
mean	O	O	O	O	O	O
another	O	O	O	O	O	O
intrusion	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
t	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
active	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
same	O	O	O	O	O	O
environment	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
same	O	O	O	O	O	O
time	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

On	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Guccifer	O	O	O	O	O	O
2.0	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
being	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
possible	O	O	O	O	O	O
disinformation	O	O	O	O	O	O
operation	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
I	O	O	O	O	O	O
recommend	O	O	O	O	O	O
closely	O	O	O	O	O	O
looking	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Guccifer	O	O	O	O	O	O
2.0	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
writing	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Based	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
style	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
how	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
done	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
looks	O	O	O	O	O	O
like	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
written	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
someone	O	O	O	O	O	O
who	O	O	O	O	O	O
doesn	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
t	O	O	O	O	O	O
speak	O	O	O	O	O	O
English	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
first	O	O	O	O	O	O
language	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
uses	O	O	O	O	O	O
mannerisms	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
people	O	O	O	O	O	O
based	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Eastern	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Europe	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
purposely	O	O	O	O	O	O
written	O	O	O	O	O	O
like	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

I	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
recommend	O	O	O	O	O	O
reading	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Twitter	O	O	O	O	O	O
timeline	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
pwnallthethings	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
twitter.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
pwnallthethings	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
talks	O	O	O	O	O	O
about	O	O	O	O	O	O
claimed	O	O	O	O	O	O
operational	O	O	O	O	O	O
security	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
OPSEC	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
failures	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
behalf	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Guccifer	O	O	O	O	O	O
2.0	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
various	O	O	O	O	O	O
files	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
were	O	O	O	O	O	O
uploaded	O	O	O	O	O	O
online	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

I	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
ll	O	O	O	O	O	O
add	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
initially	O	O	O	O	O	O
I	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
surprised	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
how	O	O	O	O	O	O
quickly	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
disinformation	O	O	O	O	O	O
operation	O	O	O	O	O	O
could	O	O	O	O	O	O
possibly	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
executed	O	O	O	O	O	O
after	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Washington	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Post	O	O	O	O	O	O
article	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Final	O	O	O	O	O	O
Remarks	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

I	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
ll	O	O	O	O	O	O
finish	O	O	O	O	O	O
things	O	O	O	O	O	O
off	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
repeating	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
my	O	O	O	O	O	O
opinion	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
emergence	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Guccifer	O	O	O	O	O	O
2.0	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
does	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
all	O	O	O	O	O	O
conflict	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
CrowdStrike	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
findings	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Guccifer	O	O	O	O	O	O
2.0	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
may	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
separate	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
may	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
tied	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
one	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
both	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
intrusion	O	O	O	O	O	O
groups	O	O	O	O	O	O
CrowdStrike	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
claims	O	O	O	O	O	O
were	O	O	O	O	O	O
active	O	O	O	O	O	O
inside	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
DNC	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

