<DOCSTART>	O	O	O	O	O	O

APT-C	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
-	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
36	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
recent	O	O	O	O	O	O
activity	O	O	O	O	O	O
analysis	O	O	O	O	O	O

January	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
15	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE

From	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
tracking	O	O	O	O	O	O
during	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
last	O	O	O	O	O	O
months	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
activity	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT-C	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
-	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
36	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
named	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
publicly	O	O	O	O	O	O
introduced	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Company	O	O	O	O	O	O
360	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
last	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
year	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
article	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
highlighted	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
main	O	O	O	O	O	O
objective	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
companies	O	O	O	O	O	O
located	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Colombia	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

If	O	O	O	O	O	O
you	O	O	O	O	O	O
don	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
t	O	O	O	O	O	O
know	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT-C	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
-	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
36	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
recommend	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
article	O	O	O	O	O	O
mentioned	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
July	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
2019	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
company	O	O	O	O	O	O
TrendMicro	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
published	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
article	O	O	O	O	O	O
related	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
another	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
seems	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
focused	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
Colombia	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
some	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
TTPs	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
T	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
actics	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
T	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
echniques	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
P	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
rocedures	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
overlap	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT-C	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
-	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
36	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
although	O	O	O	O	O	O
TrendMicro	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
indicates	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
don	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
t	O	O	O	O	O	O
consider	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
advanced	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
had	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
different	O	O	O	O	O	O
very	O	O	O	O	O	O
recent	O	O	O	O	O	O
spear-phishings	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
following	O	O	O	O	O	O
summary	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
obtained	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
analysis	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
these	O	O	O	O	O	O
mails	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
This	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
already	O	O	O	O	O	O
mentioned	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
articles	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
knows	O	O	O	O	O	O
well	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Spanish	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
language	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
They	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
usually	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
use	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
different	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
types	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
of	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
url	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
shorteners	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
in	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
their	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
mailings	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
case	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
cort.as	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
shortenner	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
caught	O	O	O	O	O	O
our	O	O	O	O	O	O
attention	O	O	O	O	O	O
since	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
shortener	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Spanish	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
newspaper	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
El	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Pais	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
belongs	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
Prisa	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Group	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
very	O	O	O	O	O	O
spread	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Latin	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
America	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
We	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
links	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
to	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
docs.google.com	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
,	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
mediafire	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
and	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
onedrive	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
to	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
download	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
the	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
samples	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
inside	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
some	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
malspam	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
emails	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Their	O	O	O	O	O	O
most	O	O	O	O	O	O
popular	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
LimeRAT	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
although	O	O	O	O	O	O
many	O	O	O	O	O	O
others	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
found	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
indicated	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
reports	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

VJWorm	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
recently	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
different	O	O	O	B-TACTIC	O	B-TACTIC
techniques	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
for	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
exfiltration	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
It	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
some	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
spear-phishings	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
exfiltration	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
by	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
Yopmail	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
’	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
s	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
HTTPS	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
webmail	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
service	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
.	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
coincides	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
indications	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
TrendMicro	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
The	O	O	O	O	O	O
most	O	O	O	O	O	O
common	O	O	O	O	O	O
dynamic	O	O	O	O	O	O
domains	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

1	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
duckdns	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
org	O	O	O	O	O	O

2	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
publicvm	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
com	O	O	O	O	O	O

3	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
linkpc	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
net	O	O	O	O	O	O

Since	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
does	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
enough	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
able	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
say	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
everything	O	O	O	O	O	O
analyzed	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
single	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
only	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
said	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
these	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
different	O	O	O	O	O	O
techniques	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
attack	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
country	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

From	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
infrastructure	O	O	O	B-TACTIC	O	B-TACTIC
used	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
by	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
the	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
attackers	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
as	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
command	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
and	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
control	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
servers	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
when	O	O	O	O	O	O
executing	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
analyzed	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
following	O	O	O	O	O	O
graph	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
obtained	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
io	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
uploads	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2020	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
01	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
image1	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

Three	O	O	O	O	O	O
sets	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
clusters	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
ip	O	O	O	O	O	O
addresses	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
identified	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
each	O	O	O	O	O	O
one	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
some	O	O	O	O	O	O
characteristics	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cluster	O	O	O	O	O	O
A	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
following	O	O	O	O	O	O
characteristics	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
All	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
infrastructure	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
geolocated	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Colombia	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

All	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
IPs	O	O	O	O	O	O
correspond	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
Colombian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
ISPs	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
IPs	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
This	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
perhaps	O	O	O	O	O	O
one	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
most	O	O	O	O	O	O
outstanding	O	O	O	O	O	O
aspects	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Domains	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
reused	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
ip	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
points	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
changed	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
This	O	O	O	O	O	O
cluster	O	O	O	O	O	O
only	O	O	O	O	O	O
uses	O	O	O	O	O	O
free	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
duckdns.org	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
domains	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cluster	O	O	O	O	O	O
B	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
following	O	O	O	O	O	O
characteristics	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Its	O	O	O	O	O	O
infrastructure	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
located	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Colombia	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Costa	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Rica	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Panama	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
geolocated	O	O	O	O	O	O
ip	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
United	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
correspond	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
domains	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
sinkholed	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

By	O	O	O	O	O	O
obtaining	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
about	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
IPs	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
how	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
using	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
VPN	O	O	O	O	O	O
service	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
allows	O	O	O	O	O	O
having	O	O	O	O	O	O
geolocalized	O	O	O	O	O	O
IPs	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Colombia	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Costa	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Rica	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Panama	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
service	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
called	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
Powerhouse	O	O	O	O	O	O
Management	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
phmgmt	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
com	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Therefore	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
cluster	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
compromising	O	O	O	O	O	O
infrastructure	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Colombian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
ISP	O	O	O	O	O	O
clients	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
but	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
using	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
VPN	O	O	O	O	O	O
service	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
This	O	O	O	O	O	O
cluster	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
reusing	O	O	O	O	O	O
domains	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
changing	O	O	O	O	O	O
ip	O	O	O	O	O	O
addresses	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
lot	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

They	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
very	O	O	O	O	O	O
short	O	O	O	O	O	O
duration	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
This	O	O	O	O	O	O
cluster	O	O	O	O	O	O
uses	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
SLD	O	O	O	O	O	O
linkpc.net	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
publicvm.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
This	O	O	O	O	O	O
cluster	O	O	O	O	O	O
coincides	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
part	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
domains	O	O	O	O	O	O
registered	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
report	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
company	O	O	O	O	O	O
360	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT-C	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
-	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
36	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cluster	O	O	O	O	O	O
C	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
following	O	O	O	O	O	O
characteristics	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
All	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
infrastructure	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
geolocated	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Colombia	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

All	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
IPs	O	O	O	O	O	O
correspond	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
Colombian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
ISPs	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
IPs	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
In	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
case	O	O	O	O	O	O
many	O	O	O	O	O	O
domains	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
few	O	O	O	O	O	O
ip	O	O	O	O	O	O
addresses	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
This	O	O	O	O	O	O
cluster	O	O	O	O	O	O
uses	O	O	O	O	O	O
free	O	O	O	O	O	O
domains	O	O	O	O	O	O
duckdns.org	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Among	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
domains	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
these	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
highlight	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
domain	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
cobroserfinansa	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
com	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
domain	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
solved	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
than	O	O	O	O	O	O
150	O	O	O	O	O	O
different	O	O	O	O	O	O
ip	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
157	O	O	O	O	O	O
exactly	O	O	O	O	O	O
when	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
report	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
made	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
where	O	O	O	O	O	O
all	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
them	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
located	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Colombia	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Another	O	O	O	O	O	O
outstanding	O	O	O	O	O	O
aspect	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
infrastructure	O	O	O	O	O	O
point	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
view	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
ip	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
located	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Colombia	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
correspond	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
high	O	O	O	O	O	O
probability	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
ip	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
routers	O	O	O	O	O	O
compromised	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
attackers	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
hypothesis	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
attackers	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
compromise	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
routers	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
with	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
default	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
credentials	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
and	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
use	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
them	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
as	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
a	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
frontend	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
for	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
their	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
real	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
command	O	O	O	B-TACTIC	I-TECHNIQUE	B-TACTIC
and	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	I-TECHNIQUE	I-TACTIC
control	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	I-TECHNIQUE	I-TACTIC
server	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	I-TECHNIQUE	I-TACTIC
.	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	I-TECHNIQUE	I-TACTIC

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
fact	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
verified	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
but	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
common	O	O	O	O	O	O
TTP	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
other	O	O	O	O	O	O
groups	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
routers	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
allow	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
use	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
iptables	O	O	O	O	O	O
command	O	O	O	O	O	O
so	O	O	O	O	O	O
automation	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
attackers	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
redirection	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
simple	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Conclusions	O	O	O	O	O	O

-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
The	O	O	O	O	O	O
attackers	O	O	O	O	O	O
know	O	O	O	O	O	O
well	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
language	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
attacked	O	O	O	O	O	O
country	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Spanish	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
so	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
could	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
considered	O	O	O	O	O	O
Spanish-speaking	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
countries	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
main	O	O	O	O	O	O
options	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
attacking	O	O	O	O	O	O
countries	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
aspect	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
already	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
indicated	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
other	O	O	O	O	O	O
reports	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

From	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
would	O	O	O	O	O	O
reinforce	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
hypothesis	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
use	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
shortener	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
cort.as	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
The	O	O	O	O	O	O
emails	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
are	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
well	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
written	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
and	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
are	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
almost	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
always	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
related	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
to	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
financial	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
matters	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
,	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
specifically	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
related	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
to	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
debt	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Currently	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
attackers	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
using	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
developed	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
themselves	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
using	O	O	O	O	O	O
public	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
projects	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
LimeRAT	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Attackers	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
using	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
high	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
ports	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
to	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
communicate	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
with	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
command	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
and	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
control	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
servers	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
.	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Attackers	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
probably	O	O	O	O	O	O
using	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
multi-level	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
command	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
and	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
control	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
architectures	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
to	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
hide	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
the	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
main	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
command	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
and	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
control	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
server	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
.	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE

As	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
first	O	O	O	O	O	O
level	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
until	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
moment	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

+	O	O	O	O	O	O
VPN	O	O	O	O	O	O
services	O	O	O	O	O	O
where	O	O	O	O	O	O
Colombia	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Panama	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Costa	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Rica	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
exist	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
outgoing	O	O	O	O	O	O
ip	O	O	O	O	O	O

+	O	O	O	O	O	O
Routers	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
ISP	O	O	O	O	O	O
clients	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
default	O	O	O	O	O	O
credentials	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
vulnerabilities	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

All	O	O	O	O	O	O
these	O	O	O	O	O	O
ISPs	O	O	O	O	O	O
belong	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
Colombia	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Attackers	O	O	O	O	O	O
use	O	O	O	O	O	O
shorteners	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
for	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
links	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
in	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
emails	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
.	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
advisable	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
watch	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
shortcuts	O	O	O	O	O	O
belonging	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
newspaper	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
El	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Pais	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Another	O	O	O	O	O	O
option	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
shorteners	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
links	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
file	O	O	O	O	O	O
hosting	O	O	O	O	O	O
services	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
google	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
mediafire	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
dropbox	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
etc	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
ti	O	O	O	O	O	O
.360	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
net	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
articles	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
apt-c	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
36	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
continuous-attacks-targeting-colombian-government-institutions-and-corporations-en	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
<	O	O	O	O	O	O
http	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog.la.trendmicro.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
proyecto-rat-una-campana-de-spam-dirigida-a-entidades-colombianas-a-traves-del-servicio-de-correo-electronico-yopmail	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

