<DOCSTART>	O	O	O	O	O	O

Winnti	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
Group	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
Geostrategic	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
TTP	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tactics	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Techniques	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Procedures	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

May	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
16	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2019	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Executive	O	O	O	O	O	O
Summary	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O

China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
one	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
world	O	O	O	O	O	O
powers	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
presence	O	O	O	O	O	O
within	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
international	O	O	O	O	O	O
market	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaming	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
sector	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
controlling	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Southeast	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Asian	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
market	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
even	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
than	O	O	O	O	O	O
half	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
global	O	O	O	O	O	O
market	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gaming	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
sector	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Winnti	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
Group	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
currently	O	O	O	O	O	O
considered	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
group	O	O	O	I-CON	O	I-CON
allegedly	O	O	O	O	O	O
attributed	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
government	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
of	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
China	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Among	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
various	O	O	O	O	O	O
targets	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
specializes	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
designing	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
executing	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyber-espionage	O	O	O	O	O	O
operations	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
companies	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gaming	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
sector	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
order	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
collect	O	O	O	O	O	O
classified	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
Game	O	O	O	O	O	O
Design	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Geostrategic	O	O	O	O	O	O
analysis	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Winnti	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
Group	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyber	O	O	O	O	O	O
attacks	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
Thailand	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaming	O	O	O	O	O	O
industry	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
increase	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyber-attacks	O	O	O	O	O	O
within	O	O	O	O	O	O
Southeast	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Asian	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
countries	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
correlating	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
progressive	O	O	O	O	O	O
shift	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
accumulation	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gross	O	O	O	O	O	O
Domestic	O	O	O	O	O	O
Product	O	O	O	O	O	O
towards	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
same	O	O	O	O	O	O
area	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Southeast	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Asia	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
forecast	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
evolution	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
global	O	O	O	O	O	O
economy	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
reflected	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
estimates	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
percentages	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
GDP	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gross	O	O	O	O	O	O
Domestic	O	O	O	O	O	O
Product	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
GDP	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gross	O	O	O	O	O	O
Domestic	O	O	O	O	O	O
Product	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
shown	O	O	O	O	O	O
below	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
es	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
uploads	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2019	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
05	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
Captura	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
12	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Illustration	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
The	O	O	O	O	O	O
Global	O	O	O	O	O	O
Economy	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
shifting	O	O	O	O	O	O
centre	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
gravity	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
es	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
uploads	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2019	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
05	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
Captura	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
13	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Illustration	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
Forecast	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
center	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
gravity	O	O	O	O	O	O
movement	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
global	O	O	O	O	O	O
economy	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

As	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
percentages	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
map	O	O	O	O	O	O
show	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
evolution	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
global	O	O	O	O	O	O
distribution	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
GDP	O	O	O	O	O	O
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
concentrated	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
countries	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Southeast	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Asia	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
same	O	O	O	O	O	O
area	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
industry	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
service	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
sector	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
increase	O	O	O	O	O	O
considerably	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
2045	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Innovations	O	O	O	O	O	O
within	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
IT	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
sector	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
continue	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
highly	O	O	O	O	O	O
confidential	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
those	O	O	O	O	O	O
companies	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
States	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
maintain	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
interest	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
economic	O	O	O	O	O	O
control	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Southeast	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Asian	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
area	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
3	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
gaming	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
”	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
sector	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
acquired	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
high	O	O	O	O	O	O
relevance	O	O	O	O	O	O
within	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
international	O	O	O	O	O	O
market	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
countries	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Southeast	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Asia	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
acquired	O	O	O	O	O	O
significant	O	O	O	O	O	O
relevance	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
relation	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
design	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
subsequent	O	O	O	O	O	O
production	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
4	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
As	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
following	O	O	O	O	O	O
graph	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
evolution	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
profitability	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
global	O	O	O	O	O	O
market	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaming	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
sector	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
remarkably	O	O	O	O	O	O
beneficial	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
clear	O	O	O	O	O	O
forecast	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
growth	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
es	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
uploads	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2019	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
05	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
Captura	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
14	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Illustration	O	O	O	O	O	O
3	O	O	O	O	O	O
The	O	O	O	O	O	O
Global	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
Gaming	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
Market	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

Within	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
constant	O	O	O	O	O	O
growth	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
sector	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
subsector	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaming	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
mobile	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
sector	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
grows	O	O	O	O	O	O
especially	O	O	O	O	O	O
faster	O	O	O	O	O	O
compared	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gaming	O	O	O	O	O	O
PC	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
videogames	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
console	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
following	O	O	O	O	O	O
graph	O	O	O	O	O	O
shows	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
generation	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
benefits	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
global	O	O	O	O	O	O
regions	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
es	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
uploads	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2019	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
05	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
Captura	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
15	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Illustration	O	O	O	O	O	O
4	O	O	O	O	O	O
Distribution	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaming	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
market	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
countries	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Asia-Pacific	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
region	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
generated	O	O	O	O	O	O
up	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
$71.4	O	O	O	O	O	O
billion	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
than	O	O	O	O	O	O
half	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
generated	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
$37	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bn	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
surpassing	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
annual	O	O	O	O	O	O
profits	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
US	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
within	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
gaming	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
”	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
sector	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
5	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
Southeast	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Asia	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
controls	O	O	O	O	O	O
64%	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
sales	O	O	O	O	O	O
related	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
Gaming	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
”	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
sector	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Its	O	O	O	O	O	O
main	O	O	O	O	O	O
regional	O	O	O	O	O	O
competitor	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
Japan	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
South	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Korea	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Supposedly	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
government	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
intention	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
maintaining	O	O	O	O	O	O
growth	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
control	O	O	O	O	O	O
within	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
international	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
gaming	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
”	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
market	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
attributed	O	O	O	O	O	O
links	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
activity	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
Winnti	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
Group	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
one	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
main	O	O	O	O	O	O
objectives	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
collect	O	O	O	O	O	O
classified	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
Game	O	O	O	O	O	O
Designers	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaming	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
sector	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
6	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
ESET	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
company	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
published	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
investigation	O	O	O	O	O	O
about	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
Winnti	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
Group	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
where	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
company	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
Thai	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
developer	O	O	O	O	O	O
Electronics	O	O	O	O	O	O
Extreme	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyber-attacked	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
could	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
distributed	O	O	O	O	O	O
infected	O	O	O	O	O	O
versions	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
product	O	O	O	O	O	O
called	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
Infestation	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gameplay	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

As	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
following	O	O	O	O	O	O
graph	O	O	O	O	O	O
shows	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
highest	O	O	O	O	O	O
percentage	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
infected	O	O	O	O	O	O
products	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
distributed	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Thailand	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
percentages	O	O	O	O	O	O
published	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
ESET	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
follows	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
es	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
uploads	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2019	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
05	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
Captura	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
16	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Illustration	O	O	O	O	O	O
4	O	O	O	O	O	O
Countries	O	O	O	O	O	O
most	O	O	O	O	O	O
infected	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Winnti	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
Group	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
graph	O	O	O	O	O	O
above	O	O	O	O	O	O
shows	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
high	O	O	O	O	O	O
percentage	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyber-attacks	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Winnti	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
Group	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
against	O	O	O	O	O	O
companies	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaming	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
sector	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Thailand	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

One	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
most	O	O	O	O	O	O
unique	O	O	O	O	O	O
characteristics	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaming	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
sector	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
within	O	O	O	O	O	O
Thailand	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
companies	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
global	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
large	O	O	O	O	O	O
multinationals	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
vast	O	O	O	O	O	O
majority	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
companies	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Thailand	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
’	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
s	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
gaming	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
sector	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
SMEs	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
Thai	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
capital	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

However	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
these	O	O	O	O	O	O
same	O	O	O	O	O	O
companies	O	O	O	O	O	O
usually	O	O	O	O	O	O
work	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
international	O	O	O	O	O	O
organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
Nintendo	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
Xbox	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
among	O	O	O	O	O	O
others	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Another	O	O	O	O	O	O
feature	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
high	O	O	O	O	O	O
value	O	O	O	O	O	O
within	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaming	O	O	O	O	O	O
market	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Thailand	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
companies	O	O	O	O	O	O
focused	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
behavioral	O	O	O	O	O	O
study	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
videogame	O	O	O	O	O	O
consumers	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
Asiasoft	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
Thai	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
gaming	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
industry	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
may	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
high	O	O	O	O	O	O
interest	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
state	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
terms	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyber	O	O	O	O	O	O
espionage	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
since	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
collaboration	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
large	O	O	O	O	O	O
international	O	O	O	O	O	O
companies	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
research	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaming	O	O	O	O	O	O
consumers	O	O	O	O	O	O
could	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
high	O	O	O	O	O	O
value	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
international	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
gamer	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
industry	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
7	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Conclusions	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O

As	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
could	O	O	O	O	O	O
realize	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
research	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
almost	O	O	O	O	O	O
all	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
sectors	O	O	O	O	O	O
would	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
relevant	O	O	O	O	O	O
target	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Currently	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
globalized	O	O	O	O	O	O
market	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
able	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
interconnect	O	O	O	O	O	O
all	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
companies	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
specific	O	O	O	O	O	O
field	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
fact	O	O	O	O	O	O
means	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
day	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
day	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
targets	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
groups	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
extended	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
specialized	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Apparently	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaming	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
sector	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
would	O	O	O	O	O	O
look	O	O	O	O	O	O
like	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
non-significant	O	O	O	O	O	O
sector	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
worldwide	O	O	O	O	O	O
economy	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

However	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
could	O	O	O	O	O	O
analyze	O	O	O	O	O	O
there	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
specialized	O	O	O	O	O	O
within	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

We	O	O	O	O	O	O
conclude	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
all	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
sectors	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
relevant	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
current	O	O	O	O	O	O
globalized	O	O	O	O	O	O
economy	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
consequently	O	O	O	O	O	O
would	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
potential	O	O	O	O	O	O
target	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
some	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Another	O	O	O	O	O	O
relevant	O	O	O	O	O	O
conclusion	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
research	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
strategy	O	O	O	O	O	O
applied	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
Winnti	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
Group	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
compromise	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
much	O	O	O	O	O	O
organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
aimed	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
important	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaming	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
supply	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
chain	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
organization	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
reach	O	O	O	O	O	O
high	O	O	O	O	O	O
rates	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
victims	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
organization	O	O	O	O	O	O
distributed	O	O	O	O	O	O
massively	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
infected	O	O	O	O	O	O
product	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Wherefore	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
national	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
international	O	O	O	O	O	O
suppliers	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
important	O	O	O	O	O	O
target	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
many	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Indicators	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Compromise	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Samples	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
compromised	O	O	O	O	O	O
files	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
SHA	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
Compile	O	O	O	O	O	O
Time	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
UTC	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
RC4	O	O	O	O	O	O
Key	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
PayloadSH1	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
7cf41b1acfb05064518a2ad9e4c16fde9185cd4b	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tue	O	O	O	O	O	O
Nov	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
13	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
10	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
12	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
58	O	O	O	O	O	O
2018	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
1729131071	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
8272c1f4	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
7f73def251fcc34cbd6f5ac61822913479124a2a	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
Wed	O	O	O	O	O	O
Nov	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
14	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
03	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
50	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
18	O	O	O	O	O	O
2018	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
19317120	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
44260a1d	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
dac0bd8972f23c9b5f7f8f06c5d629eac7926269	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tue	O	O	O	O	O	O
Nov	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
27	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
03	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
05	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
16	O	O	O	O	O	O
2018	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
1729131071	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
8272c1f4	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

Payload	O	O	O	O	O	O
samples	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
SHA	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
C	O	O	O	B-TACTIC	O	B-TACTIC
&	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
C	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
Server	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
URL	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
a045939f53c5ad2c0f7368b082aa7b0bd7b116da	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
bugcheck.xigncodeservice	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
Common	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lib	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
Common	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
bsod.php	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
a260dcf193e747cee49ae83568eea6c04bf93cb3	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
bugcheck.xigncodeservice	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
Common	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lib	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
Common	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
Include.php	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
dde82093decde6371eb852a5e9a1aa4acf3b56ba	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
bugcheck.xigncodeservice	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
Common	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lib	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
common.php	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
8272c1f41f7c223316c0d78bd3bd5744e25c2e9f	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
nw.infestexe	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
version	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
last.ph	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
44260a1dfd92922a621124640015160e621f32d5	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
dump.gxxservice	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
common	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
up	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
up	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
base.php	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

Dropper	O	O	O	O	O	O
download	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
api.goallbandungtravel	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
com	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
ID	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Description	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
T1195	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Supply	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Chain	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Compromise	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
T1050	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
New	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Service	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
T1022	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
|	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
Data	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
Encrypted	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
T1079	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
|	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
Multilayer	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
Encryption	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
T1032	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
|	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
Standard	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
Cryptographic	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
Protocol	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
(	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
RC4	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
,	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
RC5	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
)	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
T1043	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Commonly	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Used	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Port	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
(	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
80,443	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
)	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
T1009	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Binary	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Padding	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mitre	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
ATT	O	O	O	O	O	O
&	O	O	O	O	O	O
TTP	O	O	O	O	O	O
Matrix	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
following	O	O	O	O	O	O
table	O	O	O	O	O	O
you	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
check	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
TTPs	O	O	O	O	O	O
associated	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
following	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
ATT	O	O	O	O	O	O
&	O	O	O	O	O	O
CK	O	O	O	O	O	O
Framework	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
MITRE	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Domain	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
ID	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Name	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Description	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
Enterprise	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
T1195	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Supply	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Chain	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Compromise	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Winnti	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Has	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Compromised	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
software	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
provider	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
companies	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
Enterprise	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
T1085	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Rubdll32	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Winnti	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
modifies	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Windows	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Dll	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
files	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
to	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
persistance	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
Enterprise	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
T1050	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
New	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Service	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Winnti	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
creates	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
a	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
new	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
service	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
that	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
runs	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
in	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
background	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
Enterprise	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
T1060	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Registry	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Run	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Keys	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
/	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Start	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
folder	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Winnti	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
modify	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Windows	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Registry	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
to	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
check	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
if	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
should	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
stop	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
Enterprise	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
T1102	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Web	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Service	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Winnti	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
contact	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
C	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
&	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
C	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
Enterprise	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
T1140	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Deobfuscate	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
/	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Decode	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Files	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
or	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Information	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Winnti	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
send	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
information	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
ofuscated	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
Enterprise	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
T1012	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Query	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Registry	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Winnti	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
modifies	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Windows	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
dll	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
files	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
to	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
persistence	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
Enterprise	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
T1024	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Custom	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Cryptographic	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Winnti	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
communicates	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
the	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
C	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
&	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
C	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
with	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
base64	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
-	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
encoded	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
data	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
Enterprise	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
TT1001	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Data	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Obfuscation	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Winnti	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
uses	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Cryptographic	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Protocol	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
(	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
RC4	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
,	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
RC5	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
)	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
Enterprise	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
T1219	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Remote	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Access	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Tools	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
Winnti	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
installs	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
backdoor	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
that	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
communicates	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
with	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
C	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
&	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
C	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
to	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
download	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
executable	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
code	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
References	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
Léveillé	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
M	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
E	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
2019	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
11	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
March	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Gaming	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
industry	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
still	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
scope	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
attackers	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Asia	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.welivesecurity.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2019	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
03	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
11	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaming-industry-scope-attackers-asia	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
Barnabás	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
C	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
S	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
A	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
B	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
A	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
2017	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

CHINA	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
’	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
S	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
RISE	O	O	O	O	O	O
AND	O	O	O	O	O	O
THE	O	O	O	O	O	O
GEOPOLITICS	O	O	O	O	O	O
OF	O	O	O	O	O	O
SOUTHEAST	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
ASIA	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
Distant	O	O	O	O	O	O
Magazine	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
3	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
BBVA	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
2014	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
BBVA	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Research	O	O	O	O	O	O
Geo	O	O	O	O	O	O
World	O	O	O	O	O	O
Report	O	O	O	O	O	O
A	O	O	O	O	O	O
Visual	O	O	O	O	O	O
Guide	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
Geopolitical	O	O	O	O	O	O
Affairs	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.bbvaresearch.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
uploads	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2014	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
12	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
Geo-World-Report	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
2H	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
2014	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
pdf	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
4	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
Newzoo	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
2018	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Mobile	O	O	O	O	O	O
Revenues	O	O	O	O	O	O
Account	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
More	O	O	O	O	O	O
Than	O	O	O	O	O	O
50%	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Global	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
Games	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
Market	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
It	O	O	O	O	O	O
Reaches	O	O	O	O	O	O
$137.9	O	O	O	O	O	O
Billion	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
2018	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
newzoo.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
insights	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
articles	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
global-games-market-reaches	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
137	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
9	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
billion-in	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
2018	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
mobile-games-take-half	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
5	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
Global	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
Game	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
Services	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
2017	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
1	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
January	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Asia	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
Game	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
Markets	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
LAI	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
Global	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
Game	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
Services	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
.	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR

Retrieved	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.lai.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
asia-game-markets	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
6	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kaspersky	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Lab	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Global	O	O	O	O	O	O
Research	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Analysis	O	O	O	O	O	O
Team	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
2013	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Winnti	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
Retrieved	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
media.kasperskycontenthub.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
uploads	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
sites	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
43	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2018	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
03	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
20134508	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
winnti-more-than-just-a-game	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
130410	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
pdf	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
7	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
Fung	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
A	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
2016	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Global	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
Game	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
Industries	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cultural	O	O	O	O	O	O
Policy	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
3rd	O	O	O	O	O	O
edit	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hong	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Kong	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

