<DOCSTART>	O	O	O	O	O	O

New	O	O	O	O	O	O
PatchWork	O	O	O	O	O	O
Spearphishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
Attack	O	O	O	O	O	O

October	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
22	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2019	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE

Recently	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
somewhat	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
elaborated	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
caught	O	O	O	O	O	O
our	O	O	O	O	O	O
attention	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
consists	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
malicious	O	O	O	O	O	O
office	O	O	O	O	O	O
document	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
real	O	O	O	O	O	O
article	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
Samaa.tv	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
published	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
07	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
-	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
10	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
-	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2019	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
one	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
most	O	O	O	O	O	O
important	O	O	O	O	O	O
media	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pakistan	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
article	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
related	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
current	O	O	O	O	O	O
rise	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
tension	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
geopolitical	O	O	O	O	O	O
Indian-Pakistani	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
conflict	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kashmir	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
headline	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
article	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
India	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
become	O	O	O	O	O	O
center	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
extremism	O	O	O	O	O	O
under	O	O	O	O	O	O
Modi	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
AJK	O	O	O	O	O	O
PM	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
io	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
uploads	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2019	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
10	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
image1	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

Illustration	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
Headlines	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
document	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
name	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
India	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
Extremisms	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
Under	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mobi.docx	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
hash	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
167062593cb9e42a404dc9c8a0347e74888712a1256731724417e6f1d411cbbb	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
written	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
English	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
official	O	O	O	O	O	O
language	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
both	O	O	O	O	O	O
countries	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
startling	O	O	O	O	O	O
headline	O	O	O	O	O	O
selected	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
tries	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
attract	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
attention	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
interest	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pakistani	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Indian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
people	O	O	O	O	O	O
through	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
social	O	O	O	O	O	O
fear	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

So	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
main	O	O	O	O	O	O
target	O	O	O	O	O	O
would	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
focused	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pakistani	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
victims	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
download	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
malicious	O	O	O	O	O	O
document	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

At	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
moment	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Delhi	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Islamabad	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
claim	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
control	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
whole	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kashmir	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
area	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

However	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
each	O	O	O	O	O	O
public	O	O	O	O	O	O
administration	O	O	O	O	O	O
manage	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
concrete	O	O	O	O	O	O
area	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
region	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
3	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
io	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
uploads	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2019	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
10	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
image2	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
666x1024	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

Illustration	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
External	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kashmir	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
’	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
s	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
influence	O	O	O	O	O	O

China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
involved	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
geopolitical	O	O	O	O	O	O
scenario	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
carrying	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
important	O	O	O	O	O	O
investment	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pakistan	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
especially	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
China-Pakistan	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Economic	O	O	O	O	O	O
Corridor	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

A	O	O	O	O	O	O
public	O	O	O	O	O	O
officer	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
Beijing	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
declared	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
if	O	O	O	O	O	O
there	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
any	O	O	O	O	O	O
unacceptable	O	O	O	O	O	O
geostrategic	O	O	O	O	O	O
movement	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
India	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
would	O	O	O	O	O	O
defend	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
legal	O	O	O	O	O	O
right	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pakistan	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kashmir	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
’	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
s	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
area	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
3	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
io	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
uploads	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2019	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
10	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
image3	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

Illustration	O	O	O	O	O	O
3	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Pakistan	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Economic	O	O	O	O	O	O
corridor	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
economic	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
trade	O	O	O	O	O	O
geopolitical	O	O	O	O	O	O
interests	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pakistan	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
highly	O	O	O	O	O	O
relevant	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Currently	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
relevant	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
investments	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pakistan	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
keep	O	O	O	O	O	O
developing	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
&	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pakistan	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
economic	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
join	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
OBOR	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
route	O	O	O	O	O	O
until	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gwadar	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Karachi	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Port	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
4	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
Indian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
claim	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
control	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
whole	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kashmir	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
area	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
means	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
important	O	O	O	O	O	O
approach	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
India	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Economic	O	O	O	O	O	O
Corridor	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
China-Pakistan	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
geopolitical	O	O	O	O	O	O
situation	O	O	O	O	O	O
provokes	O	O	O	O	O	O
discomfort	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
both	O	O	O	O	O	O
partners	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
logistical	O	O	O	O	O	O
project	O	O	O	O	O	O
would	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
danger	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
disrupted	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

As	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
showed	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pakistan	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
India	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
showing	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
interests	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kashmir	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
area	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
document	O	O	O	O	O	O
appeared	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
public	O	O	O	O	O	O
sources	O	O	O	O	O	O
around	O	O	O	O	O	O
15	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
-	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
10	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
-	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2019	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
internal	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
document	O	O	O	O	O	O
dates	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
12	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
-	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
10	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
-	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2019	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
so	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
seems	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
recent	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

When	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
document	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
opened	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
MSOffice	O	O	O	O	O	O
Word	O	O	O	O	O	O
editor	O	O	O	O	O	O
process	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
constantly	O	O	O	O	O	O
suspended	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
acts	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
unstable	O	O	O	O	O	O
way	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Analyzing	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
depth	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
document	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
contains	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
file	O	O	O	O	O	O
called	O	O	O	O	O	O
image1	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
eps	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
corresponds	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
Flash	O	O	O	O	O	O
element	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
document	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
exploits	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
adobe	O	O	O	O	O	O
Flash	O	O	O	O	O	O
vulnerability	O	O	O	O	O	O
known	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
CVE	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
2017	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
0261	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
io	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
uploads	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2019	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
10	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
image4	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

Illustration	O	O	O	O	O	O
4	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dropped	O	O	O	O	O	O
files	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
document	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
exploit	O	O	O	O	O	O
executed	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
document	O	O	O	O	O	O
contains	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
shellcode	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
dumps	O	O	O	O	O	O
into	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
folder	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
C	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
ProgramData	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
Microsoft	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
DeviceSync	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
3	O	O	O	O	O	O
executable	O	O	O	O	O	O
files	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
two	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
them	O	O	O	O	O	O
related	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
VMWare	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
one	O	O	O	O	O	O
named	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
MSBuild.exe	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

After	O	O	O	O	O	O
creating	O	O	O	O	O	O
these	O	O	O	O	O	O
files	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
shellcode	O	O	O	O	O	O
runs	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
binary	O	O	O	O	O	O
named	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
VMWareCplLauncher.exe	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

As	O	O	O	O	O	O
described	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
Unit42	O	O	O	O	O	O
report	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
6	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
executable	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
VMWareCplLauncher.exe	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
signed	O	O	O	O	O	O
binary	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
VMWare	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
DLL	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
legitimate	O	O	O	O	O	O
part	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
VMWare	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
automatically	O	O	O	O	O	O
loaded	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
executable	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
modified	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
create	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
case	O	O	O	O	O	O
two	O	O	O	O	O	O
scheduled	O	O	O	O	O	O
tasks	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
io	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
uploads	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2019	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
10	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
image5	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

Illustration	O	O	O	O	O	O
5	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tasks	O	O	O	O	O	O
created	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
VMWareCplLauncher.exe	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
io	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
uploads	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2019	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
10	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
image6	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

Illustration	O	O	O	O	O	O
6	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
Second	O	O	O	O	O	O
binary	O	O	O	O	O	O
path	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
first	O	O	O	O	O	O
task	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
points	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
yet	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
executable	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
MSBuild.exe	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
second	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
binary	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
isn	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
t	O	O	O	O	O	O
generated	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
any	O	O	O	O	O	O
time	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
infection	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
could	O	O	O	O	O	O
point	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
next	O	O	O	O	O	O
stage	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
infection	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
may	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
downloaded	O	O	O	O	O	O
after	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
recon	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
infected	O	O	O	O	O	O
machine	O	O	O	O	O	O
made	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
fist	O	O	O	O	O	O
stage	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

After	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
minute	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
task	O	O	O	O	O	O
programmed	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
name	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
Windows	O	O	O	O	O	O
Update	O	O	O	O	O	O
…	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
launches	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
MSBuild.exe	O	O	O	O	O	O
binary	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
consists	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
first	O	O	O	O	O	O
stage	O	O	O	O	O	O
trojan	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
multitude	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
capabilities	O	O	O	O	O	O
described	O	O	O	O	O	O
below	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
sample	O	O	O	O	O	O
contacts	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
domain	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
yetwq.twilightparadox.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
through	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
HTTP	O	O	O	O	O	O
protocol	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
constantly	O	O	O	O	O	O
sends	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
collected	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
victim	O	O	O	O	O	O
computer	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
together	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
parameter	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
crc	O	O	O	O	O	O
=	O	O	O	O	O	O
e3a6	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
hardcoded	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
logic	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
io	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
uploads	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2019	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
10	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
image7	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
1024x270	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

Illustration	O	O	O	O	O	O
7	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
Malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
traffic	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
C2	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
response	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
server	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
checked	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
logic	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
search	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
one	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
following	O	O	O	O	O	O
numbers	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
4	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
5	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
8	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
13	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
23	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
33	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
correspond	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
different	O	O	O	O	O	O
commands	O	O	O	O	O	O
related	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
download	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
execution	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
other	O	O	O	O	O	O
binaries	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
keyboard	O	O	O	O	O	O
monitoring	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
sending	O	O	O	O	O	O
screenshots	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
command	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
control	O	O	O	O	O	O
server	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
theft	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
files	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
following	O	O	O	O	O	O
list	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
extensions	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
doc	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
docx	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
pdf	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
ppt	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
pptx	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
jpg	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
jpeg	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
rtf	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
txt	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
7z	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
rar	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
zip	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
docm	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
msg	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
wps	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
xps	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
pptm	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
io	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
uploads	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2019	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
10	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
image8	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

Illustration	O	O	O	O	O	O
8	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
Command	O	O	O	O	O	O
switch	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
case	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
sample	O	O	O	O	O	O

Both	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
capabilities	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
code	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
practically	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
same	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
those	O	O	O	O	O	O
described	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
Unit42	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
reference	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
BadNews	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
sameway	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
TTPs	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
entire	O	O	O	O	O	O
infection	O	O	O	O	O	O
chain	O	O	O	O	O	O
coincide	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
those	O	O	O	O	O	O
described	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
several	O	O	O	O	O	O
reports	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
relation	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaigns	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
attributed	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Patchwork	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
known	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dropping	O	O	O	O	O	O
Elephant	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT-C	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
09	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Furthermore	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
due	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
characteristics	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
current	O	O	O	O	O	O
geopolitical	O	O	O	O	O	O
scenario	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
area	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
seems	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
main	O	O	O	O	O	O
targets	O	O	O	O	O	O
could	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
located	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pakistan	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
would	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
linked	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese-Pakistani	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Economic	O	O	O	O	O	O
Corridor	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
CPEC	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
route	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

IOCs	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
167062593cb9e42a404dc9c8a0347e74888712a1256731724417e6f1d411cbbb	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
6b656dc98773255cbc3592122db6487326e39b8e01966cca174dde87e72f82ec	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
5f5a1af57872610aa692ee3d0fba4a0171c2ec1a8cc3cf45f21f52caa2ab9041	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
31c913899d50d78f2d7d9657e7534bd36819ec9571566216f1c963bf605417f7	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
yetwq.twilightparadox.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
185.161.208.252	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

References	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.samaa.tv	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
news	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2019	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
10	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
india-to-become-center-of-extremism-under-modi-ajk-pm	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.bbc.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
news	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
world-asia-india	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
49737886	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
3	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.dw.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
pakistan-thanks-china-for-support-on-kashmir-issue	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
50745277	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
4	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.dw.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
belt-and-road-forum-is-the-china-pakistan-economic-corridor-failing	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
48473486	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
5	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
attack.mitre.org	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
groups	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
G0040	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
6	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
unit42	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
paloaltonetworks.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
unit42	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
patchwork-continues-deliver-badnews-indian-subcontinent	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

