<DOCSTART>	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
energy	O	O	O	O	O	O
reserves	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Eastern	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Mediterranean	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
Sea	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
malicious	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT10	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
against	O	O	O	O	O	O
Turkey	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC

May	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
14	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE

Energy	O	O	O	O	O	O
reserves	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Eastern	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Mediterranean	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
Sea	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
MEDEAST	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
gas	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
pipeline	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mediterranean	O	O	O	O	O	O
Sea	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
become	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
increasingly	O	O	O	O	O	O
relevant	O	O	O	O	O	O
geostrategic	O	O	O	O	O	O
topic	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ministries	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
of	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Foreign	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Affairs	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Turkey	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Greece	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cyprus	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Israel	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
even	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
due	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
controversies	O	O	O	O	O	O
generated	O	O	O	O	O	O
during	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
last	O	O	O	O	O	O
decade	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
discoveries	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
natural	O	O	O	O	O	O
gas	O	O	O	O	O	O
resources	O	O	O	O	O	O
located	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Eastern	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Mediterranean	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
seas	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
States	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
Israel	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cyprus	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Egypt	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
presence	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Turkish	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
troops	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Libya	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Syria	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Franco-Greek	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
alliance	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
avoid	O	O	O	O	O	O
Turkish	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
intrusions	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
maritime	O	O	O	O	O	O
territory	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Greece	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
show	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
relevance	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
global	O	O	O	O	O	O
interest	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
energy	O	O	O	O	O	O
resources	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
area	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

As	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
could	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
following	O	O	O	O	O	O
map	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
part	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
geostrategic	O	O	O	O	O	O
conflict	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
focused	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Turkish	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
EEZ	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Turkey	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
carried	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
agreement	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
Libya	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
tries	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
carry	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
expansion	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
exclusive	O	O	O	O	O	O
maritime	O	O	O	O	O	O
economic	O	O	O	O	O	O
zones	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
relevant	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
clarify	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
EEZ	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
maritime	O	O	O	O	O	O
zone	O	O	O	O	O	O
prescribed	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
United	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Nations	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Convention	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
law	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
sea	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
state	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
special	O	O	O	O	O	O
rights	O	O	O	O	O	O
regarding	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
exploration	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
exploitation	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
sea	O	O	O	O	O	O
resources	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
including	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
production	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
energy	O	O	O	O	O	O
through	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
water	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
wind	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
3	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
17	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
io	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
uploads	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2020	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
05	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
IL	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
1024x678	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Illustration	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
Expansion	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Turkish	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
EEZ	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
expansion	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Turkish	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
government	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
tries	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
carry	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O
could	O	O	O	O	O	O
increase	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
geopolitical	O	O	O	O	O	O
risk	O	O	O	O	O	O
among	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cypriots	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Greeks	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
even	O	O	O	O	O	O
Israeli	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
governments	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
military	O	O	O	O	O	O
presence	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
area	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
those	O	O	O	O	O	O
States	O	O	O	O	O	O
could	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
map	O	O	O	O	O	O
shown	O	O	O	O	O	O
above	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
strategy	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
increasing	O	O	O	O	O	O
Turkey	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
EEZ	O	O	O	O	O	O
would	O	O	O	O	O	O
leave	O	O	O	O	O	O
without	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
important	O	O	O	O	O	O
part	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
continental	O	O	O	O	O	O
shelf	O	O	O	O	O	O
Athens	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
4	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
addition	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cyprus	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
significantly	O	O	O	O	O	O
affected	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
EEZ	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
expansion	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
there	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
occupation	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cyprus	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
EEZ	O	O	O	O	O	O
area	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Furthermore	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
President	O	O	O	O	O	O
Erdogan	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
publicly	O	O	O	O	O	O
declared	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
his	O	O	O	O	O	O
oil	O	O	O	O	O	O
exploration	O	O	O	O	O	O
projects	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
coast	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cyprus	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
cease	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Turkey	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
tries	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
stablish	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
zone	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
EEZ	O	O	O	O	O	O
controlled	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Turkish	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
influence	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
would	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
represented	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
following	O	O	O	O	O	O
map	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
5	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
io	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
uploads	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2020	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
05	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
IL	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Illustration	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
Expansion	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Turkish	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
EEZ	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
location	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
energy	O	O	O	O	O	O
resources	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
previous	O	O	O	O	O	O
map	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
you	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
see	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
energy	O	O	O	O	O	O
exploration	O	O	O	O	O	O
areas	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
located	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Israel	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cyprus	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Egypt	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Moreover	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
these	O	O	O	O	O	O
States	O	O	O	O	O	O
give	O	O	O	O	O	O
diplomatic	O	O	O	O	O	O
support	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cyprus	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Greece	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
regarding	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
expansion	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
conflict	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Turkish	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
EEZ	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Furthermore	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
27th	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
of	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
February	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
of	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Greece	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cyprus	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Israel	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
signed	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
agreement	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
build	O	O	O	O	O	O
up	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
gas	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
pipeline	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
transport	O	O	O	O	O	O
gas	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
Europe	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Leviathan	O	O	O	O	O	O
gas	O	O	O	O	O	O
reserves	O	O	O	O	O	O
located	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Israel	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Moreover	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
near	O	O	O	O	O	O
future	O	O	O	O	O	O
there	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
intention	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
joining	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
pipeline	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
extractions	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cypriot	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
gas	O	O	O	O	O	O
reserves	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Aphrodite	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Calypso	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
6	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
io	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
uploads	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2020	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
05	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
IL	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
3	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Illustration	O	O	O	O	O	O
3	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mediterranean	O	O	O	O	O	O
Gas	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
Pipeline	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

Turkey	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
displaced	O	O	O	O	O	O
several	O	O	O	O	O	O
warships	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
coast	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cyprus	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
order	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
carry	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O
gas	O	O	O	O	O	O
exploration	O	O	O	O	O	O
projects	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
Eastern	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
European	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
gas	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
pipeline	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
reduces	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
geopolitical	O	O	O	O	O	O
power	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Turkey	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
tries	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
exclude	O	O	O	O	O	O
Turkey	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
any	O	O	O	O	O	O
participation	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
pipeline	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
called	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
EastMed	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
6	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

However	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
during	O	O	O	O	O	O
March	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Turkey	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
put	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
offshore	O	O	O	O	O	O
drilling	O	O	O	O	O	O
vessel	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
order	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
continue	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
oil	O	O	O	O	O	O
exploration	O	O	O	O	O	O
projects	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
EEZ	O	O	O	O	O	O
waters	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Greece	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cyprus	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
EU	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
order	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
try	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
acquire	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
future	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
role	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
gas	O	O	O	O	O	O
supplier	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
EU	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
8	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Interests	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
influence	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mediterranean	O	O	O	O	O	O
area	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
unlike	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
US	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
diplomatic-military	O	O	O	O	O	O
expansionism	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
focused	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
expansionist	O	O	O	O	O	O
strategy	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
diplomatic-commercial	O	O	O	O	O	O
strategy	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

For	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
one	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
geo-strategically	O	O	O	O	O	O
key	O	O	O	O	O	O
regions	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Port	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Piraeus	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Greece	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
Greek	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
government	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
tendered	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
next	O	O	O	O	O	O
35	O	O	O	O	O	O
years	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
67%	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Port	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
operations	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
COSCO	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Ocean	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Shipping	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
368.5	O	O	O	O	O	O
million	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
350	O	O	O	O	O	O
million	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
euros	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
invested	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Piraeus	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
port	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
infrastructure	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
9	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
Port	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Piraeus	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
represents	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
potential	O	O	O	O	O	O
gate	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
all	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
commercial	O	O	O	O	O	O
flow	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
comes	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
OBOR	O	O	O	O	O	O
sea	O	O	O	O	O	O
route	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
addition	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
during	O	O	O	O	O	O
November	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
of	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2019	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Greece	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
signed	O	O	O	O	O	O
up	O	O	O	O	O	O
16	O	O	O	O	O	O
cooperation	O	O	O	O	O	O
agreements	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
different	O	O	O	O	O	O
matters	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
including	O	O	O	O	O	O
trade	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
energy	O	O	O	O	O	O
investments	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
10	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

On	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
other	O	O	O	O	O	O
hand	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cyprus	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
signed	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
agreement	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
consortium	O	O	O	O	O	O
led	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
build	O	O	O	O	O	O
up	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
first	O	O	O	O	O	O
natural	O	O	O	O	O	O
gas	O	O	O	O	O	O
import	O	O	O	O	O	O
terminal	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cyprus	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
terminal	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
designed	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
convert	O	O	O	O	O	O
imported	O	O	O	O	O	O
liquefied	O	O	O	O	O	O
gas	O	O	O	O	O	O
into	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
gaseous	O	O	O	O	O	O
form	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
energy	O	O	O	O	O	O
plants	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
11	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
construction	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
being	O	O	O	O	O	O
developed	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Petroleum	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Pipeline	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Engineering	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Metron	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hudong-Zhngua	O	O	O	O	O	O
Shipbuilding	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Wilhelmsen	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Ship	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Management	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Construction	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
expected	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
done	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
2022	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Regarding	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
international	O	O	O	O	O	O
security	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
investigates	O	O	O	O	O	O
Turkey	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
relation	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Uighur	O	O	O	O	O	O
community	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
Uyghurs	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
Turkish-speaking	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
people	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
interior	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Asia	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
mostly	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
them	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
Muslim	O	O	O	O	O	O
religious	O	O	O	O	O	O
confession	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
Uyghurs	O	O	O	O	O	O
live	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
northwestern	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
China	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Uyghur	O	O	O	O	O	O
autonomous	O	O	O	O	O	O
region	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Xinjiang	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
considered	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
People	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
’	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
s	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
Republic	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
of	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
China	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
considered	O	O	O	O	O	O
largely	O	O	O	O	O	O
jihadist	O	O	O	O	O	O
terrorists	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
12	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Turkey	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
country	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
given	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
most	O	O	O	O	O	O
international	O	O	O	O	O	O
support	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Uyghur	O	O	O	O	O	O
community	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Currently	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
up	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
45,000	O	O	O	O	O	O
Uyghur	O	O	O	O	O	O
refugees	O	O	O	O	O	O
live	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Turkey	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
temporary	O	O	O	O	O	O
visa	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
even	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
permanent	O	O	O	O	O	O
residence	O	O	O	O	O	O
permit	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
13	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Turkey	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
foreign	O	O	O	O	O	O
affairs	O	O	O	O	O	O
policies	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
misaligned	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
those	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
possible	O	O	O	O	O	O
obstruction	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
OBOR	O	O	O	O	O	O
route	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Port	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Piraeus	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
collaborative	O	O	O	O	O	O
policies	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Uyghur	O	O	O	O	O	O
community	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Xinjiang	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
region	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
could	O	O	O	O	O	O
damage	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
diplomatic	O	O	O	O	O	O
relations	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Due	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
diplomatic	O	O	O	O	O	O
confrontations	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
conflicting	O	O	O	O	O	O
interests	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
two	O	O	O	O	O	O
countries	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
could	O	O	O	O	O	O
carry	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyber	O	O	O	O	O	O
espionage	O	O	O	O	O	O
operations	O	O	O	O	O	O
against	O	O	O	O	O	O
Turkish	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
institutions	O	O	O	O	O	O
linked	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
diplomacy	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
defense	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
energy	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
telecommunications	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
foreign	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
trade	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Its	O	O	O	O	O	O
main	O	O	O	O	O	O
objective	O	O	O	O	O	O
could	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
collect	O	O	O	O	O	O
confidential	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
order	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
gain	O	O	O	O	O	O
advantages	O	O	O	O	O	O
within	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
future	O	O	O	O	O	O
geostrategic	O	O	O	O	O	O
movements	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Turkey	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
rest	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
involved	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
conflicts	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
energy	O	O	O	O	O	O
resources	O	O	O	O	O	O
located	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mediterranean	O	O	O	O	O	O
Sea	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Malicious	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
against	O	O	O	O	O	O
Turkish	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

A	O	O	O	O	O	O
malicious	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
allegedly	O	O	O	O	O	O
attributed	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT10	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
against	O	O	O	O	O	O
Turkish	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
various	O	O	O	O	O	O
sectors	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
telecommunications	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
finance	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
identified	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
Adeo	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
January	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
of	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
14	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

APT10	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
presumably	O	O	O	O	O	O
attributed	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ministry	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
of	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
State	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Security	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
China	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
15	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
addition	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
usually	O	O	O	O	O	O
targets	O	O	O	O	O	O
organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
various	O	O	O	O	O	O
sectors	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
defense	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
energy	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
health	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
telecommunications	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
governments	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
military	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
shipping	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
IT	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
16	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
identified	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT10	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
usually	O	O	O	O	O	O
carries	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O
malicious	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaigns	O	O	O	O	O	O
against	O	O	O	O	O	O
organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
could	O	O	O	O	O	O
damage	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
State	O	O	O	O	O	O
interests	O	O	O	O	O	O
into	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
global	O	O	O	O	O	O
market	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

On	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
other	O	O	O	O	O	O
hand	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
detected	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT10	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
usually	O	O	O	O	O	O
carries	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O
malicious	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaigns	O	O	O	O	O	O
against	O	O	O	O	O	O
organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
support	O	O	O	O	O	O
foundations	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
carry	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O
aid	O	O	O	O	O	O
projects	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
ethnic	O	O	O	O	O	O
groups	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
may	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
potential	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
against	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
national	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
security	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
case	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Uyghur	O	O	O	O	O	O
community	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Moreover	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
identified	O	O	O	O	O	O
several	O	O	O	O	O	O
similarities	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
TTP	O	O	O	O	O	O
published	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
other	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT10	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
reports	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
2019	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
14	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
case	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
identified	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
began	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
2016	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
initial	O	O	O	B-TACTIC	O	B-TACTIC
access	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
carried	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
exploitation	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
of	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
a	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
public	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
web	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
application	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
.	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE

Summary	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
executed	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kill	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chain	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
14	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

•	O	O	O	O	O	O
Initial	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
attackers	O	O	O	O	O	O
deployed	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
following	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Chopper4	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
JspSpy5	O	O	O	O	O	O
webshells	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
obtain	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
foothold	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
victim	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
network	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
execute	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
commands	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
to	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
upload	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
files	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
to	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
the	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
target	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
machines	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
.	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE

•	O	O	O	O	O	O
Reconnaissance	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
execution	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
theft	O	O	O	B-TACTIC	O	B-TACTIC
of	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
credentials	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
reconnaissance	O	O	O	O	O	O
phase	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
series	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
commands	O	O	O	O	O	O
were	O	O	O	O	O	O
launched	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
collect	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	B-TECHNIQUE	B-TECHNIQUE
information	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	I-TECHNIQUE	I-TECHNIQUE
from	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	I-TECHNIQUE	I-TECHNIQUE
users	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	I-TECHNIQUE	I-TECHNIQUE
,	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	I-TECHNIQUE	I-TECHNIQUE
domains	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	I-TECHNIQUE	I-TECHNIQUE
and	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
shared	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
folders	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
hostile	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
legitimate	O	O	O	O	O	O
tools	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Windows	O	O	O	O	O	O
operating	O	O	O	O	O	O
systems	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
reconnaissance	O	O	O	O	O	O
stage	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
ipconfig.exe	O	O	O	B-TOOL	O	B-TOOL
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
whoami.exe	O	O	O	B-TOOL	O	B-TOOL
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
net.exe	O	O	O	B-TOOL	O	B-TOOL
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
ping.exe	O	O	O	B-TOOL	O	B-TOOL
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
powershell.exe	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
BloodHound	O	O	O	B-TOOL	O	B-TOOL
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
bloodHound	O	O	O	B-TOOL	O	B-TOOL
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
legitimate	O	O	O	O	O	O
binary	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
Microsoft	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
attacker	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
advanced	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
tool	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
called	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
“	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
dns.exe	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
”	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
to	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
list	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
all	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
the	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
machines	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
that	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
were	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
registered	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
in	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
a	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
particular	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
domain	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Regarding	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
execution	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
hostile	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
implemented	O	O	O	O	B-TACTIC	O
“	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
hTran	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
”	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
backdoor	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
able	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
exfiltrate	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
information	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
.	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
previous	O	O	O	O	O	O
malicious	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT10	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
campaigns	O	O	O	O	O	O
against	O	O	O	O	O	O
Turkey	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
executable	O	O	O	O	O	O
file	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
name	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
java.exe	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
compromised	O	O	O	O	O	O
hosts	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Hostile	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
loaded	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
a	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
malicious	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
DLL	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
into	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
the	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
memory	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
of	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
a	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
legitimate	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
binary	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
final	O	O	O	O	O	O
payload	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
injected	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
into	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
the	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
legitimate	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
process	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
“	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
svchost.exe	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
identified	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
payload	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
variant	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
CobaltStrike	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
Beacon	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
post-exploitation	O	O	O	O	O	O
framework	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

To	O	O	O	O	O	O
carry	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
out	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
the	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
theft	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
of	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
credentials	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
the	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
hostile	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
actor	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
used	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
the	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
following	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
tools	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
:	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
“	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
QuarksPWdump	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	I-TECHNIQUE	B-MALWARE
”	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
and	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
“	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
Mimikatz	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	I-TECHNIQUE	B-MALWARE
”	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
.	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O

•	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lateral	O	O	O	O	B-TACTIC	O
movements	O	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O

Through	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
lateral	O	O	O	B-TACTIC	O	B-TACTIC
movements	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
they	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
were	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
able	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
to	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
compromise	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
critical	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
servers	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
and	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
gain	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
access	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
as	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
a	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
domain	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
administrator	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
.	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
NTLM	O	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O
hashes	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
to	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
move	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
laterally	O	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

They	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
tools	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
net.exe	O	O	O	B-TOOL	O	B-TOOL
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
wmic.exe	O	O	O	B-TOOL	O	B-TOOL
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
psexec.exe	O	O	O	B-TOOL	O	B-TOOL
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
smbexec	O	O	O	B-TOOL	O	B-TOOL
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
wmiexec	O	O	O	B-TOOL	O	B-TOOL
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

•	O	O	O	O	O	O
Persistence	O	O	O	B-TACTIC	O	B-TACTIC

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
advanced	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	B-TACTIC	O	B-TACTIC
established	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
persistence	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
certain	O	O	O	O	O	O
servers	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
were	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
interest	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
deployed	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
remote	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
Trojans	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
QuasarRAT	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
moreover	O	O	O	O	O	O
penetration	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
pentesting	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
tools	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cobalt	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
Strike	O	O	O	I-MALWARE	O	I-MALWARE
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	B-MALWARE	O	B-MALWARE
kerberos	O	O	O	I-MALWARE	O	I-MALWARE
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

•	O	O	O	O	O	O
C	O	O	O	B-TACTIC	O	B-TACTIC
&	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
C	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
connections	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC

Hostile	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
two	O	O	O	O	O	O
different	O	O	O	B-TACTIC	O	B-TACTIC
ways	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
to	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
keep	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
connections	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
with	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
C	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
&	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
C	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
servers	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
.	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC

Once	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
vulnerability	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
was	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
exploited	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
to	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
establish	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
itself	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
on	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
the	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
public	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
server	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
moved	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
terminal	O	O	O	O	O	O
server	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

To	O	O	O	O	O	O
establish	O	O	O	B-TACTIC	O	B-TACTIC
communications	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
with	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
the	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
other	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
hosts	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
in	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
the	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
internal	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
network	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
,	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
they	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
installed	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
an	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
SMB	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
beacon	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
terminal	O	O	O	O	O	O
server	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
using	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
bridge	O	O	O	O	O	O
between	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
internal	O	O	O	O	O	O
network	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
C	O	O	O	O	O	O
&	O	O	O	O	O	O
C	O	O	O	O	O	O
server	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
io	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
uploads	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2020	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
05	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
IL	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
4	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Illustration	O	O	O	O	O	O
4	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
First	O	O	O	B-TACTIC	O	B-TACTIC
C	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
&	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
C	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
communication	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
method	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

However	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
established	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
different	O	O	O	O	O	O
method	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
hosts	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
that	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
had	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
direct	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
access	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
or	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
had	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
a	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
proxy	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
.	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
case	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
used	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
the	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
http	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
protocol	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
to	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
establish	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
the	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
communications	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
with	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
the	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
C	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
&	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
C	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
.	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
io	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
uploads	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2020	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
05	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
IL	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
5	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Illustration	O	O	O	O	O	O
5	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
Second	O	O	O	O	O	O
C	O	O	O	B-TACTIC	O	B-TACTIC
&	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
C	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
communication	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
method	O	O	O	I-TACTIC	O	I-TACTIC
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
following	O	O	O	O	O	O
chart	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
there	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
TTPs	O	O	O	O	O	O
developed	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT10	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
during	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
malicious	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
against	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Turkish	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
16	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
14	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
io	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
uploads	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2020	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
05	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
IL	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
6	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Illustration	O	O	O	O	O	O
6	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
TTP	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT10	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

Recommendations	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
recommendable	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
defense	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
sector	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
governments	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
energy	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
telecommunications	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
finance	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
linked	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
projects	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
may	O	O	O	O	O	O
affect	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
interests	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
apply	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
maximum	O	O	O	O	O	O
prevention	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
increase	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
malicious	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaigns	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
groups	O	O	O	O	O	O
presumably	O	O	O	O	O	O
linked	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
recommended	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
apply	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
IOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT	O	O	O	B-CON	O	B-CON
identified	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
intelligence	O	O	O	O	O	O
provider	O	O	O	O	O	O
LAB52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
soon	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
possible	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
recommended	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
keep	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
operating	O	O	O	O	O	O
systems	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
services	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
tools	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
organization	O	O	O	O	O	O
updated	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
latest	O	O	O	O	O	O
security	O	O	O	O	O	O
patches	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
recommended	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
establish	O	O	O	O	O	O
security	O	O	O	O	O	O
policies	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
GPOs	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
control	O	O	O	O	O	O
accesses	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
actions	O	O	O	O	O	O
carried	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
those	O	O	O	O	O	O
systems	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
services	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
exposed	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
internet	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Conclusions	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

Since	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
last	O	O	O	O	O	O
decade	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Turkey	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
acquired	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
important	O	O	O	O	O	O
influence	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
energy	O	O	O	O	O	O
geopolitics	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Eastern	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Mediterranean	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
Sea	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
The	O	O	O	O	O	O
Turkish	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
foreign	O	O	O	O	O	O
policies	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
hindered	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
international	O	O	O	O	O	O
trade	O	O	O	O	O	O
strategies	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Furthermore	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
diplomatic	O	O	O	O	O	O
Turkish	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
support	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
certain	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
ethnic	O	O	O	O	O	O
groups	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
considerate	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
against	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
national	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
security	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
could	O	O	O	O	O	O
provoke	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
Turkey	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
becomes	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
target	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
groups	O	O	O	O	O	O
like	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT10	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
presumably	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
linked	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ministry	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
of	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
State	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Security	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
China	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

APT10	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
wide	O	O	O	O	O	O
range	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
targets	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
sectors	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
interest	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
government	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
of	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
China	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
some	O	O	O	O	O	O
kind	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
link	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
commercial	O	O	O	O	O	O
development	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
OBOR	O	O	O	O	O	O
route	O	O	O	O	O	O
could	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
susceptible	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
being	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeted	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
groups	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT10	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

References	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.mei.edu	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
publications	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
turkeys-eastern-mediterranean-quagmire	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.petroleum-economist.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
3	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
greece.greekreporter.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2018	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
10	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
12	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
greece-egypt-aim-to-strangulate-turkey-in-east-med-turkish-daily-claims	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
4	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
moderndiplomacy.eu	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2019	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
12	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
20	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
the-exclusive-economic-zone-between-libya-and-turkey	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
5	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.ozelburoistihbarat.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
kitalar-bolgeler-akdeniz-karadeniz-ege-marmara	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
dogu-akdenizde-tartisma-harita-uydu-goruntuleri-eren-talha-altun	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
12708	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
6	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kontakos	O	O	O	O	O	O
P	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
2018	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
Blue	O	O	O	O	O	O
economy	O	O	O	O	O	O
enterpreneurship	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Offshore	O	O	O	O	O	O
Energy	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cyprus	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Greece	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Journal	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
International	O	O	O	O	O	O
Scientific	O	O	O	O	O	O
Publications	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
7	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.welt.de	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wirtschaft	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
article204725766	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
EastMed-Das-ist-Europas-neue-Problem-Pipeline.html	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
8	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.turkishminute.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2020	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
02	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
turkey-buys-third-drilling-ship-for-mediterranean-gas-exploration-erdogan	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
9	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.cidob.org	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
publications	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
publication_series	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
notes_internacionals	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
n1	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
156	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
china_moors_in_the_mediterranean_a_sea_of_opportunities_for_europe	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
10	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.aljazeera.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
news	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2019	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
11	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
greece-china-hail-strategic-partnership-eu	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
191111170150762	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
html	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
11	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
<	O	O	O	O	O	O
http	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.ekathimerini.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
247559	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
article	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
ekathimerini	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
news	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
chinese-led-consortium-to-build-cyprus-gas-import-terminal	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
12	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.icij.org	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
investigations	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
china-cables	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
china-cables-who-are-the-uighurs-and-why-mass-detention	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
13	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.voanews.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
extremism-watch	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
uighurs-concerned-china-luring-turkey-silence-xinjiang	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
14	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
Adeo	O	O	O	O	O	O
IT	O	O	O	O	O	O
Consulting	O	O	O	O	O	O

Services	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

January	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

APT10	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
Threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
Analysis	O	O	O	O	O	O
Report	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
adeo.com.tr	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
adeo_annual_threat_report	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
15	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.justice.gov	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
opa	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
pr	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
two-chinese-hackers-associated-ministry-state-security-charged-global-computer-intrusion	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
16	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
attack.mitre.org	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O
           	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
17	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.un.org	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
depts	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
los	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
convention_agreements	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
texts	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
unclos	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
part5	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
htm	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

