<DOCSTART>	O	O	O	O	O	O

(	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cyber	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
GRU	B-ORG	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-ORG
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
XIV	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
conclusions	O	O	O	O	O	O

October	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
18	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2019	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
work	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
analyzed	O	O	O	O	O	O
mainly	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
structure	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
targets	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
TTP	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
GRU	B-ORG	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-ORG
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyber	O	O	O	O	O	O
field	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
based	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
brought	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
light	O	O	O	O	O	O
during	O	O	O	O	O	O
2018	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
allowed	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
obtain	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
detailed	O	O	O	O	O	O
knowledge	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Service	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
activities	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
only	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
intelligence	O	O	O	O	O	O
services	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
but	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
poor	O	O	O	O	O	O
analysts	O	O	O	O	O	O
like	O	O	O	O	O	O
us	O	O	O	O	O	O
who	O	O	O	O	O	O
do	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
all	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
capabilities	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
state	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

With	O	O	O	O	O	O
what	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
know	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
even	O	O	O	O	O	O
analyzing	O	O	O	O	O	O
public	O	O	O	O	O	O
sources	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
some	O	O	O	O	O	O
cases	O	O	O	O	O	O
should	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
considered	O	O	O	O	O	O
sensitive	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
without	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
doubt	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
being	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
analyzed	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
services	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
all	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
world	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
starting	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
Russia	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
itself	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
fact	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
know	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
GRU	B-ORG	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-ORG
better	O	O	O	O	O	O
than	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
year	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
ago	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
does	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
mean	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
now	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
worse	O	O	O	O	O	O
service	O	O	O	O	O	O
than	O	O	O	O	O	O
before	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
remain	O	O	O	O	O	O
part	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
elite	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
fulfilling	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
missions	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
acting	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
any	O	O	O	O	O	O
part	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
world	O	O	O	O	O	O
where	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
required	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
said	O	O	O	O	O	O
one	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
former	O	O	O	O	O	O
directors	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
GRU	B-ORG	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT28	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
whatever	O	O	O	O	O	O
you	O	O	O	O	O	O
want	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
name	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
continue	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
very	O	O	O	O	O	O
important	O	O	O	O	O	O
player	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyber	O	O	O	O	O	O
field	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
course	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
non-cyber	O	O	O	O	O	O
realm	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

We	O	O	O	O	O	O
all	O	O	O	O	O	O
make	O	O	O	O	O	O
mistakes	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
GRU	B-ORG	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-ORG
made	O	O	O	O	O	O
them	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
occasion	O	O	O	O	O	O
–	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
were	O	O	O	O	O	O
published	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

However	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
concern	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
certain	O	O	O	O	O	O
circles	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
GRU	B-ORG	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-ORG
failed	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
operations	O	O	O	O	O	O
than	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
leaked	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
identities	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
modus	O	O	O	O	O	O
operandi	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
some	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
members	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Currently	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
aware	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyber	O	O	O	O	O	O
activity	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
two	O	O	O	O	O	O
Service	O	O	O	O	O	O
Units	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
work	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
coordinated	O	O	O	O	O	O
manner	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
benefit	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
interests	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Russian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Federation	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
;	O	O	O	O	O	O
one	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
them	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Unit	O	O	O	O	O	O
26165	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
responsible	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
technical	O	O	O	O	O	O
operations	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
GRU	B-ORG	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-ORG
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
CNE	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
CNA	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
while	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
other	O	O	O	O	O	O
one	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
Unit	O	O	O	O	O	O
74455	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
responsible	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
psychological	O	O	O	O	O	O
operations	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
PSYOP	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Service	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Their	O	O	O	O	O	O
joint	O	O	O	O	O	O
work	O	O	O	O	O	O
reflects	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Russian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
conception	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
warfare	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
different	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Western	O	O	O	O	O	O
conception	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
handling	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
stolen	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
favor	O	O	O	O	O	O
Russian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
interests	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
identified	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
two	O	O	O	O	O	O
fields	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
action	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
confrontation	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
technical	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
confrontation	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
psychological	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

APT28	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
linked	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
GRU	B-ORG	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
if	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
name	O	O	O	O	O	O
given	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyber	O	O	O	O	O	O
division	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Service	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
possibly	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
operational	O	O	O	O	O	O
since	O	O	O	O	O	O
1953	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
year	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
Military	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
Unit	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
26165	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
founded	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

So	O	O	O	O	O	O
instead	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
‘	O	O	O	O	O	O
fancy	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
bear	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
should	O	O	O	O	O	O
call	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
‘	O	O	O	O	O	O
old	O	O	O	O	O	O
bear	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
change	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
logo	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
attached	O	O	O	O	O	O
image	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
perhaps	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
only	O	O	O	O	O	O
steals	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
benefit	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Russian	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
government	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
but	O	O	O	O	O	O
uses	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
intelligently	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
psychological	O	O	O	O	O	O
operations	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

And	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
only	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
NEC	O	O	O	O	O	O
capabilities	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
like	O	O	O	O	O	O
any	O	O	O	O	O	O
other	O	O	O	O	O	O
intelligence	O	O	O	O	O	O
service	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
world	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
but	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
NAC	O	O	O	O	O	O
capabilities	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
since	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
must	O	O	O	O	O	O
remember	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
military	O	O	O	O	O	O
service	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
therefore	O	O	O	O	O	O
carry	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O
pure	O	O	O	O	O	O
attack	O	O	O	O	O	O
operations	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
just	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
theft	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.securityartwork.es	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
uploads	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2019	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
05	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
bear.jpg	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT28	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Source	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
Old	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bear	O	O	O	O	O	O
Press	O	O	O	O	O	O

We	O	O	O	O	O	O
hope	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
work	O	O	O	O	O	O
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
help	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
little	O	O	O	O	O	O
bit	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
get	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
know	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
GRU	B-ORG	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-ORG
better	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
talked	O	O	O	O	O	O
about	O	O	O	O	O	O
briefly	O	O	O	O	O	O
when	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
discussed	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
issue	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Russian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
cyber-intelligence	O	O	O	O	O	O
community	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
lately	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
all	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
happened	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
deserved	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
series	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
own	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Now	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
wait	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
new	O	O	O	O	O	O
public	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
allows	O	O	O	O	O	O
us	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
analyze	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyber	O	O	O	O	O	O
division	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
FSB	B-SECTOR	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-SECTOR
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
Until	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
few	O	O	O	O	O	O
months	O	O	O	O	O	O
ago	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
FSB	B-SECTOR	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-SECTOR
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
better	O	O	O	O	O	O
known	O	O	O	O	O	O
than	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
GRU	B-ORG	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-ORG
but	O	O	O	O	O	O
surely	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
aspects	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
cannot	O	O	O	O	O	O
even	O	O	O	O	O	O
imagine	O	O	O	O	O	O
…	O	O	O	O	O	O

