<DOCSTART>	O	O	O	O	O	O

China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
From	O	O	O	O	O	O
culture	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
conflict	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyberspace	O	O	O	O	O	O

April	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
14	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE

Since	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
2013	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
US	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
cybersecurity	O	O	O	O	O	O
consultancy	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mandiant	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
published	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
famous	O	O	O	O	O	O
report	O	O	O	O	O	O
about	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT1	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
showing	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
links	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
different	O	O	O	O	O	O
agencies	O	O	O	O	O	O
presumably	O	O	O	O	O	O
associated	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
government	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
news	O	O	O	O	O	O
about	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
actions	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyberspace	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
significantly	O	O	O	O	O	O
increased	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Among	O	O	O	O	O	O
others	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
find	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT15	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT27	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
Winnti	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
Group	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
(	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
APT41	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
)	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O	I-GROUP
;	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
US	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
DoJ	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
allegations	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyber	O	O	O	O	O	O
espionage	O	O	O	O	O	O
towards	O	O	O	O	O	O
five	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
military	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
members	O	O	O	O	O	O
associated	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT1	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
links	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
FBI	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
established	O	O	O	O	O	O
between	O	O	O	O	O	O
Zhu	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hua	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Zhang	O	O	O	O	O	O
Shilong	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT10	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
;	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
alleged	O	O	O	O	O	O
link	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
PLA	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
unit	O	O	O	O	O	O
61398	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
People	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
’	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
s	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Liberations	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Army	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT1	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

With	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
permission	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Russia	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
popular	O	O	O	O	O	O
operation	O	O	O	O	O	O
against	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
DNC	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
become	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
main	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyberspace	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
developing	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
uncountable	O	O	O	O	O	O
number	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
operations	O	O	O	O	O	O
against	O	O	O	O	O	O
all	O	O	O	O	O	O
kind	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
sectors	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
IT	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
military	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
naval	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
industries	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
different	O	O	O	O	O	O
governmental	O	O	O	O	O	O
organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Sometimes	O	O	O	O	O	O
using	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
sophisticated	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
sometimes	O	O	O	O	O	O
less	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
but	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
own	O	O	O	O	O	O
seal	O	O	O	O	O	O
linked	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
extensive	O	O	O	O	O	O
tradition	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

According	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
traditional	O	O	O	O	O	O
ancient	O	O	O	O	O	O
texts	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
civilization	O	O	O	O	O	O
dates	O	O	O	O	O	O
back	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
than	O	O	O	O	O	O
4,000	O	O	O	O	O	O
years	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
first	O	O	O	O	O	O
Xia	O	O	O	O	O	O
dynasty	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Due	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
continuity	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
strength	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
political	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
social	O	O	O	O	O	O
structure	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
protection	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
historical	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
cultural	O	O	O	O	O	O
legacy	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
practically	O	O	O	O	O	O
null	O	O	O	O	O	O
western	O	O	O	O	O	O
influence	O	O	O	O	O	O
until	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
19th	O	O	O	O	O	O
century	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Empire	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
considered	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
oldest	O	O	O	O	O	O
empire	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
exists	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
historical	O	O	O	O	O	O
endurance	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
empire	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
based	O	O	O	O	O	O
solely	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
military	O	O	O	O	O	O
victories	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
but	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
peculiar	O	O	O	O	O	O
way	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
understanding	O	O	O	O	O	O
resistance	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
foreign	O	O	O	O	O	O
invasion	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

As	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
example	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Qing	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dynasty	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
last	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
dynasty	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
ruled	O	O	O	O	O	O
between	O	O	O	O	O	O
1644	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
1912	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
founded	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Aisin-Gioro	O	O	O	O	O	O
clan	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Manchuria	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Manchus	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
currently	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
ethnic	O	O	O	O	O	O
minority	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
population	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
could	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
though	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Similarly	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Yuan	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
dynasty	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
1279	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
1368	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
founded	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mongol	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
invaders	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
heirs	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
legacy	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Genghis	O	O	O	O	O	O
Khan	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Despite	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
language	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
customs	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
tradition	O	O	O	O	O	O
remained	O	O	O	O	O	O
unchanged	O	O	O	O	O	O
thanks	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
bureaucratic	O	O	O	O	O	O
elites	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
who	O	O	O	O	O	O
offered	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
services	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
invaders	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
excuse	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
difficulty	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
would	O	O	O	O	O	O
supposed	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
control	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
country	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
dimensions	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
making	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
only	O	O	O	O	O	O
condition	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
maintain	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
methods	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
language	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Because	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
second-generation	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
invaders	O	O	O	O	O	O
would	O	O	O	O	O	O
assimilate	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
culture	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
coming	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
outsiders	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
home	O	O	O	O	O	O
territories	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
finally	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
ending	O	O	O	O	O	O
up	O	O	O	O	O	O
defending	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
national	O	O	O	O	O	O
interests	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
lab52	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
io	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
uploads	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2020	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
04	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
mountain	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
3022908	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
1920	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
1024x682	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
jpg	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
resistance	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
adaptability	O	O	O	O	O	O
typical	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
character	O	O	O	O	O	O
towards	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
invader	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
still	O	O	O	O	O	O
present	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
witnessed	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
transformation	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
society	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
1984	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
fundamentally	O	O	O	O	O	O
agricultural	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
40%	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
GDP	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
just	O	O	O	O	O	O
35	O	O	O	O	O	O
years	O	O	O	O	O	O
later	O	O	O	O	O	O
dominates	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
technological	O	O	O	O	O	O
world	O	O	O	O	O	O
scenario	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
United	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
well	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
leading	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
deployment	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
5G	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
hand	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Huawei	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Such	O	O	O	O	O	O
achievement	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
occurred	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
only	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
terms	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
competitiveness	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
but	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
making	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
technology	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
intrinsic	O	O	O	O	O	O
part	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
legacy	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
putting	O	O	O	O	O	O
technological	O	O	O	O	O	O
development	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
service	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
national	O	O	O	O	O	O
interest	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

As	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
comparison	O	O	O	O	O	O
mentioned	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
former	O	O	O	O	O	O
head	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Canadian	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Intelligence	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
and	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Security	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Service	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
Asia-Pacific	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Michel	O	O	O	O	O	O
Juneau-Katsua	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
if	O	O	O	O	O	O
Western	O	O	O	O	O	O
intelligence	O	O	O	O	O	O
had	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
steal	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
beach	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
he	O	O	O	O	O	O
would	O	O	O	O	O	O
go	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
night	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
wait	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
nobody	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
see	O	O	O	O	O	O
him	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
steal	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

On	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
other	O	O	O	O	O	O
hand	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
if	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
intelligence	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
had	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
do	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
would	O	O	O	O	O	O
send	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
thousand	O	O	O	O	O	O
tourists	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
way	O	O	O	O	O	O
back	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
would	O	O	O	O	O	O
shake	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
towels	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
day	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
day	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Hiding	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
broad	O	O	O	O	O	O
daylight	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
concept	O	O	O	O	O	O
associated	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
Eastern	O	O	O	O	O	O
culture	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
because	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
even	O	O	O	O	O	O
leaving	O	O	O	O	O	O
aside	O	O	O	O	O	O
large	O	O	O	O	O	O
corporations	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
Xiaomi	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
Huawei	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
obvious	O	O	O	O	O	O
possibility	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
controlling	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
devices	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
managed	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
install	O	O	O	O	O	O
software	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
all	O	O	O	O	O	O
kind	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
any	O	O	O	O	O	O
computer	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
planet	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
uncommon	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
find	O	O	O	O	O	O
binaries	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mandarin	O	O	O	O	O	O
language	O	O	O	O	O	O
resources	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
drivers	O	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O
signed	O	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O
by	O	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	I-GROUP	B-LOC
companies	O	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O
,	O	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O
which	O	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O
could	O	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O
potentially	O	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O
facilitate	O	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O
a	O	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O
directed	O	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O
against	O	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O
any	O	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O
organization	O	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O
.	O	O	O	O	I-GROUP	O

We	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
issue	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
electronic	O	O	O	O	O	O
devices	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
global	O	O	O	O	O	O
massive	O	O	O	O	O	O
sale	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
allowed	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
worldwide	O	O	O	O	O	O
deployment	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
potentially	O	O	O	O	O	O
vulnerable	O	O	O	O	O	O
network	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
video	O	O	O	O	O	O
surveillance	O	O	O	O	O	O
cameras	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
loudspeakers	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
smartbands	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Meanwhile	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
competes	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
Google	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Amazon	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
control	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
home	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

However	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
interested	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
entering	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Thucydides	O	O	O	O	O	O
trap	O	O	O	O	O	O
through	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
direct	O	O	O	O	O	O
confrontation	O	O	O	O	O	O
against	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
United	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
but	O	O	O	O	O	O
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
use	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
done	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
past	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
multipolar	O	O	O	O	O	O
geopolitical	O	O	O	O	O	O
scenario	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
achieve	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
purposes	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
If	O	O	O	O	O	O
you	O	O	O	O	O	O
use	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
enemy	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
defeat	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
enemy	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
you	O	O	O	O	O	O
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
powerful	O	O	O	O	O	O
wherever	O	O	O	O	O	O
you	O	O	O	O	O	O
go	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

About	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
end	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Korean	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
War	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mao	O	O	O	O	O	O
managed	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
gain	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
foothold	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
international	O	O	O	O	O	O
scene	O	O	O	O	O	O
through	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
strategy	O	O	O	O	O	O
very	O	O	O	O	O	O
much	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
line	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
classic	O	O	O	O	O	O
strategist	O	O	O	O	O	O
Sun	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tzu	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
world	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
two	O	O	O	O	O	O
great	O	O	O	O	O	O
superpowers	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
United	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Soviet	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Union	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
fought	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
world	O	O	O	O	O	O
hegemony	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
he	O	O	O	O	O	O
managed	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
see	O	O	O	O	O	O
them	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
equals	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
faced	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
United	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Taiwan	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Strait	O	O	O	O	O	O
conflict	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
almost	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
same	O	O	O	O	O	O
time	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
ideologically	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
geopolitically	O	O	O	O	O	O
dissociated	O	O	O	O	O	O
itself	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
communist	O	O	O	O	O	O
bloc	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
position	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
based	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
fact	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
none	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
powers	O	O	O	O	O	O
would	O	O	O	O	O	O
allow	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
launching	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
nuclear	O	O	O	O	O	O
weapons	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mandarin	O	O	O	O	O	O
territory	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
maintenance	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
public	O	O	O	O	O	O
position	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
claimed	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
no	O	O	O	O	O	O
fear	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
weapons	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

As	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mao	O	O	O	O	O	O
himself	O	O	O	O	O	O
stated	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
600	O	O	O	O	O	O
million	O	O	O	O	O	O
inhabitants	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
area	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
​​	O	O	O	O	O	O
9.6	O	O	O	O	O	O
million	O	O	O	O	O	O
square	O	O	O	O	O	O
kilometers	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
United	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
cannot	O	O	O	O	O	O
annihilate	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
simple	O	O	O	O	O	O
pile	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
atomic	O	O	O	O	O	O
bombs	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

“	O	O	O	O	O	O
Exercising	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
active	O	O	O	O	O	O
position	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mao	O	O	O	O	O	O
ended	O	O	O	O	O	O
up	O	O	O	O	O	O
being	O	O	O	O	O	O
part	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
international	O	O	O	O	O	O
balance	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
independent	O	O	O	O	O	O
voice	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
exerting	O	O	O	O	O	O
psychological	O	O	O	O	O	O
pressure	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
both	O	O	O	O	O	O
sides	O	O	O	O	O	O
through	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
conflicts	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Taiwan	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Strait	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
his	O	O	O	O	O	O
intervention	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vietnam	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
War	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
current	O	O	O	O	O	O
world	O	O	O	O	O	O
offers	O	O	O	O	O	O
very	O	O	O	O	O	O
good	O	O	O	O	O	O
opportunities	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
these	O	O	O	O	O	O
puppeteer	O	O	O	O	O	O
performances	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
attribution	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
hostile	O	O	O	O	O	O
act	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyberspace	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
truly	O	O	O	O	O	O
complex	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
evidenced	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
false	O	O	O	O	O	O
flag	O	O	O	O	O	O
operation	O	O	O	O	O	O
reported	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kaspersky	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
OlympicDestroyer	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

During	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
2018	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
South	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Korea	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
Winter	O	O	O	O	O	O
Olympics	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
OlympicDestroyer	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
paralyzed	O	O	O	B-TECHNIQUE	O	B-TECHNIQUE
IT	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
systems	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
,	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
caused	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
outages	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
,	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
and	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
brought	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
down	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
the	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
organization	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
’	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
s	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
websites	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE
.	O	O	O	I-TECHNIQUE	O	I-TECHNIQUE

What	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
relevant	O	O	O	O	O	O
about	O	O	O	O	O	O
these	O	O	O	O	O	O
actions	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
detailed	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
report	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
tactics	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
techniques	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
procedures	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
TTP	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
were	O	O	O	O	O	O
those	O	O	O	O	O	O
commonly	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lazarous	O	O	O	B-GROUP	O	B-GROUP
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
associated	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
North	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Korea	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

However	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
everything	O	O	O	O	O	O
indicated	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
intentional	O	O	O	O	O	O
errors	O	O	O	O	O	O
had	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
made	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
order	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
facilitate	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
detection	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
TTPs	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
stirring	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
international	O	O	O	O	O	O
stage	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
mediatic	O	O	O	O	O	O
overtones	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
makes	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
sense	O	O	O	O	O	O
if	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
take	O	O	O	O	O	O
into	O	O	O	O	O	O
account	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
February	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
2018	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
North	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Korea	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
surrounded	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
sanctions	O	O	O	O	O	O
derived	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
nuclear	O	O	O	O	O	O
plan	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
specifically	O	O	O	O	O	O
resolutions	O	O	O	O	O	O
2371	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
2375	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
2397	O	O	O	O	O	O
adopted	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
2017	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
fundamentally	O	O	O	O	O	O
damaged	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
relationship	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Looking	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
future	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
everything	O	O	O	O	O	O
indicates	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
continue	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
bet	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
conflict	O	O	O	O	O	O
resolution	O	O	O	O	O	O
through	O	O	O	O	O	O
operations	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyberspace	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
limiting	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
military	O	O	O	O	O	O
interventions	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
what	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
strictly	O	O	O	O	O	O
necessary	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
propaganda	O	O	O	O	O	O
purposes	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
conflict	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
cyberspace	O	O	O	O	O	O
allows	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
certain	O	O	O	O	O	O
extent	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
abandon	O	O	O	O	O	O
Clausewitz	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
theses	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
understanding	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
confrontation	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
battles	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
begin	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
end	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
where	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
enemies	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
defined	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
tangible	O	O	O	O	O	O
units	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
new	O	O	O	O	O	O
era	O	O	O	O	O	O
embraces	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suntzunian	O	O	O	O	O	O
theses	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
promoting	O	O	O	O	O	O
flexibility	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
battle	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
use	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
time	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
weapon	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
concepts	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
rather	O	O	O	O	O	O
foreign	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
Western	O	O	O	O	O	O
tradition	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

While	O	O	O	O	O	O
tradition	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
West	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
fostered	O	O	O	O	O	O
heroism	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
coup	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
decisive	O	O	O	O	O	O
moment	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
ideals	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
based	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
patience	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
subtle	O	O	O	O	O	O
harm	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
accumulation	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
advantages	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
gradual	O	O	O	O	O	O
way	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
concepts	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
matches	O	O	O	O	O	O
perfectly	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
conflict	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Internet	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Thus	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
comfortable	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
new	O	O	O	O	O	O
approach	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
multinational	O	O	O	O	O	O
conflict	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
world	O	O	O	O	O	O
whose	O	O	O	O	O	O
rules	O	O	O	O	O	O
play	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
favor	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
concealment	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
indefiniteness	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
confusion	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Actually	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
rules	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

References	O	O	O	O	O	O

<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.fireeye.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat-research	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2013	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
02	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
mandiant-exposes-apt1	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
chinas-cyber-espionage-units.html	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.elmundo.es	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
internacional	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2015	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
11	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
25	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
5654c172268e3eaa7e8b460f.html	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

On	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
–	O	O	O	O	O	O
Henry	O	O	O	O	O	O
Kissinger	O	O	O	O	O	O
Principles	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
War	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cyberspace	O	O	O	O	O	O
–	O	O	O	O	O	O
Steven	O	O	O	O	O	O
E	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cahanin	O	O	O	O	O	O

<	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.kaspersky.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
about	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
press-releases	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2018	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
the-olympic-false-flag	O	O	O	O	O	O
>	O	O	O	O	O	O

