<DOCSTART>	O	O	O	O	O	O

TA416	O	O	O	O	O	O
Goes	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ground	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Returns	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
Golang	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
Malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
Loader	O	O	O	O	O	O

November	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
23	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE

#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
Executive	O	O	O	O	O	O
Summary	O	O	O	O	O	O

Following	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
National	O	O	O	O	O	O
Day	O	O	O	O	O	O
holiday	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
September	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Proofpoint	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
researchers	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
resumption	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
activity	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
TA416	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Historic	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaigns	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
publicly	O	O	O	O	O	O
attributed	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mustang	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Panda	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
RedDelta	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
new	O	O	O	O	O	O
activity	O	O	O	O	O	O
appears	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
continuation	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
previously	O	O	O	O	O	O
reported	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaigns	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeted	O	O	O	O	O	O
entities	O	O	O	O	O	O
associated	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
diplomatic	O	O	O	O	O	O
relations	O	O	O	O	O	O
between	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vatican	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Communist	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Party	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
well	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
entities	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Myanmar	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeting	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
conducting	O	O	O	O	O	O
diplomacy	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Africa	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Proofpoint	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
researchers	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
identified	O	O	O	O	O	O
updates	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
toolset	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
deliver	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
payloads	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Specifically	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
researchers	O	O	O	O	O	O
identified	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
new	O	O	O	O	O	O
Golang	O	O	O	O	O	O
variant	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
TA416	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
loader	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
identified	O	O	O	O	O	O
consistent	O	O	O	O	O	O
usage	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeted	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaigns	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

As	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
continues	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
publicly	O	O	O	O	O	O
reported	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
security	O	O	O	O	O	O
researchers	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
exemplify	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
persistence	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
modification	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
toolset	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
frustrate	O	O	O	O	O	O
analysis	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
evade	O	O	O	O	O	O
detection	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

While	O	O	O	O	O	O
baseline	O	O	O	O	O	O
changes	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
payloads	O	O	O	O	O	O
do	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
greatly	O	O	O	O	O	O
increase	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
difficulty	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
attributing	O	O	O	O	O	O
TA416	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaigns	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
do	O	O	O	O	O	O
make	O	O	O	O	O	O
automated	O	O	O	O	O	O
detection	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
execution	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
components	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
independent	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
infection	O	O	O	O	O	O
chain	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
challenging	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
researchers	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
may	O	O	O	O	O	O
represent	O	O	O	O	O	O
efforts	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
continue	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
pursuit	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
espionage	O	O	O	O	O	O
objectives	O	O	O	O	O	O
while	O	O	O	O	O	O
maintaining	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
embattled	O	O	O	O	O	O
toolset	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
staying	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
daily	O	O	O	O	O	O
Twitter	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
conversation	O	O	O	O	O	O
popular	O	O	O	O	O	O
amongst	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
researchers	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
Renewed	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
Activity	O	O	O	O	O	O

After	O	O	O	O	O	O
nearly	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
month	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
inactivity	O	O	O	O	O	O
following	O	O	O	O	O	O
publications	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
researchers	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Proofpoint	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
analysts	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
identified	O	O	O	O	O	O
limited	O	O	O	O	O	O
signs	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
renewed	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
activity	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.proofpoint.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
us	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat-reference	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
attributed	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
APT	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
TA416	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
referred	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
Mustang	O	O	O	O	O	O
Panda	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
RedDelta	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

1	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
Recorded	O	O	O	O	O	O
Future	O	O	O	O	O	O
researchers	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
previously	O	O	O	O	O	O
noted	O	O	O	O	O	O
historic	O	O	O	O	O	O
periods	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
dormancy	O	O	O	O	O	O
following	O	O	O	O	O	O
disclosure	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
TA416	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeted	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaigns	O	O	O	O	O	O
.2	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
most	O	O	O	O	O	O
recent	O	O	O	O	O	O
period	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
inactivity	O	O	O	O	O	O
encompassed	O	O	O	O	O	O
September	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
16	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
through	O	O	O	O	O	O
October	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
10	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Notably	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
time	O	O	O	O	O	O
period	O	O	O	O	O	O
included	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
National	O	O	O	O	O	O
holiday	O	O	O	O	O	O
referred	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
National	O	O	O	O	O	O
Day	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
following	O	O	O	O	O	O
unofficial	O	O	O	O	O	O
vacation	O	O	O	O	O	O
period	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
Golden	O	O	O	O	O	O
Week	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
resumption	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
activity	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
TA416	O	O	O	O	O	O
included	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
continued	O	O	O	O	O	O
use	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
social	O	O	O	O	O	O
engineering	O	O	O	O	O	O
lures	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.proofpoint.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
us	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
corporate-blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
post	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
cybersecurity	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
101	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
what-social-engineering	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
referencing	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
provisional	O	O	O	O	O	O
agreement	O	O	O	O	O	O
recently	O	O	O	O	O	O
renewed	O	O	O	O	O	O
between	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vatican	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Holy	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
See	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Communist	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Party	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
CCP	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
.3	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O

Additionally	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
spoofed	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
header	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
fields	O	O	O	O	O	O
were	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
appear	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
imitate	O	O	O	O	O	O
journalists	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Union	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
of	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Catholic	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Asia	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
News	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
confluence	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
themed	O	O	O	O	O	O
social	O	O	O	O	O	O
engineering	O	O	O	O	O	O
content	O	O	O	O	O	O
suggests	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
continued	O	O	O	O	O	O
focus	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
matters	O	O	O	O	O	O
pertaining	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
evolving	O	O	O	O	O	O
relationship	O	O	O	O	O	O
between	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Catholic	O	O	O	O	O	O
Church	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
CCP	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
Analysis	O	O	O	O	O	O

Proofpoint	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
researchers	O	O	O	O	O	O
identified	O	O	O	O	O	O
two	O	O	O	O	O	O
RAR	O	O	O	O	O	O
archives	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
serve	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
droppers	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

One	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
these	O	O	O	O	O	O
files	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
found	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
self-extracting	O	O	O	O	O	O
RAR	O	O	O	O	O	O
archive	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

For	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
purposes	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
analysis	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
self-extracting	O	O	O	O	O	O
archive	O	O	O	O	O	O
file	O	O	O	O	O	O
AdobelmdyU.exe	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
930b7a798e3279b7460e30ce2f3a2deccbc252f3ca213cb022f5b7e6a25a0867	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
examined	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
initial	O	O	O	O	O	O
delivery	O	O	O	O	O	O
vector	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
these	O	O	O	O	O	O
RAR	O	O	O	O	O	O
archives	O	O	O	O	O	O
could	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
identified	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

However	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
historically	O	O	O	O	O	O
TA416	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
including	O	O	O	O	O	O
Google	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Drive	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dropbox	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
URLs	O	O	O	O	O	O
within	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
emails	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
deliver	O	O	O	O	O	O
archives	O	O	O	O	O	O
containing	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
related	O	O	O	O	O	O
components	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Once	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
RAR	O	O	O	O	O	O
archive	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
extracted	O	O	O	O	O	O
four	O	O	O	O	O	O
files	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
installed	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
host	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
portable	O	O	O	O	O	O
executable	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Adobelm.exe	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
executed	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
installed	O	O	O	O	O	O
files	O	O	O	O	O	O
include	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Adobelm.exe	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
0459e62c5444896d5be404c559c834ba455fa5cae1689c70fc8c61bc15468681	O	O	O	O	O	O

A	O	O	O	O	O	O
legitimate	O	O	O	O	O	O
Adobe	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
executable	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
DLL	O	O	O	O	O	O
Side-Loading	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hex.dll	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Adobehelp.exe	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
e3e3c28f7a96906e6c30f56e8e6b013e42b5113967d6fb054c32885501dfd1b7	O	O	O	O	O	O

An	O	O	O	O	O	O
unused	O	O	O	O	O	O
binary	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
previously	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
malicious	O	O	O	O	O	O
RAR	O	O	O	O	O	O
archives	O	O	O	O	O	O
linked	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
TA416	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
hex.dll	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
235752f22f1a21e18e0833fc26e1cdb4834a56ee53ec7acb8a402129329c0cdd	O	O	O	O	O	O

A	O	O	O	O	O	O
Golang	O	O	O	O	O	O
binary	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
decrypts	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
loads	O	O	O	O	O	O
adobeupdate.dat	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
payload	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
adobeupdate.dat	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
afa06df5a2c33dc0bdf80bbe09dade421b3e8b5990a56246e0d7053d5668d91	O	O	O	O	O	O

 	O	O	O	O	O	O
The	O	O	O	O	O	O
encrypted	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
payload	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
image	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O
base64	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
removed	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
Execution	O	O	O	O	O	O
Diagram	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

Following	O	O	O	O	O	O
RAR	O	O	O	O	O	O
extraction	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Adobelm.exe	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
legitimate	O	O	O	O	O	O
PE	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
DLL	O	O	O	O	O	O
side-loading	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
hex.dll	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
executed	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
calls	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
PE	O	O	O	O	O	O
export	O	O	O	O	O	O
function	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
hex.dll	O	O	O	O	O	O
named	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
CEFProcessForkHandlerEx	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
Historically	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
TA416	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaigns	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
file	O	O	O	O	O	O
name	O	O	O	O	O	O
hex.dll	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
same	O	O	O	O	O	O
PE	O	O	O	O	O	O
export	O	O	O	O	O	O
name	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
achieve	O	O	O	O	O	O
DLL	O	O	O	O	O	O
side-loading	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
Microsoft	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Windows	O	O	O	O	O	O
PE	O	O	O	O	O	O
DLL	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
These	O	O	O	O	O	O
files	O	O	O	O	O	O
served	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
loaders	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
decryptors	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
encrypted	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
payloads	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
file	O	O	O	O	O	O
would	O	O	O	O	O	O
read	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
load	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
decrypt	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
execute	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
payload	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
regularly	O	O	O	O	O	O
named	O	O	O	O	O	O
adobeupdate.dat	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
case	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
loader	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
found	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
case	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
identified	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Golang	O	O	O	O	O	O
binary	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Proofpoint	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
previously	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
file	O	O	O	O	O	O
type	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
use	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
TA416	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Both	O	O	O	O	O	O
identified	O	O	O	O	O	O
RAR	O	O	O	O	O	O
archives	O	O	O	O	O	O
were	O	O	O	O	O	O
found	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
drop	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
same	O	O	O	O	O	O
encrypted	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
file	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Golang	O	O	O	O	O	O
loader	O	O	O	O	O	O
samples	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
Golang	O	O	O	O	O	O
loader	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
compilation	O	O	O	O	O	O
creation	O	O	O	O	O	O
time	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
dates	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
June	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
24	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

However	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
command	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
control	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
infrastructure	O	O	O	O	O	O
discussed	O	O	O	O	O	O
later	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
posting	O	O	O	O	O	O
suggests	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
payload	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Golang	O	O	O	O	O	O
loader	O	O	O	O	O	O
variant	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
were	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
after	O	O	O	O	O	O
August	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
24	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Despite	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
file	O	O	O	O	O	O
type	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
loader	O	O	O	O	O	O
changing	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
functionality	O	O	O	O	O	O
remains	O	O	O	O	O	O
largely	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
same	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
reads	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
file	O	O	O	O	O	O
adobeupdate.dat	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
retrieves	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
XOR	O	O	O	O	O	O
key	O	O	O	O	O	O
beginning	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
offset	O	O	O	O	O	O
x00	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
continues	O	O	O	O	O	O
until	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
reads	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
null	O	O	O	O	O	O
byte	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
then	O	O	O	O	O	O
decrypts	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
payload	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
finally	O	O	O	O	O	O
executes	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
decrypted	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
adobeupdate.dat	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
results	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
execution	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
payload	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
ultimately	O	O	O	O	O	O
calls	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
command	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
control	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
IP	O	O	O	O	O	O
45.248.87	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
162	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
following	O	O	O	O	O	O
registry	O	O	O	O	O	O
key	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
created	O	O	O	O	O	O
during	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
process	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
runs	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
startup	O	O	O	O	O	O
establishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
persistence	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Notably	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
sample	O	O	O	O	O	O
uses	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
distinct	O	O	O	O	O	O
file	O	O	O	O	O	O
installation	O	O	O	O	O	O
directory	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
AdobelmdyU	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Registry	O	O	O	O	O	O
Key	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Data	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
HKEY	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
LOCAL	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
MACHINE	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
SOFTWARE	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
Wow6432Node	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
Microsoft	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
Windows	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
CurrentVersion	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
Run	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
AdobelmdyU	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O

  	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
C	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
ProgramData	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
Adobe	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
AdobelmdyU	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
Adobelm.exe	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
402	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
Registry	O	O	O	O	O	O
Key	O	O	O	O	O	O
established	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
persistence	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
Consistent	O	O	O	O	O	O
TA416	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tools	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
payload	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
unlike	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Golang	O	O	O	O	O	O
loader	O	O	O	O	O	O
variant	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
seems	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
remain	O	O	O	O	O	O
consistent	O	O	O	O	O	O
when	O	O	O	O	O	O
compared	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
previous	O	O	O	O	O	O
versions	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Historical	O	O	O	O	O	O
analysis	O	O	O	O	O	O
conducted	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
Avira	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Recorded	O	O	O	O	O	O
Future	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
documented	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
encrypted	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
payloads	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
disguised	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
gif	O	O	O	O	O	O
files	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
fact	O	O	O	O	O	O
encrypted	O	O	O	O	O	O
PE	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
DLL	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
files	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

These	O	O	O	O	O	O
encrypted	O	O	O	O	O	O
files	O	O	O	O	O	O
contain	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
hardcoded	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
XOR	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
decryption	O	O	O	O	O	O
key	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
begins	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
offset	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
x00	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
continues	O	O	O	O	O	O
until	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
null	O	O	O	O	O	O
byte	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
read	O	O	O	O	O	O
.4	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
In	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
case	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Golang	O	O	O	O	O	O
Binary	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
loader	O	O	O	O	O	O
reads	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
encryption	O	O	O	O	O	O
key	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
same	O	O	O	O	O	O
manner	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
x00	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
null	O	O	O	O	O	O
byte	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
hardcoded	O	O	O	O	O	O
key	O	O	O	O	O	O
ending	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
offset	O	O	O	O	O	O
x09	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
represents	O	O	O	O	O	O
continued	O	O	O	O	O	O
usage	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
anti-analysis	O	O	O	O	O	O
method	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
makes	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
execution	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
payloads	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
complex	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
complicates	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
detection	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
command	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
control	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
infrastructure	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.proofpoint.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
us	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat-reference	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
communicates	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hardcoded	O	O	O	O	O	O
Decryption	O	O	O	O	O	O
Key	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
Byte	O	O	O	O	O	O
Sequence	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
66	O	O	O	O	O	O
59	O	O	O	O	O	O
50	O	O	O	O	O	O
6C	O	O	O	O	O	O
79	O	O	O	O	O	O
73	O	O	O	O	O	O
43	O	O	O	O	O	O
46	O	O	O	O	O	O
6C	O	O	O	O	O	O
6B	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
3	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
XOR	O	O	O	O	O	O
decryption	O	O	O	O	O	O
key	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
image	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O
base64	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
removed	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
4	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
byte	O	O	O	O	O	O
sequence	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
hardcoded	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
XOR	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
decryption	O	O	O	O	O	O
key	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Following	O	O	O	O	O	O
decryption	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
resulting	O	O	O	O	O	O
file	O	O	O	O	O	O
reflects	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
valid	O	O	O	O	O	O
PE	O	O	O	O	O	O
header	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
payload	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Shellcode	O	O	O	O	O	O
appears	O	O	O	O	O	O
between	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
MZ	O	O	O	O	O	O
header	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
DOS	O	O	O	O	O	O
message	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
function	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
shellcode	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
write	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
PE	O	O	O	O	O	O
DLL	O	O	O	O	O	O
into	O	O	O	O	O	O
RWX	O	O	O	O	O	O
memory	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
begin	O	O	O	O	O	O
execution	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
beginning	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
file	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
establishes	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
entry	O	O	O	O	O	O
point	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
payload	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
prevents	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
entry	O	O	O	O	O	O
point	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
found	O	O	O	O	O	O
error	O	O	O	O	O	O
when	O	O	O	O	O	O
executing	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
common	O	O	O	O	O	O
technique	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
many	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
families	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
exclusive	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
TA416	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
variants	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
shellcode	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
unlikely	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
appear	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
legitimate	O	O	O	O	O	O
software	O	O	O	O	O	O
DLLs	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
image	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O
base64	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
removed	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
5	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
byte	O	O	O	O	O	O
sequence	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
XOR	O	O	O	O	O	O
decryption	O	O	O	O	O	O
key	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
Command	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Control	O	O	O	O	O	O
Infrastructure	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
command	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
control	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
communication	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
these	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
samples	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
consistent	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
previously	O	O	O	O	O	O
documented	O	O	O	O	O	O
versions	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
C2	O	O	O	O	O	O
traffic	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
successfully	O	O	O	O	O	O
detected	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
existing	O	O	O	O	O	O
Proofpoint	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Emerging	O	O	O	O	O	O
Threats	O	O	O	O	O	O
Suricata	O	O	O	O	O	O
signature	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
publicly	O	O	O	O	O	O
available	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
part	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
ET	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
OPEN	O	O	O	O	O	O
public	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
ruleset	O	O	O	O	O	O
.5	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
The	O	O	O	O	O	O
following	O	O	O	O	O	O
IP	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
example	O	O	O	O	O	O
command	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
control	O	O	O	O	O	O
communication	O	O	O	O	O	O
URLs	O	O	O	O	O	O
were	O	O	O	O	O	O
identified	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
45.248.87	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
162	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
hxxp	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
45.248.87	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
162	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
756d1598	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
hxxp	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
45.248.87	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
162	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
9f86852b	O	O	O	O	O	O

Further	O	O	O	O	O	O
research	O	O	O	O	O	O
regarding	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
command	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
control	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
IP	O	O	O	O	O	O
indicated	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
hosted	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Internet	O	O	O	O	O	O
Service	O	O	O	O	O	O
Provider	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Anchnet	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Asia	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Limited	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
appeared	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
active	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
use	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
command	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
control	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
server	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
least	O	O	O	O	O	O
August	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
24	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
through	O	O	O	O	O	O
September	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
28	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
notable	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
time	O	O	O	O	O	O
period	O	O	O	O	O	O
predates	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
period	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
dormancy	O	O	O	O	O	O
discussed	O	O	O	O	O	O
above	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
likely	O	O	O	O	O	O
resulted	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
Recorded	O	O	O	O	O	O
Future	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
publication	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
TA416	O	O	O	O	O	O
activity	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Additionally	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
indicates	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
server	O	O	O	O	O	O
ceased	O	O	O	O	O	O
being	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
during	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
dormancy	O	O	O	O	O	O
period	O	O	O	O	O	O
possibly	O	O	O	O	O	O
indicating	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
infrastructure	O	O	O	O	O	O
overhaul	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
during	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
time	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
image	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O
base64	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
removed	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
6	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
RiskIQ	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
indicating	O	O	O	O	O	O
TA416	O	O	O	O	O	O
command	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
control	O	O	O	O	O	O
server	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
period	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
activity	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
Conclusion	O	O	O	O	O	O

Continued	O	O	O	O	O	O
activity	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
TA416	O	O	O	O	O	O
demonstrates	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
persistent	O	O	O	O	O	O
adversary	O	O	O	O	O	O
making	O	O	O	O	O	O
incremental	O	O	O	O	O	O
changes	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
documented	O	O	O	O	O	O
toolsets	O	O	O	O	O	O
so	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
remain	O	O	O	O	O	O
effective	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
carrying	O	O	O	O	O	O
out	O	O	O	O	O	O
espionage	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaigns	O	O	O	O	O	O
against	O	O	O	O	O	O
global	O	O	O	O	O	O
targets	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
introduction	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
Golang	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
loader	O	O	O	O	O	O
alongside	O	O	O	O	O	O
continued	O	O	O	O	O	O
encryption	O	O	O	O	O	O
efforts	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
payloads	O	O	O	O	O	O
suggest	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
may	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
conscious	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
increased	O	O	O	O	O	O
detection	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
tools	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
demonstrates	O	O	O	O	O	O
adaptation	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
response	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
publications	O	O	O	O	O	O
regarding	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaigns	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

These	O	O	O	O	O	O
tool	O	O	O	O	O	O
adjustments	O	O	O	O	O	O
combined	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
recurrent	O	O	O	O	O	O
command	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
control	O	O	O	O	O	O
infrastructure	O	O	O	O	O	O
revision	O	O	O	O	O	O
suggests	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
TA416	O	O	O	O	O	O
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
persist	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeting	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
diplomatic	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
religious	O	O	O	O	O	O
organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

While	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
specifics	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
tools	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
procedures	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
evolved	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
appears	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
motivation	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeted	O	O	O	O	O	O
sectors	O	O	O	O	O	O
likely	O	O	O	O	O	O
remain	O	O	O	O	O	O
consistent	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

TA416	O	O	O	O	O	O
continues	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
embody	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
persistent	O	O	O	O	O	O
aspect	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
APT	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Proofpoint	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
analysts	O	O	O	O	O	O
expect	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
continue	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
detect	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
activity	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
coming	O	O	O	O	O	O
months	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
IOCs	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
IOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
IOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Type	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Description	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
930b7a798e3279b7460e30ce2f3a2deccbc252f3ca213cb022f5b7e6a25a0867	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
SHA256	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
AdobelmdyU.exe	O	O	O	O	O	O
        	O	O	O	O	O	O
RAR	O	O	O	O	O	O
Archive	O	O	O	O	O	O
Containing	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
  	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
6a5b0cfdaf402e94f892f66a0f53e347d427be4105ab22c1a9f259238c272b60	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
SHA256	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
Adobel.exe	O	O	O	O	O	O
            	O	O	O	O	O	O
Self	O	O	O	O	O	O
Extracting	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
RAR	O	O	O	O	O	O
Archive	O	O	O	O	O	O
Containing	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
  	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
0459e62c5444896d5be404c559c834ba455fa5cae1689c70fc8c61bc15468681	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
SHA256	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
Adobelm.exe	O	O	O	O	O	O
         	O	O	O	O	O	O
Legitimate	O	O	O	O	O	O
PE	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
loads	O	O	O	O	O	O
Golang	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Loader	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
235752f22f1a21e18e0833fc26e1cdb4834a56ee53ec7acb8a402129329c0cdd	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
SHA256	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
hex.dll	O	O	O	O	O	O
               	O	O	O	O	O	O
Golang	O	O	O	O	O	O
binary	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Loader	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
e3e3c28f7a96906e6c30f56e8e6b013e42b5113967d6fb054c32885501dfd1b7	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
SHA256	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
AdobeHelp.exe	O	O	O	O	O	O
         	O	O	O	O	O	O
Unused	O	O	O	O	O	O
PE	O	O	O	O	O	O
File	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
afa06df5a2c33dc0bdf80bbe09dade421b3e8b5990a56246e0d7053d5668d917	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
SHA256	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
adobeupdate.dat	O	O	O	O	O	O
      	O	O	O	O	O	O
Encrypted	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Payload	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
45.248.87	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
162	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
C2	O	O	O	O	O	O
IP	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
Command	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
control	O	O	O	O	O	O
IP	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
HKEY	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
LOCAL	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
MACHINE	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
SOFTWARE	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
Wow6432Node	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O

\	O	O	O	O	O	O
Microsoft	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Windows	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
CurrentVersion	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
Run	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
AdobelmdyU	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
RegKey	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
Registry	O	O	O	O	O	O
Key	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
establishes	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
persistence	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Emerging	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Threats	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Signatures	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
2018228	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
et	O	O	O	O	O	O
trojan	O	O	O	O	O	O
possible	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
plugx	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
common	O	O	O	O	O	O
header	O	O	O	O	O	O
struct	O	O	O	O	O	O

References	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O

1	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
State-Sponsored	O	O	O	O	O	O
Group	O	O	O	O	O	O
‘	O	O	O	O	O	O
RedDelta	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
Targets	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vatican	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Catholic	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Organizations	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
]	O	O	O	O	O	O

(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.recordedfuture.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
reddelta-targets-catholic-organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O

"	O	O	O	O	O	O
Chinese	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
State-Sponsored	O	O	O	O	O	O
Group	O	O	O	O	O	O
‘	O	O	O	O	O	O
RedDelta	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
Targets	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vatican	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Catholic	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Organizations	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O

2	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
Back	O	O	O	O	O	O
Despite	O	O	O	O	O	O
Disruption	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
RedDelta	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resumes	O	O	O	O	O	O
Operations	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O

(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.recordedfuture.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
reddelta-cyber-threat-operations	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O

"	O	O	O	O	O	O
Back	O	O	O	O	O	O
Despite	O	O	O	O	O	O
Disruption	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
RedDelta	O	O	O	O	O	O
Resumes	O	O	O	O	O	O
Operations	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

3	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
Holy	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
See	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
renew	O	O	O	O	O	O
Provisional	O	O	O	O	O	O
Agreement	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
years	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O

(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.vaticannews.va	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
vatican-city	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
news	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2020	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
10	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
holy-see-china-provisional-agreement-renew-appointment-bishops.html	O	O	O	O	O	O

"	O	O	O	O	O	O
Holy	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
See	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
China	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
renew	O	O	O	O	O	O
Provisional	O	O	O	O	O	O
Agreement	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
years	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

4	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
New	O	O	O	O	O	O
wave	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
targets	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hong	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Kong	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
]	O	O	O	O	O	O

(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.avira.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
en	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
new-wave-of-plugx-targets-hong-kong	O	O	O	O	O	O

"	O	O	O	O	O	O
New	O	O	O	O	O	O
wave	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
PlugX	O	O	O	O	O	O
targets	O	O	O	O	O	O
Hong	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Kong	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

5	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
Emerging	O	O	O	O	O	O
Threats	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ruleset	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O

(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
doc.emergingthreats.net	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
bin	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
view	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
Main	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2018228	O	O	O	O	O	O

"	O	O	O	O	O	O
Emerging	O	O	O	O	O	O
Threats	O	O	O	O	O	O
Rules	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

