<DOCSTART>	O	O	O	O	O	O

Phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
Attack	O	O	O	O	O	O
Report	O	O	O	O	O	O
Coronavirus	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
Payment	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lures	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Rise	O	O	O	O	O	O

April	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
01	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE

Proofpoint	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
researchers	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
emerging	O	O	O	O	O	O
trend	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
credential	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
social	O	O	O	O	O	O
engineering	O	O	O	O	O	O
lures	O	O	O	O	O	O
around	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
financial	O	O	O	O	O	O
relief	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

These	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaigns	O	O	O	O	O	O
use	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
promise	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
payments	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
global	O	O	O	O	O	O
governments	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
businesses	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
specifically	O	O	O	O	O	O
financial	O	O	O	O	O	O
institutions	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
aimed	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
easing	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
economic	O	O	O	O	O	O
impact	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
ongoing	O	O	O	O	O	O
pandemic	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
urge	O	O	O	O	O	O
users	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
click	O	O	O	O	O	O
links	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
download	O	O	O	O	O	O
files	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
credential	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
update	O	O	O	O	O	O
surrounding	O	O	O	O	O	O
payment	O	O	O	O	O	O
fraud	O	O	O	O	O	O
news	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
highlight	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
few	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
these	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
examples	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeting	O	O	O	O	O	O
those	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
U.S	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
UK	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Australia	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Government-Themed	O	O	O	O	O	O
Attacks	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Credential	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phish	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
Trump	O	O	O	O	O	O
Administration	O	O	O	O	O	O
Covid	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
Check	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
Most	O	O	O	O	O	O
Americans	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Key	O	O	O	O	O	O
Points	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
This	O	O	O	O	O	O
medium-sized	O	O	O	O	O	O
credential	O	O	O	O	O	O
phish	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
primarily	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeted	O	O	O	O	O	O
U.S	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
healthcare	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
higher	O	O	O	O	O	O
education	O	O	O	O	O	O
organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
message	O	O	O	O	O	O
claiming	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Trump	O	O	O	O	O	O
administration	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
considering	O	O	O	O	O	O
sending	O	O	O	O	O	O
most	O	O	O	O	O	O
American	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
adults	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
check	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
help	O	O	O	O	O	O
stimulate	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
economy	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
asks	O	O	O	O	O	O
recipients	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
verify	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
account	O	O	O	O	O	O
through	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
malicious	O	O	O	O	O	O
link	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
directs	O	O	O	O	O	O
them	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
US	O	O	O	O	O	O
Stimulus	O	O	O	O	O	O
Payment	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
Email	O	O	O	O	O	O
Example	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
image	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O
base64	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
removed	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
US	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Payroll	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
Relief	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lure	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Government-Themed	O	O	O	O	O	O
Attacks	O	O	O	O	O	O
Summary	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
medium-sized	O	O	O	O	O	O
credential	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
primarily	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeted	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
United	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
largely	O	O	O	O	O	O
sent	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
healthcare	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
higher	O	O	O	O	O	O
education	O	O	O	O	O	O
organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Secondary	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeting	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
includes	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
technology	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
industry	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
including	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
security	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
companies	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
messages	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
notable	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
crude	O	O	O	O	O	O
design	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
message	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
clear	O	O	O	O	O	O
grammar	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
usage	O	O	O	O	O	O
errors	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
uses	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
basic	O	O	O	O	O	O
webpage	O	O	O	O	O	O
clearly	O	O	O	O	O	O
branded	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
free	O	O	O	O	O	O
website	O	O	O	O	O	O
maker	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
credential	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
notes	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Trump	O	O	O	O	O	O
administration	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
considering	O	O	O	O	O	O
sending	O	O	O	O	O	O
most	O	O	O	O	O	O
American	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
adults	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
check	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
$1,000	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
part	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
efforts	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
stimulate	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
economy	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
help	O	O	O	O	O	O
workers	O	O	O	O	O	O
whose	O	O	O	O	O	O
jobs	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
disrupted	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
business	O	O	O	O	O	O
closures	O	O	O	O	O	O
because	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
pandemic	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Recipients	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
directed	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
verify	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
new	O	O	O	O	O	O
payroll	O	O	O	O	O	O
directory	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
clicking	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
malicious	O	O	O	O	O	O
link	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

If	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
recipient	O	O	O	O	O	O
clicks	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
link	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
taken	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
asks	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
domain	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
username	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
address	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
password	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
shown	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
Covid	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
Email	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landing	O	O	O	O	O	O
Page	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
image	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O
base64	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
removed	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
US	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Payroll	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
Relief	O	O	O	O	O	O
Credential	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
Page	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Credential	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phish	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
Australian	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Coronavirus	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tax	O	O	O	O	O	O
Relief	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Key	O	O	O	O	O	O
Points	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
This	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
claims	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
sent	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
major	O	O	O	O	O	O
Australian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
newspaper	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
uses	O	O	O	O	O	O
subject	O	O	O	O	O	O
lines	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
Government	O	O	O	O	O	O
announces	O	O	O	O	O	O
increased	O	O	O	O	O	O
tax	O	O	O	O	O	O
benefits	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
response	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Coronavirus	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
messages	O	O	O	O	O	O
contain	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
PDF	O	O	O	O	O	O
attachment	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
embedded	O	O	O	O	O	O
URL	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
leads	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
OneDrive	O	O	O	O	O	O
credential	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
Australian	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tax	O	O	O	O	O	O
Relief	O	O	O	O	O	O
Credential	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
Email	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
image	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O
base64	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
removed	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
3	O	O	O	O	O	O
Australian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tax	O	O	O	O	O	O
Benefit	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lure	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Credential	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phish	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
Australian	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Government	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Summary	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
emails	O	O	O	O	O	O
within	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
claim	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
delivered	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
major	O	O	O	O	O	O
newspaper	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Australia	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
3	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
shows	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
actually	O	O	O	O	O	O
delivered	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
Romanian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
top-level	O	O	O	O	O	O
domain	O	O	O	O	O	O
address	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
ro	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

To	O	O	O	O	O	O
appear	O	O	O	O	O	O
authentic	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
message	O	O	O	O	O	O
includes	O	O	O	O	O	O
supposed	O	O	O	O	O	O
contact	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
paper	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
notes	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
…	O	O	O	O	O	O
happy	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
advise	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
now	O	O	O	O	O	O
moved	O	O	O	O	O	O
back	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
address	O	O	O	O	O	O
provided	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
notable	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
address	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
does	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
match	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
newspaper	O	O	O	O	O	O
being	O	O	O	O	O	O
spoofed	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
claims	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
Government	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
released	O	O	O	O	O	O
its	O	O	O	O	O	O
stimulus	O	O	O	O	O	O
package	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
response	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Coronavirus	O	O	O	O	O	O
outbreak	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
encourages	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
recipient	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
open	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
malicious	O	O	O	O	O	O
attachment	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
details	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
attachment	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
Adobe	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
PDF	O	O	O	O	O	O
document	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
spoofed	O	O	O	O	O	O
Microsoft	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
OneDrive	O	O	O	O	O	O
branding	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
informs	O	O	O	O	O	O
users	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
Your	O	O	O	O	O	O
document	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
waiting	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
you	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
encourages	O	O	O	O	O	O
them	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
click	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
embedded	O	O	O	O	O	O
link	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
shown	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
4	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
OneDrive	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
PDF	O	O	O	O	O	O
Example	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
image	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O
base64	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
removed	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
4	O	O	O	O	O	O
Australian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tax	O	O	O	O	O	O
Benefit	O	O	O	O	O	O
Malicious	O	O	O	O	O	O
Attachment	O	O	O	O	O	O

After	O	O	O	O	O	O
clicking	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
link	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
recipient	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
taken	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
asks	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
Microsoft	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
OneDrive	O	O	O	O	O	O
credentials	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Credential	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phish	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
WHO-IMF	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
Relief	O	O	O	O	O	O
Compensation	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
Steals	O	O	O	O	O	O
Emails	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Passwords	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Key	O	O	O	O	O	O
Points	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
This	O	O	O	O	O	O
small	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
targets	O	O	O	O	O	O
technology	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
IT	O	O	O	O	O	O
organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
subject	O	O	O	O	O	O
line	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
Relief	O	O	O	O	O	O
Compensation	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
claims	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
come	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
World	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Health	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Organization	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
WHO	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
International	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Monetary	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Fund	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
IMF	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
says	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
recipient	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
randomly	O	O	O	O	O	O
selected	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
compensated	O	O	O	O	O	O
financially	O	O	O	O	O	O
due	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
outbreak	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
Epidemic	O	O	O	O	O	O
outbreak	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
malicious	O	O	O	O	O	O
Microsoft	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Excel	O	O	O	O	O	O
branded	O	O	O	O	O	O
attachment	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
gathers	O	O	O	O	O	O
emails	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
passwords	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
Covid	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
WHO-IMF	O	O	O	O	O	O
Credential	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
Email	O	O	O	O	O	O
Example	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
image	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O
base64	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
removed	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
5	O	O	O	O	O	O
Fake	O	O	O	O	O	O
WHO	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
IMF	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Compensation	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lure	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
WHO	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Credential	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phish	O	O	O	O	O	O
Summary	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
small	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
targets	O	O	O	O	O	O
technology	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
IT	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
companies	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
arrives	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
subject	O	O	O	O	O	O
line	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
Relief	O	O	O	O	O	O
Compensation	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
claims	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
come	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
World	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Health	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Organization	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
WHO	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
working	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
International	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Monetary	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Fund	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
IMF	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
tells	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
recipient	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
randomly	O	O	O	O	O	O
selected	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
compensated	O	O	O	O	O	O
financially	O	O	O	O	O	O
due	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
outbreak	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
Epidemic	O	O	O	O	O	O
outbreak	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
goes	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
say	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
recipient	O	O	O	O	O	O
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
paid	O	O	O	O	O	O
through	O	O	O	O	O	O
our	O	O	O	O	O	O
paying	O	O	O	O	O	O
center	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
london	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
SIC	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
your	O	O	O	O	O	O
compensation	O	O	O	O	O	O
payment	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
International	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Monetary	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Fund	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Office	O	O	O	O	O	O
treasury	O	O	O	O	O	O
account	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

To	O	O	O	O	O	O
obtain	O	O	O	O	O	O
these	O	O	O	O	O	O
funds	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
recipient	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
instructed	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
view	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
attached	O	O	O	O	O	O
file	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
print	O	O	O	O	O	O
your	O	O	O	O	O	O
winning	O	O	O	O	O	O
confirmation	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
attachment	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
malicious	O	O	O	O	O	O
HTML	O	O	O	O	O	O
attachment	O	O	O	O	O	O
titled	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID18	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
COMPENSATION.html	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
note	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
error	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID18	O	O	O	O	O	O
rather	O	O	O	O	O	O
than	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID19	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

When	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
attachment	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
opened	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
displays	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
fake	O	O	O	O	O	O
Microsoft	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Excel	O	O	O	O	O	O
branded	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
asks	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
recipient	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
password	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
shown	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
6	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
Covid	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
Microsoft	O	O	O	O	O	O
Excel	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landing	O	O	O	O	O	O
Page	O	O	O	O	O	O
Example	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
image	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O
base64	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
removed	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
6	O	O	O	O	O	O
Fake	O	O	O	O	O	O
WHO	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
IMF	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Compensation	O	O	O	O	O	O
Malicious	O	O	O	O	O	O
Attachment	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Credit	O	O	O	O	O	O
Card	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
Themed	O	O	O	O	O	O
Attacks	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Credential	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Credit	O	O	O	O	O	O
Card	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phish	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
Claim	O	O	O	O	O	O
Your	O	O	O	O	O	O
Covid	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cash	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
Major	O	O	O	O	O	O
U.S	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
Credit	O	O	O	O	O	O
Card	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Key	O	O	O	O	O	O
Points	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
The	O	O	O	O	O	O
message	O	O	O	O	O	O
below	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
part	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
small	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
attempts	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
steal	O	O	O	O	O	O
user	O	O	O	O	O	O
IDs	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
passwords	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
credit	O	O	O	O	O	O
card	O	O	O	O	O	O
numbers	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
targets	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
security	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
technology	O	O	O	O	O	O
organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
uses	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
subject	O	O	O	O	O	O
line	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
Claim	O	O	O	O	O	O
Your	O	O	O	O	O	O
Covid	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cash	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

To	O	O	O	O	O	O
increase	O	O	O	O	O	O
creditability	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
claims	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
come	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
major	O	O	O	O	O	O
United	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
credit	O	O	O	O	O	O
card	O	O	O	O	O	O
company	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
promises	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
waive	O	O	O	O	O	O
late	O	O	O	O	O	O
fees	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
issue	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
credit	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
up	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
US	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
$5,000	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
Credit	O	O	O	O	O	O
Card	O	O	O	O	O	O
Themed	O	O	O	O	O	O
Covid	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
Attack	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
image	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O
base64	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
removed	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
7	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Major	O	O	O	O	O	O
US	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Credit	O	O	O	O	O	O
Card	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
Claim	O	O	O	O	O	O
Your	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cash	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lure	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Credit	O	O	O	O	O	O
Card-Themed	O	O	O	O	O	O
Attacks	O	O	O	O	O	O
Summary	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
small	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
targets	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
security	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
technology	O	O	O	O	O	O
organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
arrives	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
subject	O	O	O	O	O	O
line	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
Claim	O	O	O	O	O	O
Your	O	O	O	O	O	O
Covid	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
Cash	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
claiming	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
come	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
major	O	O	O	O	O	O
United	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
credit	O	O	O	O	O	O
card	O	O	O	O	O	O
company	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
abuses	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
branding	O	O	O	O	O	O
extensively	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
indicates	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
l	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
ate	O	O	O	O	O	O
payment	O	O	O	O	O	O
fee	O	O	O	O	O	O
waived	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
credit	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
up	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
$5000	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
been	O	O	O	O	O	O
assigned	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
you	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
recipient	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
due	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
pandemic	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
contains	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
Claim	O	O	O	O	O	O
Now	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
link	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
takes	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
recipient	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
spoofed	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
credit	O	O	O	O	O	O
card	O	O	O	O	O	O
company	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
attempts	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
steal	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
user's	O	O	O	O	O	O
ID	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
password	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
credit	O	O	O	O	O	O
card	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
other	O	O	O	O	O	O
details	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Credit	O	O	O	O	O	O
Card	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
Major	O	O	O	O	O	O
UK	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Bank	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
Relief	O	O	O	O	O	O
measures	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Key	O	O	O	O	O	O
Points	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
If	O	O	O	O	O	O
recipients	O	O	O	O	O	O
click	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
relief	O	O	O	O	O	O
message	O	O	O	O	O	O
below	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
steal	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
personal	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
credit	O	O	O	O	O	O
card	O	O	O	O	O	O
numbers	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
part	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
large	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeting	O	O	O	O	O	O
manufacturing	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
technology	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
transportation	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
healthcare	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
aerospace	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
retail	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
energy	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
technology	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
business	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
services	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
hospitality	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
companies	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
claims	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
major	O	O	O	O	O	O
United	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Kingdom	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
bank	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
offers	O	O	O	O	O	O
300	O	O	O	O	O	O
SGD	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
Singapore	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
dollars	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
approximately	O	O	O	O	O	O
US	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
$210	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
Covid	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
Relief	O	O	O	O	O	O
Credit	O	O	O	O	O	O
Card	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
Email	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
image	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O
base64	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
removed	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
8	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Major	O	O	O	O	O	O
UK	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Bank	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
Relief	O	O	O	O	O	O
Measures	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lure	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
UK	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Bank	O	O	O	O	O	O
Credit	O	O	O	O	O	O
Card	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
Summary	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
large	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
primarily	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeting	O	O	O	O	O	O
manufacturing	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
technology	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
transportation	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
but	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
healthcare	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
aerospace	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
retail	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
energy	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
technology	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
business	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
services	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
hospitality	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
companies	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
claims	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
major	O	O	O	O	O	O
United	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Kingdom	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
bank	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
global	O	O	O	O	O	O
customers	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
spoofs	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
branding	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

These	O	O	O	O	O	O
emails	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
subject	O	O	O	O	O	O
line	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
Relief	O	O	O	O	O	O
measures	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
FINANCIAL	O	O	O	O	O	O
SUPPORT	O	O	O	O	O	O
WITH	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
names	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
bank	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
body	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
message	O	O	O	O	O	O
tells	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
recipient	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
bank	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
care	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
about	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
well-being	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
our	O	O	O	O	O	O
customers	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
community	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

To	O	O	O	O	O	O
ease	O	O	O	O	O	O
your	O	O	O	O	O	O
financial	O	O	O	O	O	O
burden	O	O	O	O	O	O
during	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
outbreak	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
offering	O	O	O	O	O	O
relief	O	O	O	O	O	O
measures	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
help	O	O	O	O	O	O
our	O	O	O	O	O	O
existing	O	O	O	O	O	O
credit	O	O	O	O	O	O
card	O	O	O	O	O	O
customers	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
offers	O	O	O	O	O	O
300	O	O	O	O	O	O
SGD	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
Singapore	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
dollars	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
approximately	O	O	O	O	O	O
US	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
$210	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
tells	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
recipient	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
Start	O	O	O	O	O	O
Here	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
claim	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
money	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
clicking	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
link	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
link	O	O	O	O	O	O
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
take	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
recipient	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
spoofed	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
bank	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
asks	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
name	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
address	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
credit	O	O	O	O	O	O
card	O	O	O	O	O	O
number	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
shown	O	O	O	O	O	O
below	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
9	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
Coronavirus	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bank	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
Landing	O	O	O	O	O	O
Page	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
image	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O
base64	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
removed	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
9	O	O	O	O	O	O
Major	O	O	O	O	O	O
UK	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
Bank	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
Relief	O	O	O	O	O	O
Measures	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
Page	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Conclusion	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
ongoing	O	O	O	O	O	O
shift	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
coronavirus-themed	O	O	O	O	O	O
messages	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaigns	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
truly	O	O	O	O	O	O
social	O	O	O	O	O	O
engineering	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
scale	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
these	O	O	O	O	O	O
recent	O	O	O	O	O	O
payment-related	O	O	O	O	O	O
lures	O	O	O	O	O	O
underscore	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
paying	O	O	O	O	O	O
attention	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
new	O	O	O	O	O	O
developments	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

We	O	O	O	O	O	O
anticipate	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
continue	O	O	O	O	O	O
modifying	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
strategies	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
news	O	O	O	O	O	O
surrounding	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
shifts	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

