<DOCSTART>	O	O	O	O	O	O

TA505	O	O	O	O	O	O
Malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
Threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
Insights	O	O	O	O	O	O

March	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
16	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE

Proofpoint	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
researchers	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
continuing	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
monitor	O	O	O	O	O	O
malicious	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
activity	O	O	O	O	O	O
surrounding	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

To	O	O	O	O	O	O
date	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
cumulative	O	O	O	O	O	O
volume	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
coronavirus-related	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
lures	O	O	O	O	O	O
now	O	O	O	O	O	O
represents	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
greatest	O	O	O	O	O	O
collection	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
attack	O	O	O	O	O	O
types	O	O	O	O	O	O
united	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
single	O	O	O	O	O	O
theme	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
our	O	O	O	O	O	O
team	O	O	O	O	O	O
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
years	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
if	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
ever	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

We	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
ve	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
credential	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
malicious	O	O	O	O	O	O
attachments	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
malicious	O	O	O	O	O	O
links	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
business	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
compromise	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
BEC	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.proofpoint.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
us	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
products	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
email-protection	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
email-fraud-defense	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
fake	O	O	O	O	O	O
landing	O	O	O	O	O	O
pages	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
downloaders	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
spam	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.proofpoint.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
us	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat-reference	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
among	O	O	O	O	O	O
others	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
all	O	O	O	O	O	O
leveraging	O	O	O	O	O	O
coronavirus	O	O	O	O	O	O
lures	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Over	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
past	O	O	O	O	O	O
week	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
team	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
TA505	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
behind	O	O	O	O	O	O
Locky	O	O	O	O	O	O
ransomware	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dridex	O	O	O	O	O	O
banking	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
Trojan	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
uses	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
coronavirus	O	O	O	O	O	O
lure	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
part	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
downloader	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeting	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
U.S	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
healthcare	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
manufacturing	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
pharmaceuticals	O	O	O	O	O	O
industries	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
team	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
found	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
separate	O	O	O	O	O	O
coronavirus-themed	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
uses	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
downloader	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
targets	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
healthcare	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
industry	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
demands	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bitcoin	O	O	O	O	O	O
payment	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Indicating	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
potential	O	O	O	O	O	O
future	O	O	O	O	O	O
shift	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
attack	O	O	O	O	O	O
landscape	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
downloaders	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
above	O	O	O	O	O	O
two	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaigns	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
sometimes	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
first	O	O	O	O	O	O
stage	O	O	O	O	O	O
payload	O	O	O	O	O	O
before	O	O	O	O	O	O
ransomware	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
later	O	O	O	O	O	O
downloaded	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
installed	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
victim	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
machine	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

[	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ransomware	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.proofpoint.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
us	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat-reference	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
ransomware	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
typically	O	O	O	O	O	O
delivered	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
either	O	O	O	O	O	O
second	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
later	O	O	O	O	O	O
stage	O	O	O	O	O	O
payload	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

We	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
ve	O	O	O	O	O	O
additionally	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
TA564	O	O	O	O	O	O
using	O	O	O	O	O	O
coronavirus	O	O	O	O	O	O
emails	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
target	O	O	O	O	O	O
Canadian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
users	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
spoofing	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Public	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Health	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Agency	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Canada	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
attempt	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
deliver	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ursnif	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
New	O	O	O	O	O	O
TA505	O	O	O	O	O	O
Malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
Examples	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O

As	O	O	O	O	O	O
everyone	O	O	O	O	O	O
around	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
world	O	O	O	O	O	O
continues	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
search	O	O	O	O	O	O
online	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
latest	O	O	O	O	O	O
developments	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
news	O	O	O	O	O	O
around	O	O	O	O	O	O
coronavirus	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Proofpoint	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
researchers	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
TA505	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
group	O	O	O	O	O	O
behind	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Locky	O	O	O	O	O	O
ransomware	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
using	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
coronavirus	O	O	O	O	O	O
lure	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
attempt	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
deliver	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
downloader	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
victim	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
computer	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Once	O	O	O	O	O	O
delivered	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
attackers	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
then	O	O	O	O	O	O
download	O	O	O	O	O	O
additional	O	O	O	O	O	O
types	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
including	O	O	O	O	O	O
banking	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
Trojans	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
ransomware	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

TA505	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
known	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
one	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
most	O	O	O	O	O	O
significant	O	O	O	O	O	O
financially	O	O	O	O	O	O
motivated	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
due	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
extraordinary	O	O	O	O	O	O
volumes	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
messages	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
send	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
one	O	O	O	O	O	O
below	O	O	O	O	O	O
shows	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
one	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
attempted	O	O	O	O	O	O
TA505	O	O	O	O	O	O
Coronavirus	O	O	O	O	O	O
attacks	O	O	O	O	O	O
purporting	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
contain	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
help	O	O	O	O	O	O
protect	O	O	O	O	O	O
users	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
friends	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
virus	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
urging	O	O	O	O	O	O
readers	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
click	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
link	O	O	O	O	O	O
provided	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ta505	O	O	O	O	O	O
Covid	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
Email	O	O	O	O	O	O
Example	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
sites	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
default	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
files	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2020	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
03	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
CV	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
TA505	O	O	O	O	O	O
Coronavirus	O	O	O	O	O	O
FAQ	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lure	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

We	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
separately	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
coronavirus-themed	O	O	O	O	O	O
emails	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
downloaders	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeting	O	O	O	O	O	O
healthcare	O	O	O	O	O	O
organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
request	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bitcoin	O	O	O	O	O	O
payments	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
below	O	O	O	O	O	O
shows	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
offering	O	O	O	O	O	O
coronavirus	O	O	O	O	O	O
remedies	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
exchange	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bitcoin	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ta505	O	O	O	O	O	O
Coronavirus	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ransomware	O	O	O	O	O	O
Email	O	O	O	O	O	O
Example	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
sites	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
default	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
files	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2020	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
03	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
CV	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
Coronavirus	O	O	O	O	O	O
Campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
Requesting	O	O	O	O	O	O
Bitcoin	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
Remedy	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

We	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
ve	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
TA564	O	O	O	O	O	O
using	O	O	O	O	O	O
coronavirus	O	O	O	O	O	O
emails	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeting	O	O	O	O	O	O
Canadian	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
users	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
spoofing	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Public	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Health	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Agency	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Canada	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
attempt	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
deliver	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ursnif	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Ursnif	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
common	O	O	O	O	O	O
banking	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
Trojan	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
steal	O	O	O	O	O	O
stored	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
including	O	O	O	O	O	O
passwords	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
banking	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
websites	O	O	O	O	O	O
via	O	O	O	O	O	O
web	O	O	O	O	O	O
injections	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
proxies	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
VNC	O	O	O	O	O	O
connections	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
3	O	O	O	O	O	O
below	O	O	O	O	O	O
shows	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
addressing	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
parents	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
guardians	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
reported	O	O	O	O	O	O
update	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Public	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Health	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Agency	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Canada	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
Medical	O	O	O	O	O	O
Officer	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Health	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
listing	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
individual	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
correct	O	O	O	O	O	O
name	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
Ta505	O	O	O	O	O	O
Coronavirus	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
Email	O	O	O	O	O	O
Example	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
sites	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
default	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
files	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
2020	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
03	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
CV	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
3	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
3	O	O	O	O	O	O
Fake	O	O	O	O	O	O
Public	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Health	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Agency	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
of	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Canada	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Lure	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Summary	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
TA505	O	O	O	O	O	O
Coronavirus	O	O	O	O	O	O
Attacks	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

We	O	O	O	O	O	O
anticipate	O	O	O	O	O	O
TA505	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
attackers	O	O	O	O	O	O
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
continue	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
leverage	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
detailed	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
our	O	O	O	O	O	O
new	O	O	O	O	O	O
Redline	O	O	O	O	O	O
Stealer	O	O	O	O	O	O
Threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
Insight	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
develops	O	O	O	O	O	O
further	O	O	O	O	O	O
worldwide	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
will	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
likely	O	O	O	O	O	O
pursue	O	O	O	O	O	O
potential	O	O	O	O	O	O
targets	O	O	O	O	O	O
who	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
now	O	O	O	O	O	O
being	O	O	O	O	O	O
asked	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
work	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
home	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Stay	O	O	O	O	O	O
vigilant	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
malicious	O	O	O	O	O	O
emails	O	O	O	O	O	O
regarding	O	O	O	O	O	O
remote	O	O	O	O	O	O
access	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
fake	O	O	O	O	O	O
corporate	O	O	O	O	O	O
websites	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
all	O	O	O	O	O	O
aimed	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
ensnaring	O	O	O	O	O	O
teleworkers	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

When	O	O	O	O	O	O
working	O	O	O	O	O	O
remotely	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
sure	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
use	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
secure	O	O	O	O	O	O
Wi-Fi	O	O	O	O	O	O
connection	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
protect	O	O	O	O	O	O
your	O	O	O	O	O	O
VPN	O	O	O	O	O	O
log-in	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
use	O	O	O	O	O	O
strong	O	O	O	O	O	O
passwords	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
think	O	O	O	O	O	O
twice	O	O	O	O	O	O
about	O	O	O	O	O	O
clicking	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
links	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
confirm	O	O	O	O	O	O
all	O	O	O	O	O	O
transactions	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
authentic	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

We	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
ll	O	O	O	O	O	O
continue	O	O	O	O	O	O
posting	O	O	O	O	O	O
future	O	O	O	O	O	O
TA505	O	O	O	O	O	O
attack	O	O	O	O	O	O
news	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
well	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
coronavirus	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaigns	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
insights	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
our	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
research	O	O	O	O	O	O
Twitter	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
account	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
twitter.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
threatinsight	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
twitter.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
threatinsight	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
You	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
review	O	O	O	O	O	O
additional	O	O	O	O	O	O
coronavirus-themed	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
examples	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
conspiracy	O	O	O	O	O	O
theories	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.proofpoint.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
us	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
corporate-blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
post	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
attackers-expand-coronavirus-themed-attacks-and-prey-conspiracy-theories	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
global	O	O	O	O	O	O
shipping	O	O	O	O	O	O
concerns	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.proofpoint.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
us	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
corporate-blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
post	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
coronavirus-themed-attacks-target-global-shipping-concerns	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
our	O	O	O	O	O	O
previous	O	O	O	O	O	O
posts	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

