<DOCSTART>	O	O	O	O	O	O

Attackers	O	O	O	O	O	O
Use	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lures	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
Spread	O	O	O	O	O	O
Malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
BEC	O	O	O	O	O	O

January	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
14	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2021	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE

Proofpoint	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
use	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
broad-scale	O	O	O	O	O	O
social	O	O	O	O	O	O
engineering	O	O	O	O	O	O
attacks	O	O	O	O	O	O
leading	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
credential	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
BEC	O	O	O	O	O	O
since	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
beginning	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
pandemic	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

We	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
themes	O	O	O	O	O	O
consistent	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
current	O	O	O	O	O	O
events	O	O	O	O	O	O
throughout	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
healthcare	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
crisis	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Initially	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
saw	O	O	O	O	O	O
lures	O	O	O	O	O	O
around	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
virus's	O	O	O	O	O	O
existence	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
then	O	O	O	O	O	O
turned	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
ancillary	O	O	O	O	O	O
lures	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
medical	O	O	O	O	O	O
supply	O	O	O	O	O	O
shortages	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

As	O	O	O	O	O	O
anticipated	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
last	O	O	O	O	O	O
two	O	O	O	O	O	O
months	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Proofpoint	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
researchers	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
attacks	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
leverage	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
news	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
approvals	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
world	O	O	O	O	O	O
governments	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
logistics	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
deployment	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
distribution	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
frontline	O	O	O	O	O	O
responders	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
other	O	O	O	O	O	O
individuals	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
provide	O	O	O	O	O	O
examples	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
email-borne	O	O	O	O	O	O
attacks	O	O	O	O	O	O
spreading	O	O	O	O	O	O
malware	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
BEC	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
These	O	O	O	O	O	O
examples	O	O	O	O	O	O
exemplify	O	O	O	O	O	O
abuse	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
popular	O	O	O	O	O	O
brands	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
WHO	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
DHL	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
manufacturers	O	O	O	O	O	O
delivered	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
users	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
located	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
United	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Canada	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Austria	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Germany	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
lure	O	O	O	O	O	O
themes	O	O	O	O	O	O
leveraged	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
range	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
topics	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
including	O	O	O	O	O	O
fear	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
person	O	O	O	O	O	O
had	O	O	O	O	O	O
encountered	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
infected	O	O	O	O	O	O
individual	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O
government	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
approvals	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
economic	O	O	O	O	O	O
recovery	O	O	O	O	O	O
fueled	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
well	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
sign	O	O	O	O	O	O
up	O	O	O	O	O	O
forms	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
receive	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
updates	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
shipment	O	O	O	O	O	O
delivery	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
Anticipation	O	O	O	O	O	O
Merger	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Acquisition	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
BEC	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
A	O	O	O	O	O	O
malicious	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
purporting	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
executive	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
asking	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
recipient	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
cooperation	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
confidential	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
acquisition	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

From	O	O	O	O	O	O
December	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
1	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
December	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
15	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Proofpoint	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
large	O	O	O	O	O	O
BEC	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
thousands	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
emails	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
spoofing	O	O	O	O	O	O
executives	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
attempting	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
elicit	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
recipient's	O	O	O	O	O	O
support	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
bogus	O	O	O	O	O	O
merger	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
acquisition	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

These	O	O	O	O	O	O
emails	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeted	O	O	O	O	O	O
various	O	O	O	O	O	O
personnel	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
roles	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vice	O	O	O	O	O	O
President	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
General	O	O	O	O	O	O
Manager	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Managing	O	O	O	O	O	O
Director	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
emails	O	O	O	O	O	O
were	O	O	O	O	O	O
primarily	O	O	O	O	O	O
sent	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
companies	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
United	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

These	O	O	O	O	O	O
emails	O	O	O	O	O	O
projected	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccines	O	O	O	O	O	O
would	O	O	O	O	O	O
fuel	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
world's	O	O	O	O	O	O
economic	O	O	O	O	O	O
recovery	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
purported	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
executive	O	O	O	O	O	O
asking	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
recipient	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
cooperation	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
confidential	O	O	O	O	O	O
acquisition	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
foreign	O	O	O	O	O	O
company	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

It	O	O	O	O	O	O
claimed	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
opportune	O	O	O	O	O	O
moment	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
make	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
acquisition	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
midst	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
every	O	O	O	O	O	O
crisis	O	O	O	O	O	O
lies	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
great	O	O	O	O	O	O
opportunity	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
Office	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
365	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
Email	O	O	O	O	O	O
screenshot	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
malicious	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Office	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
365	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
URL	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
3	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
landing	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
red	O	O	O	O	O	O
button	O	O	O	O	O	O
asking	O	O	O	O	O	O
users	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
Login	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
office	O	O	O	O	O	O
365	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
medium-sized	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
hundreds	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
messages	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
began	O	O	O	O	O	O
delivering	O	O	O	O	O	O
messages	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
January	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
1	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2021	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
over	O	O	O	O	O	O
four	O	O	O	O	O	O
days	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeting	O	O	O	O	O	O
dozens	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
different	O	O	O	O	O	O
industries	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
United	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Canada	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
emails	O	O	O	O	O	O
urged	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
potential	O	O	O	O	O	O
victims	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
click	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
link	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
confirm	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
receive	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
goal	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
steal	O	O	O	O	O	O
Office	O	O	O	O	O	O
365	O	O	O	O	O	O
login	O	O	O	O	O	O
credentials	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
password	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
notable	O	O	O	O	O	O
because	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
capitalized	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
recent	O	O	O	O	O	O
government	O	O	O	O	O	O
approval	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccines	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
rush	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
receive	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Specifically	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
talks	O	O	O	O	O	O
about	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
Government	O	O	O	O	O	O
approval	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
provides	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
link	O	O	O	O	O	O
where	O	O	O	O	O	O
one	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
supposedly	O	O	O	O	O	O
register	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
receive	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

At	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
time	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
United	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
still	O	O	O	O	O	O
available	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
first	O	O	O	O	O	O
responders	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
doctors	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
front	O	O	O	O	O	O
lines	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
also	O	O	O	O	O	O
abused	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
brands	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
manufacturers	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
lure	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
some	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
emails	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Other	O	O	O	O	O	O
emails	O	O	O	O	O	O
did	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
mention	O	O	O	O	O	O
specific	O	O	O	O	O	O
brands	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Example	O	O	O	O	O	O
subjects	O	O	O	O	O	O
included	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vaccine	B-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	B-SECTOR
manufacturer	I-SECTOR	O	O	O	O	I-SECTOR
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
40	O	O	O	O	O	O
Million	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
Dose	O	O	O	O	O	O
Supply	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
Vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O

#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
Complete	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
task	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
me	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
before	O	O	O	O	O	O
I	O	O	O	O	O	O
leave	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
covid	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
meeting	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
BEC	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
4	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Email	O	O	O	O	O	O
screenshot	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
malicious	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
asking	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
recipient	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
personal	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

On	O	O	O	O	O	O
January	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
11	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Proofpoint	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
researchers	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
another	O	O	O	O	O	O
small	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
under	O	O	O	O	O	O
100	O	O	O	O	O	O
emails	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
BEC	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
emails	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeted	O	O	O	O	O	O
various	O	O	O	O	O	O
industries	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
United	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
another	O	O	O	O	O	O
excellent	O	O	O	O	O	O
example	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
BEC	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
picking	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
lures	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
attempt	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
exploit	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
targets	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
specific	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
only	O	O	O	O	O	O
mentions	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
meeting	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
passing	O	O	O	O	O	O
;	O	O	O	O	O	O
however	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
adds	O	O	O	O	O	O
urgency—a	O	O	O	O	O	O
common	O	O	O	O	O	O
BEC	O	O	O	O	O	O
technique—to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
follow-up	O	O	O	O	O	O
request	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
Please	O	O	O	O	O	O
give	O	O	O	O	O	O
me	O	O	O	O	O	O
your	O	O	O	O	O	O
personal	O	O	O	O	O	O
number	O	O	O	O	O	O
?	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
attempts	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
increase	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
stress	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
giving	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
recipient	O	O	O	O	O	O
less	O	O	O	O	O	O
time	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
think	O	O	O	O	O	O
about	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
response	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
allowing	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
attacker	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
pivot	O	O	O	O	O	O
outside	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
protected	O	O	O	O	O	O
ecosystem	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
AgentTesla	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Malware	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
5	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Agent	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tesla	O	O	O	O	O	O
abuses	O	O	O	O	O	O
World	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Health	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Organization	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Brand	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

On	O	O	O	O	O	O
January	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
12	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Proofpoint	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
medium-sized	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
several	O	O	O	O	O	O
hundred	O	O	O	O	O	O
messages	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeting	O	O	O	O	O	O
many	O	O	O	O	O	O
industries	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
United	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
contained	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
attachment	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
DOWNLOAD-NEW	O	O	O	O	O	O
VACCINES-COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
REPORT-SAFETY1	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
xlsx.iso	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
included	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
embedded	O	O	O	O	O	O
executable	O	O	O	O	O	O
file	O	O	O	O	O	O
named	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
DOWNLOAD-NEW	O	O	O	O	O	O
VACCINES-COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
REPORT-SAFETY1	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
xlsx.exe	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
executable	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
if	O	O	O	O	O	O
run	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
user	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
drops	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
runs	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
AgentTesla	O	O	O	O	O	O
keylogger	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
notable	O	O	O	O	O	O
due	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
subject	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
APPROVED	O	O	O	O	O	O
NEW	O	O	O	O	O	O
VACCINES	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
lure	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
abuse	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
World	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Health	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Organization	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
logo	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
name	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Additionally	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Proofpoint	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
has	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
specific	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
spreading	O	O	O	O	O	O
RATs	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
stealers	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
keyloggers	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
downloaders	O	O	O	O	O	O
since	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
least	O	O	O	O	O	O
2019	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
March	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
they	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
first	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
lures	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
since	O	O	O	O	O	O
then	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
watched	O	O	O	O	O	O
them	O	O	O	O	O	O
adapt	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
lures	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
current	O	O	O	O	O	O
news	O	O	O	O	O	O
cycles	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
include	O	O	O	O	O	O
mentions	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
DHL	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Themed	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
6	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
A	O	O	O	O	O	O
screenshot	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
purporting	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
inform	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
recipient	O	O	O	O	O	O
about	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
undelivered	O	O	O	O	O	O
DHL	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
package	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
7	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
landing	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
DHL	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
branding	O	O	O	O	O	O
asking	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
user	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
username	O	O	O	O	O	O
or	O	O	O	O	O	O
Email	O	O	O	O	O	O
address	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
password	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

On	O	O	O	O	O	O
January	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
14	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
 	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2021	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Proofpoint	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
researchers	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
medium-sized	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
hundreds	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
messages	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeting	O	O	O	O	O	O
dozens	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
different	O	O	O	O	O	O
industries	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
United	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
States	I-LOC	O	O	O	O	I-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Germany	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Austria	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
emails	O	O	O	O	O	O
urged	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
potential	O	O	O	O	O	O
victims	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
click	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
link	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
go	O	O	O	O	O	O
online	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
submit	O	O	O	O	O	O
your	O	O	O	O	O	O
correct	O	O	O	O	O	O
address	O	O	O	O	O	O
so	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
can	O	O	O	O	O	O
deliver	O	O	O	O	O	O
your	O	O	O	O	O	O
package	O	O	O	O	O	O
today	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
goal	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaign	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
steal	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
login	O	O	O	O	O	O
credentials	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
address	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
password	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

While	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
body	O	O	O	O	O	O
content	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
typical	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
package	O	O	O	O	O	O
delivery	O	O	O	O	O	O
service	O	O	O	O	O	O
phish	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
notable	O	O	O	O	O	O
difference	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
one	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
subject	O	O	O	O	O	O
variants	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
subject	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
distribution	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
Re-confirm	O	O	O	O	O	O
your	O	O	O	O	O	O
delivery	O	O	O	O	O	O
address	O	O	O	O	O	O
"	O	O	O	O	O	O
implied	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
recipient	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
specific	O	O	O	O	O	O
package	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
supposedly	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
Indicators	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Compromise	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
IOCs	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
IOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
IOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Type	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Description	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
bf78ad88ad9124adde7b3fdfb867b5e848d042ae56acbb75bcfd71962c6a5fd8	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
SHA256	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
DOWNLOAD-NEW	O	O	O	O	O	O
VACCINES-COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
REPORT-SAFETY1	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
xlsx.iso	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
2a0b7eba6ec8d395dcc4485e2369c2ec289819c378e0f1f81a87a7622e0da17c	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
SHA256	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
DOWNLOAD-NEW	O	O	O	O	O	O
VACCINES-COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
REPORT-SAFETY1	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
xlsx.exe	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
hxxp	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
putrajayagemilang	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
covid	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
vaccine	O	O	O	O	O	O
\	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
delivery	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
dh	O	O	O	O	O	O
?	O	O	O	O	O	O
lo	O	O	O	O	O	O
=	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
base64	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
recipient	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
URL	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
January	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
14	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2021	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
DHL	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
themed	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
link	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

