<DOCSTART>	O	O	O	O	O	O

Agile	O	O	O	O	O	O
Threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
Actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pivot	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
Voter	O	O	O	O	O	O
Registration	O	O	O	O	O	O
Themes	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
Phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
Lures	O	O	O	O	O	O

October	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
14	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
rise	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
election-themed	O	O	O	O	O	O
messages	O	O	O	O	O	O
continues	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
recent	O	O	O	O	O	O
campaigns	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
U.S	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
President	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
health	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
twitter.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
threatinsight	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
status	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
1313860463495704578	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
Democratic	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
National	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Committee	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.proofpoint.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
us	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat-insight	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
emotet-makes-timely-adoption-political-and-elections-lures	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
now	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
impersonating	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
U.S	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
Election	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Assistance	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Commission	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
blog.knowbe4	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
malicious-actors-crash-u.s	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
election-spoofed-emails-attempt-to-gather-u.s	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
voter-registration-data	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
EAC	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
spotted	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
security	O	O	O	O	O	O
researchers	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
KnowBe4	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
latest	O	O	O	O	O	O
messages	O	O	O	O	O	O
spoof	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
voter	O	O	O	O	O	O
registration	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
attempt	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
collect	O	O	O	O	O	O
personally	O	O	O	O	O	O
identifiable	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
PII	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Proofpoint	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
researchers	O	O	O	O	O	O
identified	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
similar	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
messages	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
our	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
well	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
additional	O	O	O	O	O	O
credential	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishkits	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
same	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
detail	O	O	O	O	O	O
below	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
Impersonating	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Election	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Assistance	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Commission	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
Email	O	O	O	O	O	O
lure	O	O	O	O	O	O
impersonating	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
sites	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
default	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
files	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
inline-images	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
figure1	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
email_lure.png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
1	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
Email	O	O	O	O	O	O
lure	O	O	O	O	O	O
impersonating	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Election	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Assistance	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Commission	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

Hundreds	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
messages	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
subjects	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
voter	O	O	O	O	O	O
registration	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
application	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
details	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
couldnt	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
confirmed	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
sic	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
your	O	O	O	O	O	O
county	O	O	O	O	O	O
clerk	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
couldnt	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
confirm	O	O	O	O	O	O
voter	O	O	O	O	O	O
registration	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
sic	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
were	O	O	O	O	O	O
sent	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
recipients	O	O	O	O	O	O
across	O	O	O	O	O	O
hundreds	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
organizations	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
though	O	O	O	O	O	O
there	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
no	O	O	O	O	O	O
clear	O	O	O	O	O	O
targeting	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
any	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
specific	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
industry	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

All	O	O	O	O	O	O
messages	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
sent	O	O	O	O	O	O
via	O	O	O	O	O	O
SendGrid	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
purport	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
eac	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
@	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
usa	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
gov	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
does	O	O	O	O	O	O
not	O	O	O	O	O	O
appear	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
be	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
official	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
address	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
legitimate	O	O	O	O	O	O
EAC	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.eac.gov	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
link	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
reconfirm	O	O	O	O	O	O
application	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
takes	O	O	O	O	O	O
users	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
now-defunct	O	O	O	O	O	O
landing	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
astragolf	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
voting	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
was	O	O	O	O	O	O
likely	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
compromised	O	O	O	O	O	O
WordPress	O	O	O	O	O	O
install	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
landing	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
impersonates	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
ServiceArizona	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
servicearizona.com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
VoterRegistration	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
selectLanguage	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
though	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
messages	O	O	O	O	O	O
were	O	O	O	O	O	O
sent	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
recipients	O	O	O	O	O	O
across	O	O	O	O	O	O
multiple	O	O	O	O	O	O
states	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
landing	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
sites	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
default	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
files	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
inline-images	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
figure2	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
voter_reg_land.png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
Information	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
landing	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
impersonating	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
ServiceArizona	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
Pivoting	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
find	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishkits	O	O	O	O	O	O

Proofpoint	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
collects	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishkits	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.usenix.org	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
legacy	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
event	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
woot08	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
tech	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
full_papers	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
cova	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
cova_html	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
which	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
complete	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
web	O	O	O	O	O	O
sites	O	O	O	O	O	O
contained	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
ready-to-deploy	O	O	O	O	O	O
package	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

We	O	O	O	O	O	O
found	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
above	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishkit	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
our	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

While	O	O	O	O	O	O
examining	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
found	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
POST	O	O	O	O	O	O
request	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
POST	O	O	O	O	O	O
request	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
sites	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
default	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
files	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
inline-images	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
figure3	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishkit_post.png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
3	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
POST	O	O	O	O	O	O
request	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
voter	O	O	O	O	O	O
registration	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

We	O	O	O	O	O	O
searched	O	O	O	O	O	O
our	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
additional	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishkits	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
POSTing	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
address	O	O	O	O	O	O
above	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
obiri409	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
@	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
gmail	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
com	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
found	O	O	O	O	O	O
several	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
pages	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
likely	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
same	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
mid-June	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
promise	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
business	O	O	O	O	O	O
grant	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
collect	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
users	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
hosted	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
yard65	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
net	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
plugins	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
hello-doly	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
HM	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
4	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Interestingly	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
while	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
voter	O	O	O	O	O	O
registration	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
phish	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
US-themed	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
business	O	O	O	O	O	O
grant	O	O	O	O	O	O
references	O	O	O	O	O	O
UK-based	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
entities	O	O	O	O	O	O
like	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
HM	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Revenue	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
and	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Customs	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
https	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
www.gov.uk	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
government	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
organisations	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
hm-revenue-customs	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
business	O	O	O	O	O	O
grant	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
sites	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
default	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
files	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
inline-images	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
figure4	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
covid_grant.png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
4	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
business	O	O	O	O	O	O
grant	O	O	O	O	O	O
themed	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
POSTing	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
obiri409	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
@	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
gmail	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
com	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
late	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
August	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
same	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
used	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
PayPal	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
themed	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
landing	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
hosted	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
urbanheights	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
fullz	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
below	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
5	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
payPal	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
sites	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
default	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
files	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
inline-images	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
figure5	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
paypal_phish.png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
5	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
PayPal	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
POSTing	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
obiri409	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
@	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
gmail	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
com	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
early	O	O	O	O	O	O
October	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
identified	O	O	O	O	O	O
another	O	O	O	O	O	O
voter	O	O	O	O	O	O
registration	O	O	O	O	O	O
impersonation	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
nearly	O	O	O	O	O	O
identical	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
original	O	O	O	O	O	O
voter	O	O	O	O	O	O
registration	O	O	O	O	O	O
landing	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
began	O	O	O	O	O	O
investigating	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

One	O	O	O	O	O	O
small	O	O	O	O	O	O
detail	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
different	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
replacement	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Arizona	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
MVP	O	O	O	O	O	O
logo	O	O	O	O	O	O
with	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Election	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Assistance	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Commission	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figures	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
6	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
8	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
hosted	O	O	O	O	O	O
at	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
“	O	O	O	O	O	O
bisonengineers	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
voting	O	O	O	O	O	O
”	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
though	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
were	O	O	O	O	O	O
unable	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
capture	O	O	O	O	O	O
POST	O	O	O	O	O	O
data	O	O	O	O	O	O
for	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
striking	O	O	O	O	O	O
similarity	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
both	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
look	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
use	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
compromised	O	O	O	O	O	O
WordPress	O	O	O	O	O	O
install	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
suggests	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
same	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
Information	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
landing	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
sites	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
default	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
files	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
inline-images	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
figure6	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
new_voter_reg_phish.JPG	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
6	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Information	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
landing	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
impersonating	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
Election	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Assistance	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Commission	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
nearly	O	O	O	O	O	O
identical	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
seen	O	O	O	O	O	O
previously	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
2	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

!	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
Information	O	O	O	O	O	O
phish	O	O	O	O	O	O
landing	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
seeking	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
sensitive	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
sites	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
default	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
files	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
inline-images	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
figure7	O	O	O	O	O	O
_	O	O	O	O	O	O
voter_reg_part3	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
png	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

*	O	O	O	O	O	O
Figure	O	O	O	O	O	O
7	O	O	O	O	O	O
:	O	O	O	O	O	O
Information	O	O	O	O	O	O
phish	O	O	O	O	O	O
landing	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
seeking	O	O	O	O	O	O
more	O	O	O	O	O	O
sensitive	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
such	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
Social	O	O	O	O	O	O
Security	O	O	O	O	O	O
Number	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
Tax	O	O	O	O	O	O
ID	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
Driver	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
s	O	O	O	O	O	O
License	O	O	O	O	O	O
number	O	O	O	O	O	O
*	O	O	O	O	O	O

#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
Conclusion	O	O	O	O	O	O

Threat	O	O	O	O	O	O
actors	O	O	O	O	O	O
often	O	O	O	O	O	O
draw	O	O	O	O	O	O
inspiration	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
current	O	O	O	O	O	O
events	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
brand	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
malicious	O	O	O	O	O	O
messages	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

In	O	O	O	O	O	O
these	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
examples	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
Proofpoint	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
pivot	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
ever-present	O	O	O	O	O	O
PayPal	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
themes	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
-	O	O	O	O	O	O
19	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
business	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
grants	O	O	O	O	O	O
during	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
summer	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
when	O	O	O	O	O	O
many	O	O	O	O	O	O
businesses	O	O	O	O	O	O
were	O	O	O	O	O	O
reeling	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
economic	O	O	O	O	O	O
effects	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
global	O	O	O	O	O	O
pandemic	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Now	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
as	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
US	B-LOC	O	O	O	O	B-LOC
election	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
draws	O	O	O	O	O	O
closer	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
many	O	O	O	O	O	O
individuals	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
confirming	O	O	O	O	O	O
their	O	O	O	O	O	O
voter	O	O	O	O	O	O
registration	O	O	O	O	O	O
status	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

Using	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
messages	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
suggest	O	O	O	O	O	O
voter	O	O	O	O	O	O
registration	O	O	O	O	O	O
is	O	O	O	O	O	O
invalid	O	O	O	O	O	O
drives	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
user	O	O	O	O	O	O
urgency	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
uncertainty	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
an	O	O	O	O	O	O
election	O	O	O	O	O	O
season	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
last	O	O	O	O	O	O
messages	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
from	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
using	O	O	O	O	O	O
voter	O	O	O	O	O	O
registration	O	O	O	O	O	O
themes	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
were	O	O	O	O	O	O
sent	O	O	O	O	O	O
on	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
October	O	O	B-DATE	O	O	B-DATE
7	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
,	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
2020	O	O	I-DATE	O	O	I-DATE
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

This	O	O	O	O	O	O
suggests	O	O	O	O	O	O
that	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
may	O	O	O	O	O	O
have	O	O	O	O	O	O
already	O	O	O	O	O	O
shifted	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
another	O	O	O	O	O	O
type	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
lure	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

The	O	O	O	O	O	O
major	O	O	O	O	O	O
changes	O	O	O	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O	O	O	O
are	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
branding	O	O	O	O	O	O
only–the	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor	O	O	O	O	O	O
continues	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
use	O	O	O	O	O	O
similar	O	O	O	O	O	O
UI	O	O	O	O	O	O
elements	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
backend	O	O	O	O	O	O
code	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
evidenced	O	O	O	O	O	O
by	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
POST	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
user-supplied	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
same	O	O	O	O	O	O
email	O	O	O	O	O	O
address	O	O	O	O	O	O
across	O	O	O	O	O	O
multiple	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
phishing	O	O	O	O	O	O
operations	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

As	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
election	O	O	O	O	O	O
fades	O	O	O	O	O	O
and	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
a	O	O	O	O	O	O
new	O	O	O	O	O	O
story	O	O	O	O	O	O
dominates	O	O	O	O	O	O
the	O	O	O	O	O	O
headlines	O	O	O	O	O	O
,	O	O	O	O	O	O
we	O	O	O	O	O	O
’	O	O	O	O	O	O
ll	O	O	O	O	O	O
likely	O	O	O	O	O	O
see	O	O	O	O	O	O
this	O	O	O	O	O	O
actor–and	O	O	O	O	O	O
others	O	O	O	O	O	O
like	O	O	O	O	O	O
them–pivot	O	O	O	O	O	O
once	O	O	O	O	O	O
again	O	O	O	O	O	O
to	O	O	O	O	O	O
take	O	O	O	O	O	O
advantage	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
current	O	O	O	O	O	O
events	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O

#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
#	O	O	O	O	O	O
Indicators	O	O	O	O	O	O
of	O	O	O	O	O	O
Compromise	O	O	O	O	O	O
(	O	O	O	O	O	O
IOCs	O	O	O	O	O	O
)	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
IOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
IOC	O	O	O	O	O	O
Type	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
Description	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
astragolf	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
it	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
voting	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
URL	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
ServiceArizona-themed	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
phish	O	O	O	O	O	O
landing	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
urbanheights	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
in	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
fullz	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
URL	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
PayPal-themed	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
phish	O	O	O	O	O	O
landing	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
yard65	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
net	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
plugins	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
hello-doly	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
HM	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
URL	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
COVID	O	O	O	O	O	O
business	O	O	O	O	O	O
grant-themed	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
phish	O	O	O	O	O	O
landing	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

|	O	O	O	O	O	O
bisonengineers	O	O	O	O	O	O
[	O	O	O	O	O	O
.	O	O	O	O	O	O
]	O	O	O	O	O	O
com	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
wp-content	O	O	O	O	O	O
/	O	O	O	O	O	O
voting	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
URL	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O
Election	B-ORG	O	O	O	O	B-ORG
Assistance	I-ORG	O	O	O	O	I-ORG
Commission-themed	O	O	O	O	O	O
information	O	O	O	O	O	O
phish	O	O	O	O	O	O
landing	O	O	O	O	O	O
page	O	O	O	O	O	O
 	O	O	O	O	O	O
|	O	O	O	O	O	O

